Night Sky Patrol
of Tomorrow
I do whatever suits my mood, a boy picking out enemies and fighting
No hopes for the future, I waited to be drawn in a dream
And yet I fear the future,
hating tomorrow,
wishing towards the past
There's no longer anything
I can do, so I shout out,
"Tomorrow, please, don't come,"
Leaving the old me behind,
the moon sets, and the sun rises
But that night was different from all the others ―
when you took my hand...
The Big Dipper's first star illuminates the darkness, dancing into the sky and beyond this world
"Let's start facing towards tomorrow again,
both you and me."
"If this is to end as a dream,
at least allow me to change yesterday..."
I won't say anything like that,
so let me keep smiling together with you
tomorrow as well
Ever since then, the world's been completely different ―
That's what I honestly believed
Yet no matter how much I tried to hope or change,
the future was cruel
Even so, the world I always watched with you
was truly beautiful
I still haven't forgotten that,
I've put an end to it all so I can remember
Daydreaming about flying with or without you,
or even just taking a walk alone
I can't do either of those, and begged for someone to break down
the illusions formed from the indigo wind
"If you want it, then make it come true yourself,"
said...
You
said that...
I think about how I want to go see you again tomorrow night,
but I don't know, maybe you won't be there
But even so, we will always be one
So, see you later, Sky Arrow
Let's smile on
I want to be together
with you in the future,
however short our time may be, so I'll shout out
"Remember this day
someday in the future,
whoever we may be then..."
Night Sky Patrol
of Tomorrow