Those who pretend to be incompetent beings
Simply want to be told that they aren't useless
And their days go on, lulled into a sense of security
Are you satisfied with that?
Kick it back easy, and you're done?
Are you a fool...?
An unending cycle within your chest
The subsistence of life spent in a cocoon
Let us become a little stronger than who we were yesterday
And let us grow a little kinder
Not everyone knows how to deal
Act so that you will not come to hate your helpless self...
Tear through
Let us tear though the present and be reborn
Adding up the division of cells in your body and heart,
every day's your birthday
Living without wavering
Is something only people with one-celled brains can do
That's why today, as your cells are born as they should be, you waver
You're no one, but you're you
How long will you act like a brat?
Always looking for an escape route?
Pick up the pace!
Tear through
Let us tear through the past and be reborn
Close your eyes, and in the pure-white darkness is the origin of space
Never be sorry
You may reflect on your actions, but never repent
You may acknowledge your incompetent self as such, but never hate yourself
However...
Flowers want to bloom
Birds want to fly
I want to eat delicious foods
Likewise, as long as you're you,
I want you to be by my side...
In your chest...
You nurture a cocoon
One containing a world infinitely large
Eternal catharsis
Tear through
Let us tear though the present and be reborn
Adding up the division of cells in your body and heart,
every day's your birthday
Born into this good-for-nothing world
Life is more than enduring and staying alive
You're in the middle of evolution, one heading in a positive direction...