Nemesis of the Ruined Kingdom
The children who stand on the scorched plains
continue to dig graves with their powerless hands
Atop the scarred battlefield, they covered the bodies
of nameless boys and the remaining corpses, with earth
Steal, be stolen from; What remains is despair
The consequence of mutual loathing
As I embrace a cold corpse,
Each time still-warm eyes begin to shut,
I sobbed, choked with tears
To grieve for those short-lived, lost lives, I can only mourn
Is there anything I can protect with my own hands?
So we may someday put a stop to this unending war,
So we will no longer have war as well,
we'll live on
Inside, we shared our unhealing wounds
Believe in what we'd spoken about,
in the promise we'd made as children; I swear I will fulfill it with my own hands
Time flows on, forgetting the past
How much longer will this blood-stained lineage continue?
Atop the stolen land, carrying hopes, I draw my sword
and met you, from memories long ago, on the other side of my blade
Believe in the you I'd known, and move forwards,
I'd searched for so long
Now, you're right before my eyes ―
for you, and now you're here; We ―
How can we fight?
Without wiping my overflowing tears, I face the blade
If you could allow me to atone,
Return our destroyed future, return our country, I shout out
I'll protect our future, protect you, I shout out
...but my voice doesn't reach
My words no longer reaching, I continue to receive your blade
I'd believed in, and continued to wait for you
The promise we'd made as children has disappeared, unfulfilled
Short-lived, fallen tears, and the buds left behind, connect to the future
If those lives bet cannot be repaid,
So I may protect the future we'd both dreamed of,
In order to steal and throw away those dreams of the future,
I will fight
Deceiving even my heart, I point my blade at you
I will believe in and continue to wait for you
until I fulfill the promise from those foolish days with my own hands
Song: Hitoshizuku x Yama△
Illustrations: Suzunosuke
Video: Hitoshizuku
Nemesis of the Ruined Kingdom