I,
you,
←that guy,
I,
you,
←that guy,
this guy,→
you,
←that guy,
this guy,→
whoever else too,
are just common idiots (conclusion)
so,
with anonymous hopes,
let's play
now
good-bye, triangles,
a square,
bye!
good-bye, triangles,
a square,
bye
Literature Girl
Insane
just between us
Yo.
Welcome
to the
Bourbon
house.
This
tequila
is on
the house,
so
first
of all,
please
take a
drink
and relax.
Yeah, "again".
My apologies.
They say,
"even the
buddha
gets angry
if hit", so
I don’t think
you’ll forgive
me even if
I apologize.
But, when
you saw
this
keyword,
you were
surely
speechless
and felt
something
like "your
heart
throbbing".
In this
brutal
world, I
want you
to not
forget
such
feelings.
You
thought
so, and
some time
ago wrote
"just
between
us".
beginning
I am a cat,
my name is...
whatever
.         .
.                     .
←I didn't know that
is what it’s called (valid)
aspiring hearts, even when we have them
people without ambition are
foolish
aspiring hearts, even when we have them
"idiots"
is what we're called (after all)
lives full of shame
sink
the slanted
sun
rolling with laughter and turning into clowns
human disqualification
goodbye.
(ha)
if we escaped from the tunnel,
it’d be a disastrous scene
now,
[interjection]
let’s
escape
but,
→（English..﻿ｂｕｔ）
I wonder?
where,
(so-called)
the
track
to the
ideal country
after
all,
even if we
cry,
make
noise,
shout,
cry,
make
noise,
shout,
go
mad,
the world won't
change
255: Anonymous
↓sad sight hahahahahaha
256: Anonymous
↓rofl hahahahahahaha
257: Anonymous
what could you be planning hahahahahaha
258: Anonymous
won't change hahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
259: Anonymous
so,
let's get a lemon bomb
"Ahh, that’s right, that's right." At that moment, I remembered the lemon in my sleeve. The
books were just a pile of mixed up colors, I wanted to try out this lemon once. "That’s right".
The light excitement from before had returned to me. I grabbed whatever
I could, smashing and grabbing, unplugging, removing, pulling books
from the shelves. A strange and fantastic castle had, at that time, become
blue and red. At last, it was complete. Then, as I controlled my pounding
heart, I mounted the lemon gently on the drawbridge. Now it was good.
I looked at the lemon. Its yellow hue sucked in and absorbed the gradient
of clashing colors from within its spindle-shaped body, replacing them with clarity.
and set it!
now
together, with me,
let's play!
ah
I,
you,
that guy,
this
guy,
too
whoever else,
are just
idiots!
so,
with anonymous hopes,
let's play!
now!
good-bye, triangles,
a square
note: can’t read
Anonymous.
Reading too much      is this dangerous!
People who
read books
have a
100%
probability
of dying
within the
next 200 years.
The
probability
that a
perpetrator
will purchase
cup ramen
is much
higher than
the probability
that the same
culprit will buy
the nation
of Afghanistan.
Hey, it’s dangerous, isn’t it?
I think, therefore, I’m troubled
if we
doubt,
brittle
things are
broken
right now, why
am I
cry
ing?
right now, why
am I
beginning to rage?
things like the substance of the arts,
not knowing them is
happiness
God
has
died
brain-
washed
let's be
let's do that!
bleh!
should I be alive,
even?
should I be dead
I don't know!
but,
let’s decide!
even forcibly
popularity contest full of cheating
in a democratic way
vote count results!
Vote count results!
Conclusion: everyone dies excluding for the majority　Conclusion: everyone dies excluding the majority　Conclusion: everyone dies excluding for the majority
after
all,
even if we
cry,
make
noise,
shout,
cry,
make
noise,
shout,
go
mad,
the applause
is
great acclamation!
woooooooooooooooooooooooooooah
godly!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
world view-!
↑a person who doesn't understand what god is
goosebumps
hm...do I not like it...
this isn’t god hahahaha is your head okay? hahaha
crush------------------------!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
wherewherewherewherewherewherewhere
crush---------------------!!!!!!!!
so,
let's sing a
(certainly this song)
degraded copy
now!
let's do it like that and let's
live together!
ah
a b c d e
f g h i j k
l m n o p
q r s t u v
w x y z
pretend the alphabet has more letters
I,
you,
that guy,
this
guy,
whoever else, too
won't change!
so,
with an original style,
let's be proud!
now,
we’ve killed many
let's
laugh
!!!!!
if something is important, then
it’ll break and disappear
let's         cry
?? 「but, aren’t you a hindrance?
look
(pressing)
move to the side,
move
to
the
side,
like that, disappear 」
No Longer
Human
Daizai
Osamu
No Longer
Human
Daizai
Osamu
Kokoro
Natsume
Souseki
No Longer
Human
Daizai
Osamu
Kokoro
Natsume
Souseki
Yamanashi
Miyazawa Kenji
No Longer
Human
Daizai
Osamu
Kokoro
Natsume
Souseki
Yamanashi
Miyazawa Kenji
No Longer
Human
Daizai
Osamu
Kokoro
Natsume
Souseki
Yamanashi
Miyazawa Kenji
No Longer
Human
Daizai
Osamu
Kokoro
Natsume
Souseki
Yamanashi
Miyazawa Kenji
Lemon
Kajii Motojiro
brief blank space
anonymous
mind
exer
cises,
one
two
three
four
even if I try to think,
I don't kno~w!
(ha)
look,
aside from that,
like always,
give me the medicine
ahahahahahahahahahahaha
ahahahahahahaha
ahahahahaha
okay.
entrance (character) introduction
black cat
sitting
on a chair
(probably)
three
people’s
hands, one
insincere
hand
retro cabinet
book (inside the cabinet)
mysterious medicine
lemon
bicolor hat
spiderwort and a pearl necklace,
and then a book used under writing paper
mysterious black hand
red
flowers
lemon bomb
(included in book below)
hair
ornament
(older
sister's)
frame
a
comfortable-
looking
chair
books fluttering in the wind
hairpin
(twins)
hair ornament (older sister's)
daruma
relatively
new
brush
flag
countless others
revolutionary
pretension
ridicu-
lous
lead
tickets
let’s give them out,
let’s write with blood
a book of self-denial confessions
after
all,
even if we
cry,
make
noise,
shout,
cry,
make
noise,
shout,
go
mad,
the world won't
change
so,
clown
around
let’s delude!
now,
let’s gulp down
a cup
of
poison!
ah,
what a
foolish
painful
miserable
meaningless
thing, isn't it!
so,
Clammbon laughed
"kapukapu"
ah-
Be not Defeated by the Rain
hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
ha
ahahaha
hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
ha
haha...ha...
should I go forget, I wonder?
yes,
??「I was satisfied,
so,
I’ll disappear!」
Final Chapter
Literary Girl Insane
Volume Two 「Insanity Propaganda」
abnormal sentiment, the world dances
Find the 「ほ」！
seven
six
five
four
three
two
one
zero
end