...I hate this world...
No matter how hard you tried in life, you end up with nothing...
...respectable humans are hurt one after another...
...irrationality exists as if it's a fact...
I'll kill you.
The final days of the previous era.
An unknown particle called aether was discovered by a lone scientist.
And then, by further research, the mechanism by which aether's cycle influences biological evolution was explicated.
As a result, the soul's exterior was born, and it became so that the idea could have a large influence on each academic branch.
100 years after the discovery of aether.
Those in charge at the time placed restraints on a certain project.
For the sake of making the absoluteness of scientific progress known once again, after many repeated failures, there was only one successful experiment.
She was named Eve.
Project Houshin episode3
C.W.R./Control World Room
The 27th periodic inspection is planned for 3 pm today.
Preparations are progressing without any problems.
I see. How about Eve?
It seems like she's in the reference room at the moment.
I see.
On that subject, during the last time leap, we observed a large response in Eve's mental graph.
Since then, Eve's emotion levels have been climbing rapidly.
She's gradually becoming more and more humanlike.
Isn't that right?
The designated coordinates were from you, Professor Miranda, weren't they?
In the paper that the professor had published previously regarding the circle of birth, death, and rebirth, there certainly was an report case involving a time leap to the same coordinates.
Could there possibly a correlation?
Now, I wonder if there could?
Composition/Kamiuta & Hirata Junichi
Lyrics/Kamiuta
Singing/LIQU@.
Video/Nasuno
Project Houshin produced by Team Kamiuta
Control World Room
Composition/Kamiuta & Hirata Junichi
Lyrics/Kamiuta
Singing/LIQU@.
Video/Nasuno
Following a right face log, opposition to plastic
Time limit, trash lacking release
Time limit, trash lacking resources
trash lacking resources
So, I'll turn it black
If we can meet again, if we connect with each other again,
Stop the rhythm made by the soul
I float time on my index finger
This is an endless line from 1.0.0.0.
Hey, continue to spin
Overtaking blue tenderness,
bl
ue
beautiful lies should be able to be loved
If even the ability to expose is hidden,
is this love?
Is it really? Could it be?
Following a right about-face bug, opposition to physiology
Appending the instinct function left behind
I'm sorry, I'll turn it white
If I pray, if it's fulfilled,
I gaze at you from across the monitor
I float time on my index finger
This is an endless line from 1000
Hey, continue to spin
Surpassing blue tenderness,
The dirtied truth
should be able to roll
If this cruel end were rewritten,
is that fatalism? A theory?
「Why am I...!」
「I was only advocating the theory.」
「What are you calling logic...」
「That doesn't mean that a clone was actually made!」
「...I see...so that was the real reason. I understand now.」
「The world should have chosen thedevelopment of science as its maximum priority!」
「In the end, I won't be able to escape from the curse of Oakwood either...」
「You already know my background, don't you?」
「I'll go anywhere as long as I'll be able to continue my research.」
「Because it's all I have.」
「For what purpose have the government officials come this far?」
「I won't become like you...」
「...Gin.」
This is
This is the Control World Room
Spinning and spinning, high-end turn
The end of the soul's end, listen carefully
Then, here, a lullaby
Control World Room
Composition/Kamiuta & Hirata Junichi
Lyrics/Kamiuta
Singing/LIQU@.
Video/Nasuno
Project Houshin produced by Team Kamiuta