Weekend Heroines
Work hard to the maxx!
Joking? To the maxX
A brave new group of challengers
is approaching from the ringside
(Ba-ba-ba-ban!)
Tossing aside the trauma of crushing defeat,
it's dance or die; Reaching for the stars, (we go!)
Overly stubborn, my dream is to have
my rival be my very best partner
Bringing out the best in each other,
(Chai Maxx!)
we fight!
Chime the gong to the max!
We're seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously
aiming to win, so jump on in!
This ring holds equal opportunity for a reversal of power
We'll rise to the top,
testing our limits to the maxx
You can't even begin to call this difficult!
We'll break through to the max
It's a fight for survival in this
in this mismatch game, but even so,
seize dreams of success!
Swish, swish, swish, swish,
swish, swish,
We'll stand firm!
Spin 'round, glance 'round, a flash of light, smooth hit! Round 1!
A milky ruffian, Chai Maxx
Every gene in my body, an extension of evolution
Rewrite history with the future
(Ba-ba-ba-ban!)
Search for complications; Even you can
make your the weed of your heart bloom gallantly
(You go!)
Move forth, friends, and shout together!
Rouse your hearts
with powerful
(Chai Maxx)
special words
Chime the gong to the max!
Of true, true, true, true
fervor and pure love, and pure sympathy
Sing of them without a care and it'll be a breeze
Even with scrapes all over,
strategize to the maxX
You're not even at that much of a disadvantage
Put your soul into it
From the ultimate endless overtime of your dreams,
find love and peace
Steadily, steadily, steadily, steadily,
steadily, steadily,
we'll stand back up!
Back and forth; One win, one loss
Round 2!
Sweet spiciness, Chai Maxx
I won't give up, I won't look back
The name of the shooting star I'm chasing after is stardom
So radiant, even my uniform could melt
The clapping and cheers enter my hearing
To be honest, I was about to lose spirit
But then I felt your arm embracing me
I truly, truly, truly, truly,
seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously mean it
I haven't opened up the path to my future yet,
so I'll seize dreams of success from this mismatch game
Strive towards a new mindset dedicated to fighting
Your enemy was within you all along
The visions I have for the future are limitless,
so I'll find love and peace from this endless overtime
Swish, swish, swish, swish,
swish, swish, get the jump on your opponent!
Nimbly, smoothly, with a grin, turn the tables – Winner!
Seconds, please! Chai Maxx
Work hard to the maxx!
Joking? To the maxX
Similar-minded to the maxx?
A milky ruffian, Chai Maxx