Fudanjuku
Chenmen Paradise
Heart- Heart-pounding love, fast- fast-paced love
Kiss- I'll make your heart go wild
Hey, listen here- Ever since the day I first met you...
Oh, it's no use. I'd played out this scenario thousands of times yesterday...
But in the end, I'll just say it straight out.
"I love you."
Oh, I love you! Oh, I love you!
I love you!
Chenmen Paradise!
I can't keep it in any longer!
Please, look at no one but me.
Until the day you realize I was meant for you...
I'll keep waiting, however long it takes.
I'll protect you to the end, okay?!
I will make you happy.
"Well? Make your choice."
Oh, I love you! Oh, I love you!
I love you!
Chenmen Paradise!
You've always got a grin on your face.
I love it when you smile.
But still, I sometimes worry, watching you like this.
"You don't have to try so hard in front of me."
I will protect you, honey honey baby
By your side whatever happens to us two
And so, take this (hand of mine) into yours (grasp it tight)
I'll hold on (for eternity)
Ah~, I won't ever let you go
Oh, I love you! Oh, I love you!
I love you!
Chenmen Paradise!
Heart- Heart-pounding love,
fast- fast-paced love
Kiss- I'll make your heart go wild
Go ahead.
Really, go ahead.
Like I said, really, go ahead.
C'mon, how many times have I told you now?
Listen here...
"Tonight, I'll pamper you all you want."
The food you hand-made the other day was delicious.
I've never eaten such a delicious hamburger before!
Hey, what're you laughing at?
You're making fun of me 'cause you
think I'm like a little kid, aren't you?
Hey... This time, I want to savor you.
Sorry for suddenly calling you all the way out here.
It's about time we put this to an end.
Why, you ask?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm tired of our current relationship.
Just let me say one last thing.
Please marry me.
I want you, honey honey baby
I wanna hold you close, and stay like this always
Let it reach (your ears), resound in (your chest)
And steal that (heart of yours)
Ah~, can't stop myself anymore
Oh, I love you! Oh, I love you!
I love you!
Chenmen Paradise!
Chenmen is the only thing that can cure you.
I love you.
Shall we kiss?
I will protect you, honey honey baby
By your side whatever happens to us two
And so, take this (hand of mine) into yours (grasp it tight)
I'll hold on (for eternity)
Ah~, I won't ever let you go
Oh, I love you! Oh, I love you!
I love you! (I love you so much!)
I'll never stop telling you! I'll never stop telling you!
I love you so much!
Chenmen Paradise!
Che- Chenmen Paradise!
Heart-pounding love, fast- fast-paced love
Kiss- I'll make your heart go wild
Heart- Heart-pounding love, fast- fast-paced love
You're all mine!