Kurosawa Madoka
Emilio
Boy L opened the door
and found cold, rotting scrap garbage
Even I'm the same,
he mutters,
and again closes the door
The bread that girl was holding
seemed delicious
so I threatened to hit her
and made it my own
This country is kind
and protects futures,
so they'll forgive killing
because I'm just a child, right?
When loitering around town at night,
I grasp onto a sweet butterfly
After being touched harshly,
it can bite back and run away
The words coming out of these dry mouths
know nothing of the future
Our hearts and bodies are both frozen,
With vacant eyes,
we're Chilledren
Left alone and neglected in a refrigerator,
We play, making shoplifting a game,
The number of children cutting their wrists
increase
When blackmail and
violence are immature,
they can be settled by crying "bully"
That good-looking guy who seems
unrelated to depravity
is really
full of bad additives
If you're going to make a problem of lowering the age for crime,
then isn't it natural for adults to commit crimes?
Without even the words
on the screen appearing,
we simply hurt each other
Die
Is it really fine for us to live, depending on something?
I hide a knife in my chest,
The coldly laughing boys' and girls'
bitter shouts are heard by no one
We can't
find any
place to
belong
Within a refrigerator,
we're Chilledren
When the door's closed and it grows cold, we'll finally go bad,
If we become adults as we are right now,
we'll lack maturity as Mr. Chilledren
We can't find any place to belong
in this frozen world like a refrigerator
The words coming out
of these dry mouths
know nothing of the future
Our hearts and bodies are both frozen,
Someone warm us up,
we're Chilledren
Neglected by adults,
Simply starved for love single-mindedly,
we're Chilledren