We board the night train
Our destination is our 「secret」
Merry friends are waiting
Darling small birdies
A compass with a
needle that's gone crazy
Don't hesitate and
advance at full speed
Come on, ring the bell proudly!
I whistle
and raise my voice in high spirits
With a light step,
we finally reach
Come, join hands
In this town where dawn doesn't come,
Is this
a secret fairyland?
No, this is
a super fun place
because everyday is full of merrymaking!
We follow a green pierrot
who jumped into the mirror's reflection
Together with our strange friends
Sing a song
and drink alcohol together,
free and easy
Tonight is special dreaming
a magical Fantasy night
Where are you guys going?
A secret land where you
don't grow older
and you can be a child forever,
that kind of, Yes! Wonderland!
The stars twinkle
and the moon also breaks into song
Don't hesitate and advance at full speed
It's our secret to keep
Absolutism?
Authoritarianism?
If I order it,
Bow, OK?
As I feel,
As my heart
desires,
Everyone is at a loss
A square piece
The queen of the blazing sun
has a square mind
Answer with
An unforgiving
queen
Get off of my domain this instant!
Match our steps
line up,
and walk together!
Our smiles match, see,
we arrive at the secret land
My dream
and my dream
This sparkling world
I want to stay as a child
with my wonderful friends
But...
That means that you won't
get to see your mama again
I don't want that, because I love her
Does that mean I can't see papa either?
That's the rule of fairyland
Come, which will you choose?
What do I do?
Hey,
what do I do?
I love both papa and mama
but I want to stay as a child
But
What do I do?
Hey,
what do I do?
There's no time! Hurry,
or the train will come
The night train pulls into station
Its moment of departure
is midnight, 0 'o clock
Come, what will you do?
While the door
to the next world remains unopened,
jump into this world!
Let's go!
We board the night train
Our destination is our world
Our warm family is waiting
The clever, darling white birdies
are smiling and having fun
We wave our hands and depart,
Come on, ring the bell proudly!
The 「secret」 of the naughty twins
who'd jumped into the mirror's reflection
In this merry world, everyone,
The stars twinkle, the signal of our hands clapping
Tonight is special dreaming, a magical Fantasy night
In loud singing voices,
a toast to our secret night!
The twins' 「secret」 was almost
like a fairytale
A secret,
wonderful,
merry
The stars twinkle
Today is rather Fantastic
Stars, twinkle
Today is, yes, Fantastic
Now, let's start the story
Now, let's begin the story
Now, raise your hands