the rusted map buried in my distant memories,
changing trains 3 times, I reached town
is this the bustle of Shibuya?
the you from some time blurred and disappeared
if a monster walks making the same face
that shop has already disappeared somewhere
taking out my time capsule,
I roll it in the palm of my hand, gazing
「That’s, a story from when?」 even if I ask the mirror, it remains expressionless
memories, dreams disconnect
7 years ago is yesterday
crossing through time,
I immediately came to meet you
feelings slipping, slipping through surfaces,
feelings packed at a standstill
from the opening in the clouds shining beyond,
if I give up this light reality
fading, fading wishes,
the concealed truth
anyone else is, yes, a last moment cloud rider
the two of us secretly promised out loud
we could sing that day’s popular songs from memory
because this is a local conflict,
there’s only one chance to escape
「When's the next time you'll come back?」I don’t even have a response to the question
the thin string is cut
this made-up story is freedom, isn’t it?
crossing through time,
I immediately came to meet you
daydreams spinning, spinning in my chest
warped, distorted, impulses
from the opening in the clouds shining beyond,
if I give up this light reality
a response is returned, returned,
depth piercing your gaze
anyone else is, yes, a last moment cloud rider
I cry with a smile that hasn’t been seen
are unspeakable stories multiplying within people?
with prayers, reality runs in reverse
surprisingly, even so, you are special to me
crossing through time,
I immediately came here to meet you
feelings slipping, slipping on surfaces
feelings packed at a standstill
from the opening in the clouds shining beyond,
if I give up this light reality
fading, fading wishes,
the concealed truth
anyone else is, yes, lost, even I,
I immediately came to meet you
daydreams spinning, spinning in my chest
warped, distorted, impulses
from the opening in the clouds shining beyond,
if I give up this light reality
a response is returned, returned,
depth piercing your gaze
anyone else is, yes, a last moment cloud rider