The Innocence of D'
Momoiro Clover Z
All'Z clear, Boss.
Infiltrating this castle should be a piece of cake.
All clear!
Now then, how about we go make the
Illusionary Thing hidden in this castle ours?
All clear!
The Illusionary Thing...! Just imagining it makes my heart flutter!
Oh no!
We have no other choice now.
We'll force our way through. Move out!
Nin-nin!
I can't believe thiiiiiZ!
Only those familiar with the darkness
realize that they let off a profound light
and that they were born to charm
Though the flowers piercing my chest may spill,
the dream won't end just yet
Don't worry, dash!
(I'll keep running)
Developing!
(I'll keep dancing)
Daringly, unfailingly, best as you can, purely,
make adversity into your ally!
Take back tomorrow!
Tonight, our tears are cleansed by light
The moon is atop this stage
One great step can remake the times
Let's go the distance together
Now, come see me
Dash, dash, dash, dash,
dash, dash, dash, dash!
Without showing the faintest hint of a smile,
you gave me your kindness, bittersweet
It was my first taste of what would become a new addiction
If your definition of youth is immaturity,
then I'll break that notion of yours
Detestation,dash!
(I hate to lose)
Developing!
(I'll keep singing)
With all your body, all your soul, emotions, instinct,
act on your excitement
Take back your heart!
Be honest with yourself and look straight at me
Hell's moon
Reborn from the darkness as many times as it takes,
let's go the distance together
Now, if you want to believe,
dash, dash, dash, dash,
dash, dash, dash, dash!
I'm happy we could meet
My heart throbs
Countless times, I cried out,
“thank you,” “thank you,”
I'd called out to you this whole time
As painful as the things I love doing are,
they feel almost effortless
Take back our romance
It's so mysterious - strength is overflowing from my clenched chest
Take back tomorrow
Tonight, our tears are cleansed by light
The full moon's wasteland
All hopes will form a pure-white being
Let's dance together
Until our hearts melt into one,
dash, dash, dash, dash,
dash, dash, dash, dash!
Boss!
The Illusory Thing... is ourZ now!
Yeah, it's ourZ!
It's ourZ!
Looks delicious! What are we waiting for?
Let's help ourselves!
It's ourZ, it's ourZ!
That's our Takagi-san! Thanks for the food!
Thanks for the food!
I can't believe thiiiiis!
End