Welcome!
Please sit wherever you'd like.
...okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Welcome!
Have you decided on your order?
A strawberry smoothie, please.
Certainly.
Chenmen, chen, chenmen, chen, chenmen
Crossdressing fandom!
Revolution!
“I beg of you, my lady.
Please look at no one but me.”
With the rose-red raw emotion of passion
Let the moment I spin around and kiss you stop time
Hey! Crossdressing fandom!
I love! (I love!) you! (you!)
Gaze at me as much as you'd like through the Twelfth Night
and dye me deep in your colors, Shakespeare
Hey! Crossdressing fandom!
I've got no want for a hurtful love
so let's love one another, ah
“I won't let go of you tonight.”
Want you!
I'll break through the crossdressing asphalt for you
(Hey! Hey! Come on! Yeah!)
because I want to teach you the meaning of true love! Yeah!
Chenmen, chen, chenmen, chen, chenmen
Shoot through your heart with a loving wink
And so, to the captivating world of the 2.5th dimension
Come, on with me
Crossdressing fandom!
Chenmen, chen, chenmen, chen, chenmen
Revolution!
(Yeah, yeah! Come on!)
If you find it fun,
then just go ahead and enjoy yourself
Walk around as a shota
Hey! Crossdressing fandom!
Tsundere (tsundere!)
Yandere (yandere!)
If you've fallen in love with a different version of yourself
then feel it throughout your body, Jeanne d'Arc
Hey! Crossdressing fandom!
Although a love no more than playing around is the last thing I want,
when you take off your glasses, ah
“I love you to the very bone.”
Love you!
Falling into a catharsis of delusions is no sin
(Hey! Hey! Come on! Yeah!)
I just want to search for what the greatest love is! Yeah!
Chenmen, chen, chenmen, chen, chenmen
Binding you to me with the kiss I blow
And so, to the captivating world of the 2.5th dimension
Come, on with me
Entwine your fingers with mine
I'll make you melt, ah
Yeah! Chenmen, chen!
I'll break through the crossdressing asphalt for you
because I want to teach you the meaning of true love
Falling into a catharsis of delusions is no sin
(Hey! Hey! Come on! Yeah!)
I just want to search for what the greatest love is! Yeah!
Chenmen, chen, chenmen, chen, chenmen
Shoot through your heart with a loving wink
And so, to the captivating world of the 2.5th dimension
Come, on with me
Crossdressing fandom!
Chenmen, chen, chenmen, chen, chenmen
Revolution!