"Scar!" Just 'cause you tried and failed
You'd better not be turning back!
If they're not burned to nothing, throw away all that rhetorical flourish!
Thrown into disarray, confronted by new developments from something big? C'mon!
Why don't you just take all the good things and stuff 'em in a bag!
The layers pile up from the withdrawal of previous statements
But who cares if sky's the limit! Why not overshoot!
The troubling logic of serious dreaming tendencies?
You don't want to cast away the courage to step forward!
Nothing will go without a hitch
But relief -> conceit -> grave wounds is something you want to seriously avoid!
Awaken nonfiction! Revive the confliction!
Rather than live defying your instinct
"Hold up! Isn't that a little pushy?!"
Well, that's perfectly fine
Rip off that dire decoration, and go!
Let me put that infantile pride of yours
to sleep for you with a lullaby; now, good night
See, if you put everything on the table and shout out, your love will reach!
Embrace the miracle that you and I share with one another
Now, I will strip this ostentatious world
of its lies, its decorations!
This world with no chance of reconcilation perpetuates its fantasy
My motto is to never stop changing; regressing is a solid no
Your criticism may be absolutely right; I'll take it into consideration, and no more
Let's adventure, further! (More, more, more, more!)
Seize this moment, this instant, and go!
Under the pressure of a big declaration; take deep breaths in recovery mode
Actually, I think I'm pretty good at covering myself with eloquent words
Wrapping things up by unreservedly getting straight to the point, pleasantly
But if I can follow up with a little smile and a "Yes?" I'm all OK
365 days of being called a good kid
Can't show your own weaknesses
If you don't even like it, then just whose dream is it?
Aren't you getting caught up in these times where everyone wants to become flawless?
Electric signals crossing paths
Bring a consensus and go, go!
Rather than live defying your instinct
If you're going to regret, do so heartily
Rip off that dire decoration, and go!
Peace out!! Your infantile pride
Is a jewelry case filled with imitations
Surface wounds of sentiment, this is where I bid you farewell!
What do I want to protect from the lies?
Now that I've realized what, I've taken it upon myself to
For the sake of those I hold dear, strip myself of this fake decoration!
No one will get ya if you don't put your feelings into words
Hey, God! Why're you such a cheapskate?
Ahh! It's a never-ending heated tie
It's because unexpected things happen that life is fun!
Let me put that infantile pride of yours
to sleep for you with a lullaby; now, good night
See, if you put everything on the table and shout out, your love will reach!
Embrace the miracle that you and I share with one another
Now, I will strip this ostentatious world
of its lies, its decorations!
This world with no chance of reconcilation perpetuates its fantasy
Sorry, but I'm not down for a West Side Story-esque ending
Your criticism may be absolutely right; I'll take it into consideration, and no more
My motto is to never stop changing; regressing is a solid no
Take every single little good thing and "Stuff 'em all in a bag!"
Sorry, but I'm not down for a West Side Story-esque ending
We may never reach reconcilation
"But a solution definitely exists!"
Let's adventure, further! (More, more, more, more!)
Seize this moment, this instant, and go!