I could just sit back and be satisfied
with a simple and frugal, average life
That doesn't sound too bad
But I've got a few more things that I wanna do
When it comes down to it, I don't want to hold myself back
You feel the same, don't you?
Everyone wants to have fun for their whole lives
The grownups all say there's no way that's happening
But that's not true at all!
Life's about the way you look at it!
In this world, the winner's club is made of the most free-spirited people!
Now, here we go!
Enjoy life like no one's before!
Bring 'em on! The fun and the storms
Today, the next day, and every day after
Hey, let's all dance! Let's all dance! Let's all dance on!
We won't fear going down in flames
Just give it a try; no pain, no game
We have a huge dream right here in our sights
Hey, let's have fun! Let's shout out! Let's ditch, too! Ready, go!
Because I still, I still, I still
haven't had enough fun
She always looks lively and energetic, so of course there's just
no way that she could have any worries at all
That's what everyone thinks
But truth is, keeping up with studies is pretty tough
and there's many other painful hardships along the way
That's reality for you
Life always throws the unexpected at you
A lot of things, you just have to stand fast and bear
I know that, but still, no
Hey, do you know why?
Why I can't be a good girl, nodding along obediently
Now, here we go!
Enjoy life! Yeah, rock and roll!
Just can't stop! Our bursting passion
Become the very brightest star that there is!
Hey, let's shine bright! Let's shine bright! Let's all shine bright!
Of course it won't last forever
No one knows where the tides of time flow
We're spot in the middle of our shining youth!
Hey, let's have fun! Let's shout out! Let's ditch, too! Ready, go!
Because I still, I still, I still
don't want to change just yet
One sudden moment, I realized
that everyone was really growing up, bit by bit
Oh, please - don't give me such a cold look
Please, don't belittle our dreams
You're always at your best when you smile!
Yes, you see,
overtime will keep on going
I want every day to be an adventure
Let's walk the roadless road
Hey, let's have fun! Let's have fun! Let's all have fun!
Enjoy life like no one's before!
Bring 'em on! The fun and the storms
Today, the next day, and every day after
Hey, let's all dance! Let's all dance! Let's all dance on!
We won't fear going down in flames
Just give it a try; no pain, no game
We have a huge dream right here in our sights
Hey, let's have fun! Let's shout out! Let's ditch, too! Ready, go!
Because we still, we still, we still
have just gotten started