Don't listen to the BGM
Sugarless is just half-assed -
I don't need it, don't need it
With each other, step, step, step
Take me on a bullet train ride, please
A merry-go-round isn't enough, not enough
Don't tell me A to Z -
show me what you mean
The nooks of my brain
I can't erase, can't erase
Break the GPS
I'm a little unable to wait
It's all your fault - 3, 2, 1
Hey, Mr. Sunday - wait, please care about me
Follow the course of time and wind up my spring
When you open up the box, see - it's all fake! Fake!
Make some noise - clap, clap clap
Being careful is useless
Playing make-believe is a no-no, a no-no
Avoid scoring MVP,
hurl away your opportunities
My left ear on its own isn't enough, not enough
Pile them up - stock, stock, stock
Provoking others is a no-no
The cards laid out before me
I can't pull, can't pull in advance
Let me out, get home quick
Yeah, like that full-length novel kid - 3, 2, 1
Hey, Mr. Sunday - wait, please care about me
Follow the course of time and wind up my spring
When you open up the box, see - it's all fake! Fake!
The taste of the poison apple...
Just like my right hand.
What does an incomplete blink taste like?
'cause I'm sure it's coated in bottomless sweetness...
The mirror reflects only lies
since your voice is all inside-out, isn't it?
Hey, Mr. Sunday - wait! Please care about me!
Hold my hand tight until I can fall asleep
Hey, Mr. Sunday - wait, please care about me
When you open up the box, see - it's all fake! Fake!
Follow the course of time and wind up my spring
Hey, Mr. Sunday - wait, please care about me
Outside the door, see- it's all fake! Fake!