█████████████████████████
I'm sleeping, wrapped in your arms
How many times have I dreamed that today?
In this room which has you missing,
it feels a bit too spacious for a lone person
The gears broken that day
can no longer be turned back
I was even the one who cut off this love, so why -
I'm acting like a fool
Our distance apart is only centimeters on a map,
yet I again pass the night alone
Sending out a wish for the arms that had once embraced me
"I want to see you..."
I wake up, wrapped in your arms
How many times have I dreamed that today?
When I heard your voice from the other side of the phone
I ended up lying, "I'm fine"
I'd held everything back because I didn't want to make you worry
But say, if I said I wanted to meet you,
would you come see me?
Our distance apart is only centimeters on a map,
yet I again pass the night alone
Sending out a wish for the arms that had once embraced me
"I want to see you..."
I again and again pass the night like this,
like I'm being crushed
If it were possible to rewind time, back to when we were together,
I want to go back
Our distance apart is only centimeters on a map,
yet I again pass the night alone
Sending out a wish for the arms that had once embraced me
The two of us's memories left in this room
are the only thing that hasn't changed since then
I know our love can't be started over,
yet I keep on hoping for something
I again pass the night
while gazing up at the starry sky
Sending out a wish for the arms that had once embraced me
I want to see you...
Song(Orchestra)・Voice: Giga
Song (Melody): LettuceP
Illust: Nagi
Video: Norainu