I long to meet you
The path of my journey stretches beyond eternity
Among the impermanence of all worldly things,
that wish will never change...
The Five Skandhas
Is this love a worldly passion?
I'm unable to completely free myself of desires
No need for words - I can tell by way of divine powers
This karma is as if we had been together in a previous life
The days that I wept dismally
For some reason, those are the memories I can't seem to forget
Blunt at face, but actually kind at heart
I feel urged to chase after that someone who resembles you so much
The gemstones that I had worked and worked so hard to build up
Toppled and fell into millions of tiny pieces
"All because of your lack of faith!"
The deceptive evil spirit cackles, laughing as it mocks me
A true miracle is the final result of good karma
Because it's no longer a miracle, but an
unknown guiding power coming from within yourself
I long to see you at any time
With a mysterious synchronicity,
our souls are connected deep within
All of these unbounded emotions in the palm of your hand
With the scent of nectar...
Shambhala; recklessly, without thought
Above the unfortunate town,
the cruel demon passes through
I'll purify the cursed demon raging through my heart
Just you watch, suspicious evil spirit!
I'm fine, I can handle myself!
I said those distant words were because I wanted you to know
I hate relying on others only at times like these
I want to show you how I never give in
Oh, I'm being called out to, so drawn to you
Can you fly away to a loving state with neither sky nor land?
The questioning voices ask, "How about it?" laughing arrogantly
I can no longer attach a name to these emotions about to fall to pieces
Love, friendship, or whatever
What I have here surpasses it all
I long to meet you
On this path of lotus flowers, somehow,
our souls are connected deep within
I want to cleanse these feelings forming a vortex going forth
All will end someday; that is what they call fate
All that prospers must decline? Allow me to decline
I want to be my own incarnation
A true miracle is the final result of good karma
Because it's no longer a miracle, but an
unknown guiding power coming from within yourself
So you may come to realize what has been suppressed by the raging river,
the mandala of all living things
I offer you these prayers, these words of my hopes
With my thanks
Shangri-La; recklessly, without thought
The cruel demon beckons invitingly
That path is the path of evil
The entrance is wide-open, but there's no escape
I won't be deceived! Suspicious evil spirit