The Defeated Boy
After struggling
and running away,
I had
somehow ended up standing where I am
I'd wanted to
become someone that everyone would admire,
a hero -
but I couldn't
Of course, I'd already known
Someone like me
isn't even halfway there
Defeated boy,
sing praises of reality
None of us can fly through the sky like that
If there will be
meaning to a night such as this,
we will crawl across the ground
A buzz echoes
through my ears
It seems
a miracle
is inviting me -
"Your dream -
to become an admired hero -
Why don't I make it come true right now?"
When it's just offered
to me like a candy,
I can't be all that happy...
Defeated boy,
sing praises of existence
We may not be able to become as radiant as you
But if there will be
meaning to a night such as this,
we will crawl across the ground
And yet crawl the ground...
I feel my heartbeat
and take a deep breath:
"Thanks, but I'm good."
Defeated...
Defeated boy,
sing praises of normalcy
Unfortunately, gods aren't the sorts that should believed
And so to this
passing story,
farewell...
Defeated boy,
sing praises of reality
We will be the ones to crawl through the mud
Because even a night
such as this is beloved,
we will crawl across the ground
And just crawl the ground...