Hm, hm?
Who might you be?
♪Avarice (Kebyou Ningen Track 10)
Oh, I see now.
You've lost your way, haven't you?
I don't know who you are,
but you're quite the unfortunate sort.
Well, this might just be perfect.
I, too, was set upon by boredom...
Which makes us a pair.
Why do you look so surprised?
I know, I know.
You consider the world you live in...
boring, do you not?
As such, you arrived upon this place.
Oh, please, stop giving me that look.
The number of reasons one could have for coming to Ripica's place
is not within reasonable bounds.
It's simple, really.
Humans don't know what they should do.
That is why
we continue to take records.
Humans are the ones
who upset the balance of the Akashic Records.
And the gasoline
which drives us humans
is curiosity.
You, for rejecting that fact,
are "fakely ill", so to speak.
Yes, how about we call you a "Fakely Ill Human"?
But come now, do take a seat.
I don't have any sweets here,
but I can, at the very least, bring out some tea.
Where is this place, you ask?
Let's be honest:
does that really matter?
So, allow me to get straight to the point.
What sort of story do you wish to hear?
We only have so much time.
What do I mean by "story"...?
Very well.
Shall I choose one for you?
Please wait here momentarily.
Let me see here...
For a Fakely Ill Human such as you,
perhaps this would be best?
♪Promulgation (Youka-me, Ame ga Yamu mae ni. Track 5)
Sa, shi, su? Sa, shi, su?
Sa, shi, su,
su, su, suzu, suuzuu,
Sa, shi, su? Sa, shi, su?
Sa, shi, su,
su, su, suzu, suuzuu,
suzu, ma mi mu?
...oh, here, found it!
"The Liar Epica: Suzumu"
"The Liar Ripica: Suzumu"
All this guy records
is stories that middle schoolers would like.
Perfect fit for you.
Among his works is...
Where was it?
Case File A, B, C, D...
"The Bookmark of Demise"?
Not this.
Pando...ra...?
Not this, either...
Oh, here it is.
Finally found it.
This is what you seek, isn't it?
"Seven mysterious tales
which occurred over the seven days before the world's end."
Listen to him. How poetic.
The title is...
"On the Eighth Day, Before the Rain Stops."
So it seems.
Go ahead.
Right.
You don't know how to use it, do you?
Don't worry.
I believe you have them in your age as well?
CD player stereo systems, PCs...
Please use one of those devices to play it.
Once you do so, perhaps your boring world
will become a little more bearable.
Well, I still have business to take care of,
so would you allow me to take my leave here?
Take care to leave
through the same door you entered from.
So, with this...
May we meet again when it rains once more.
"Because that is when the story begins."
In the November of 2011, the mysterious circle KEMU VOXX skyrocketed to prominence on an internet video-sharing site. He is a member of the circle as a composer/arranger, the videos he took part in surpassing 3 million views. The group's album also reached a rank of 10 on the Oricon rankings along with garnering a tremendous amount of support from many users.
♪Humanity Five Minutes Before Hypothesis (Youka-me, Ame ga Yamu mae ni. Track 2)
The 2012 unique "music x novel" collaboration "The Bookmark of Demise Project", surprised the world, shining at rank 10 in the Oricon rankings. As the project's thrilling storyteller, Suzumu continues to betray users' expectations altogether.
He is also the writer of the series's novelization, which has printed a total of
over 8 million copies.
In 2013, Suzumu was placed in charge of the ending theme to "Dangan Ronpa:
The Animation" as part of the explosively popular creators' circle "Asukasoromanya-z" with his friend Soraru. With the group, he released his single
"Despairity: The Cure for Heroes".
And his time has come in 2015, now that the release of his first major album has
been set. The industry has all of its attention on this young multi-creator.
【Limited Edition A】
CD+Bonus DVD ¥3,000 (+Tax)
Illustrator: Tokiti & DMYM (No. 734)
DISC 1
01. Manifesto■■
02.Humanity Five Minutes Before Hypothesis
03. Ashen Boy's Rock■■
04. Heart Connect
05. Promulgation
06. Coming Out from that Time Tunnel.
07. Existence■■■■■■
08. Retort Irony■■■■■■
09. Enactment
10. Revolutionarity: King Epidemic
11. The World's Lifespan and the Last Day
12.On the Eighth Day, Before the Rain Stops.
13. Execution■■■■■■
DISC 2 (Bonus DVD)
【A box containing the dream we saw that day.】
01. Indulging: Idol Syndrome
02. Sincerity: Feigned Ignorance's
■■■Drastic Treatment■■■■■■■
03. Shoddy Utopia Policy■■■■■■
04. Sakura-Colored Time Capsule
05. Liar Peter Pan■■■■■■■
06. The World's Lifespan and the Last Day
07. Heart Connect
08. Halloween Late Party■■■■■■■
(Newly-Created PV)
【Limited Edition B】
CD + Bonus CD ¥3,000 (+Tax)■
Illustrator: Saine■■■■
DISC 1
01. Manifesto■■
02.Humanity Five Minutes Before Hypothesis
03. Ashen Boy's Rock■■
04. Heart Connect
05. Promulgation
06. Coming Out from that Time Tunnel.
07. Existence■■■■■■
08. Retort Irony■■■■■■
09. Enactment
10. Revolutionarity: King Epidemic
11. The World's Lifespan and the Last Day
12.On the Eighth Day, Before the Rain Stops.
13. Execution■■■■■■
DISC 2 (Bonus DVD)
【Fakely Ill Human: Continuation】
01. Endless
02. Despairity: The Cure for Heroes
03. Indulging: Idol Syndrome■■■■■■■■
04. Sincerity: Feigned Ignorance's
■■■Drastic Treatment■■■■■■■■■■■■
05. Shoddy Utopia Policy■■■■■■■■
06. Sakura-Colored Time Capsule
07. Don't Say Whatever You Want to
08. Hidden at That Transient Summer's End
09. Liar Peter Pan■■■■■■■■
10. To the Lonely You and the Lone Me
11. Valedictory■■■■
【Regular Edition】
CD ¥2,000 (+Tax)■■■■■■
Illustrator: Kuronokuro
DISC 1
01. Manifesto■■
02.Humanity Five Minutes Before Hypothesis
03. Ashen Boy's Rock■■
04. Heart Connect
05. Promulgation
06. Coming Out from that Time Tunnel.
07. Existence■■■■■■
08. Retort Irony■■■■■■
09. Enactment
10. Revolutionarity: King Epidemic
11. The World's Lifespan and the Last Day
12.On the Eighth Day, Before the Rain Stops.
13. Execution■■■■■■
So, well.
Looks like another day went by according to the Akashic Records.
February 4th: 1st Album "On the Eighth Day, Before the Rain Stops."
Booooring.