Shiritsu Ebisu Chuugaku
Like a Toothache!
Maidens are solitary and pure-hearted
Attractiveness vs appetite? Jesus!
Passing the night with the 2nd dimension as company
The Wi-Fi-Crazy Club
Universal sweet-tooth; three days zazen
A bad experience with non-REM rejection
He's the cause of this sensation
A riajuu? You know?
It suddenly began one morning
I couldn't take it anymore
Could it be the first signs of that?
Don't tell me...!
Like a toothache! A painful love
Mental health check; I've got the jitters!
A friend? Or foe? Rather away
The fight for reality over illusions
Exclusivity! Out of range of these taste buds
Not without complications; my head's spinning!
Painkillers not working?!
Of the ride to the operation chair
I'm not afraid-aid-aid-aid-aid....
Blow this coward's heart, and teeth, and hardware with dynamite
The fluff down I bite between my teeth
is a limited-time offer of a petit sense of safety
The powerless S.O.S. my right hand raises -
Meaningless! Dat u know!
A shoddy reaction chain of unknown whereabouts
More like a heart disease than a headache?
Stealthy footsteps, barefoot, lacking any courage
Payback for cutting corners?
I'll try and tell him how I feel without dying of embarrassment
It's the "last resort" they all mention
I'm in love!
Like a toothache! A sweet love
An accident while I wasn't looking
Flower petal prediction; coming? Or not?
Slightly darker than anticipated
Exclusivity! A resolute fate
Even the teacher doesn't get it!
Polishing myself; life's runway
This pride unyielding to any timidness
I won't ever give it up
These chipped teeth and heart, my past sacrifice
So, so
Slowly creeping up on me while I wasn't looking
This unaccountable throbbing in my heart
"Doki doki?"
Honestly, I've got no choice but to admit it
I surprisingly don't hate it??
I'm not afraid
of the dentist
What I'm scared of
is pain, pain, pain
Like a toothache! A painful love
Mental health check; I've got the jitters!
A friend? Or foe? Rather away
The fight for reality over illusions
Exclusivity! Out of range of these taste buds
Not without complications; my head's spinning!
Painkillers not working?!
Of the ride to the operation chair
I'm not afraid-aid-aid-aid-aid....
Blow this coward's heart, and teeth, and hardware with dynamite
I'm not afraid (I'm not afraid)
of love itself (of love itself)
What I'm scared of (What I'm scared of)
is the pain (is the pain)
I'm not afraid (I'm not afraid)
of the dentist (of the dentist)
What I'm scared of (What I'm scared of)
is pain, pain, pain...