Whatever sort of hell my heart is living right now,
as usual, in the world around me, it's just another day...
Friends laughing, feigning ignorance
Meanwhile, in a dream with the name of solitude,
I'm right here, waving my hand...
Bit by bit, things started to fall apart
In the midst of nothing but small failures,
I'd thought to myself that it'd be best to give up on it all
But I don't have the courage to quit
I got the feeling somewhere that I just shouldn't
Yet when looking at all these happy sceneries,
I don't cry; I can't cry - I'm sulking a little
No one is truly alone
We just attempt to isolate ourselves
Slipping underneath the sheets of a cold bed, hiding away in our dreams,
but we're not alone
"How about you? Haven't given up yet?"
"You're not looking for promising excuses, are you?"
The dream I saw when I shut my eyes was one where I was all alone
When you give up too much, you end up an idiot
So I won't give up on a single thing anymore
Solitude gives despair a kiss
Moonlight - Paint in the moon
Daybreak - Even if the darkness obstructs the daybreak...
Choosing to smile all the time, I hesitated, unsure if I should show my tears
In attempting to become someone strong,
I sealed away my weak self and ended up all alone
Let's be reborn in the daybreak
Your honest self is platinum
Once we awaken from this bad dream, splash water on yourself
and wash away that glum sleepy face
Whatever sort of hell my heart is living right now,
the world around me is giving me a trial to overcome
That's why...
Choosing to smile all the time, I hesitated, unsure if I should show my tears
In attempting to become someone strong,
I sealed away my weak self and ended up all alone
Let's be reborn in the daybreak
Your honest self is platinum
Once we awaken from this bad dream, splash water on yourself
and wash away that glum sleepy face
Our today...
dawns...
Daybreak...