This is the eastern samurai cool
this world is where I dance the world, 1 , 2
The drunken, drunken blue, the drunken, drunken blue
Here is a Great Edo oiran girl
the spring of the full moon dancing with eternity, 3,4
The drunken, drunken blue, the drunken, drunken blue
When, when shall we meet?
Will an evening at daybreak be fine?
I slip within a cage,
swaying, sway, swaying, dyed in red
Who is in front of me?
Then, rather,
I will stab the crimson
with the pale pink of the world reflecting the brilliant cherry blossoms
At the end, ingrained in affection,
being with just you
Look, look, it’s beautiful, isn’t it?
This is the land of the gods' underworld road
one more year, why?
The drunken, drunken blue, the drunken, drunken blue
When we meet,
let it bloom until the dawn breaks
You are, without a slip, a sleeping beauty,
drawing an arc and extending an arm to song
Who is this person?
Eve 「Heart?」
Mira 「Yes...falling in love and feeling pain when you lose something. That is a heart.」
Eve 「．．．?」
Mira 「It’s alright, if you remember it from now on.」
Mira 「You won’t age, won’t die, a perfect existence who can’t die. You have plenty of time.」
The shrouded fragrance also
sends off a faint sound far away
Following memories is an uncertain world
disappearing into the dancing flowers
The trance-like scene is...
The crimson color of the world
reflecting brilliant cherry blossoms is adorned just for me
At this end, ingrained in affection,
being with just you
Now, the one shadow under the brilliant cherry blossoms
cries to the heavens
The flowers are cherry blossom trees, you are people,
the beautiful end of a play
Look, look, it’s beautiful...
This is the 1000after
I see, I see, I see, I’m alive