"Hashire! -Z ver.-"
Momoiro Clover Z
I can't stop smiling!
My heart won't stop pounding!
I'll make my first move towards you
Run! Run! Run!
I've always seen you in the same train car as me
I wonder when it all started? When these feelings for you
had grown so strong in my chest
Unable to even start a conversation, I'd always
pretend to be talking with my friends
as I watched you from the side of my eye
But I'm tired of regretting things
now that I've realized how I feel
I don't want to run away by lying to myself, either
Scooping everything up,
not leaving a single bit behind,
I'll pour all of my feelings into these words
I can't stop smiling!
My heart won't stop pounding!
I'll make my first move towards you
Run! Run! Run!
Right now, I still don't have the courage to!
There aren't enough little chances for me!
And so I will my body to start moving
Run! Run! Run!
Always thinking of nothing but excuses
right before taking the first step,
I end up unable to do a thing
as time marches on without me
My heart, all too used to forgetting,
began to race, running forwards
In comparison to this vast world,
someone like me might seem minuscule
But my feelings for you
are even greater than this vast sky
I can't stop smiling!
My heart won't stop pounding!
I'll make my first move towards you
Run! Run! Run!
Right now, I still don't have the courage to!
There aren't enough little chances for me!
And so I will my body to start moving
Run! Run! Run!
Waiting around won't start anything!
I want to face you with all my willpower
We were born on the same planet,
born into the same generation
To distance myself from you
with a word as simple as "coincidence"-
Just thinking about it makes my chest hurt
I earnestly want to connect with you, even now
Even in years, decades, from now on, into the future
Because we've only got one shot at life
I want to be honest when I'm with you
But even so, I can't give you an answer
I can't say aloud the smallest of words
“I like you!” – Will just those three words
change the world? Will they?
I can't stop smiling!
My heart won't stop pounding!
I'll make my first move towards you
Run! Run! Run!
Right now, I still don't have the courage to!
There aren't enough little chances for me!
And so I will my body to start moving
Run! Run! Run!