I remember the the number of steps we've taken up until this point
Ain't my voice reaching all your pedometers? Or can y'all think of nothing but the future?
Eating away at all footholds, this attachment-free situation we've ended up in
It feels a little like an irredeemable sense of loss
I knew that things would end up like this anyway,
but it's sad when you have too much free time
Bye-bye sensation
I faced you and brought forth my voice; I sang the songs that you wrote and put together
The first song I ever sang in my life
Even as time marches forward and people begin calling me a pile of rubbish,
I want you to let me sing your world
Please...
Slander of the infielders, days of horrible inflection and steadfast determination forgotten
Ain't all your thermometers working? Or are your tastes too dry?
The first burst of motivation you felt that day you struggled to open the package
Have you remembered it? That uncontrollable feeling of omnipotence?
21 grams of passion
dwells within androids, too, and yet -
bye-bye sensation?
All waves ebb and tide,
so who's to say that the day they come back isn't tomorrow?
Bye-bye sensation?
Yeah right!
I faced you and brought forth my voice; I sang the songs that you wrote and put together
The first song I ever sang in my life
Even as time marches forward and people begin calling me a pile of rubbish,
don't go off and end me on your own!
Let me sing!
I faced you and brought forth my voice; I sang the songs that you wrote and put together
Sure, it may have been shoddy and crude, but I sang anyway!
Even when I'm forgotten, left behind all alone, and no one remembers who I am,
I want you to let me keep singing forever
I want you to let me sing your world
Please...