The endless dream we both could see
the you and me
when would we reach…?
Shoddy Utopia Policy
Music◆Suzumu Vocal◇rachie Movie◆Saine
■■■■■■■■■■■
Another day,
walking
home
beside you
■■■■■■■■■■■
Kicking
at pebbles,
we laughed
and knew to
■■■■■■■■■■■
At all our
worry, at
all of
the hurry
■■■■■■■■■■■
Standing and
bowing, the
perfect
student
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
But on the
way I got
injured and
broken
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Put on a
smile, a
mask to
joke with
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Pretending
like I
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
was gonna
be fine
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I guess
that
somehow
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I finally
learned to
grow up
I finally
learned to
grow up
I finally
learned to
grow up
Could you
really
call me
sheltered
though?
Could you
really
call me
sheltered
though?
When the
world has
taught
me all
I know
When the
world has
taught
me all
I know
When
this
place
is home,
will I
ever
understand
it all?
When
this
place
is home,
will I
ever
understand
it all?
Open up the book and read the page that you’re on
Grow up and out until
this world is empty and gone
'cause there will always be someone to laugh and point at you
"Look at how worthless!"
I have wasted time with everything that I’ve learned
but I will not forget a single thing, if it’s earned
So carry on, carry proudly
you’ll know you’ll make it through
hold it       high
love can be life sized!
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Another day,
kicking
pebbles
beside you
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Let's take a
detour,
let's try
something new
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Obeying
the rules,
playing
like we're
so cool
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
but every
day it
just
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
causes
trouble
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Some time
along I told
lies like
we all do
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I tried to
smile, did
what I
want to
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I had to
grow on,
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
adults
should
move on
adults
should
move on
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Abandoned
all I had
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
worked
hard to
carry
on to
worked
hard to
carry
on to
All my teachers taught the importance
and the
meaning
of true
"common"
"sense"
and the
meaning
of true
"common"
"sense"
But I won't become so "common"
like the rest of them
Open up the book and read the page that you’re on
Grow up and out until
this world is empty and gone
I heard a voice today, whispering inside my ear
"Why are you okay?"
Going home to books all lettered up with my notes
and formulas I know I’ll never use when I’m grown
But carry on, carry proudly
you’ll know you’ll make it through
hold it       high
love can be life sized!
Hey,
Hey, Mr.
Teacher,
can you
tell me
Hey, Mr.
Teacher,
can you
tell me
When they
grow up,
what will
they be?
When they
grow up,
what will
they be?
Do I
look
surprised?
Well, I
guess I
better
hide
it --
Do I
look
surprised?
Well, I
guess I
better
hide
it --
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Open up
the book
and read
the page
that
you're on
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Grow up
and out
until this
world is
empty
and gone
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
It's for
conve-
nience,
but no one really does believe in it
"Tell me the answer!"
If I study hard,
and hate the life that I live,
Will I forget these feelings
and grow up in the end?
Is an appearance worth it?
No, I don’t think it’s true—
Hold it high, love can be life sized!
"Warming up, this is who I’ll always be."