Unforgivable.
Persecution Complex Cellphone Girl (lol)
Music: Giga
Lyrics: Suzumu
Video: Okiku
Persecution Complex Cellphone Girl (lol)
"You know, him,
he was just talking big."
Suddenly, everyone's raw desires
are crystal clear - my revelation
It sees through only the liars,
and then tells who they are
A truly enigmatic cellphone
My target is
that composer
Sweet-
talking girls,
making them
into playthings
Hearts
in love
crushed
underfoot
as play
And back
then, even me...
I had loved and longed
"So, then, why?"
A delusional girl
spends another day
walking by
worrying about
justice
for appearances
Victim and oneself,
blind to her own faults
egoism and
e
go
egoism and
ego
i
egoism and
egoi
s
egoism and
a bullshit stance
a bullshit
shit
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit
s
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit s
ta
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit sta
n
stance
a bullshit stance
"I'm not the bad one.
He's the attacker."
I knew it, he's a liar
"You can't trust
males at all."
I don't tell anyone, just speak to myself
and hold this knowledge up
The phone rings again - This time, it's for that long-face
acting like they're a star or something
Deceivingly seduce, come on, call me too
As you made innocent girls in love
into prey
A delusional girl
spends another day
walking by
suspicious cellphone
in hand
Morality dictated by self,
blind to her own faults
egoism and
e
go
egoism and
ego
i
egoism and
egoi
s
egoism and
a bullshit stance
a bullshit
shit
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit
s
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit s
ta
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit sta
n
stance
Truth and
blind acceptance
In utter addiction
Finding faults in others
in her search for who's "it"
A game of hide and seek
made public
"Now who, where
could the true
liar could be, hm?
Are you satisfied now?
No, not just yet
ah
I've found you out
"You alone are definitely...definitely..."
Unforgivable.
A delusional girl
spends another day
walking by
worrying about
justice
for appearances
Victim and oneself,
blind to her own faults
egoism and
e
go
egoism and
ego
i
egoism and
egoi
s
egoism and
a bullshit stance
a bullshit
shit
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit
s
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit s
ta
stance
a bullshit stance
a bullshit sta
n
stance
a bullshit stance
The lie-searching
cellphone
goes off -
"Who will be next?"
Let's bring up the tension
In notification
mayhem
"Why? It's not me -
I'm just a victim."
"You are a liar.
Just go die. see ya"
Persecution Complex Cellphone Girl (lol)
Music: Giga
Lyrics: Suzumu
Video: Okiku
Persecution Complex Cellphone Girl (lol)