tsutaetai koto ga aru no
There's something I want you to know,
koko ni shirushitetai kara
something I want to make my mark with
doushitemo dounikashitemo
So whatever happens, no matter what it takes,
yume janai tte sakebou
let's shout out that this isn't a dream
honmono da to shinjiteita
I always had believed
sora wa tenjou no rakugaki de
the sky drawn on the ceiling of my room was real
itsunomanika
Before I knew it,
semai heya ni
I'd been locked away
tojikomerareteta no
in a cramped room
jibun no basho koko janai da tte
This place isn't where you belong
mirai omou tsuyosa ga
See, if you keep the strength to believe so,
areba hontou no sora wa hora
the true sky will someday
mieru kara
reveal itself to you
tsutaetai koto ga aru no
That's why I have something I want you to know
kono kimochi katachi ni shite
I'll show you just what I mean
massugu ni ima sugu ni
by sincerely, immediately
risou no jibun ni naru!
becoming the me I've dreamed of!
suki na koto wo zutto
With all the things I love,
koko ni shirushitetai kara
I want to make my mark here forever
doushitemo dounikashitemo
So whatever happens, no matter what it takes,
yume janai tte sakebou
let's shout out that this isn't a dream
honmono da to iikikaseta
I always had been told
tsukurimono no ashita toka wo
our artificial future laid out for us was real
suteru yuuki mo hitsuyou da yo
Gather the courage to abandon that path
mae ni mukau tame ni
so you may face forwards
jibun no koe hibiku tokoro he
Off towards the place where you can hear your own voice,
asu mo aragatte yukeru
you have the strength to keep on fighting
pawaa wo tayasanaide yukeba
Never lose that power,
kanau kara
and your dreams will become reality
tsutaetai koto ga aru no
That's why I have something I want you to know
kono kimochi katachi ni shite
I'll show you just what I mean
massugu ni ima sugu ni
by sincerely, immediately
risou no jibun ni naru!
becoming the me I've dreamed of!
suki na koto wo zutto
With all the things I love,
koko ni shirushitetai kara
I want to make my mark here forever
doushitemo dounikashitemo
So whatever happens, no matter what it takes,
yume janai tte sakebou
let's shout out that this isn't a dream
detarame demo
However unreasonable it seems,
yumemita risou nara
if your ideal is one you dream of,
sutecha dame nanda yo
you can't cast it aside
chiisakatta watashitachi no omoi
Our dreams had once been small
sukoshi zutsu sodatete
I want to nurture them bit by bit
kanadetai koto ga aru yo
There's so many things I want to make music with,
egakitai koto ga aru yo
so many things I want to draw
tsutaetai koto ga aru no
There's something I want you to know
kono kimochi katachi ni shite
I'll show you just what I mean
massugu ni ima sugu ni
by sincerely, immediately
risou no jibun ni naru!
becoming the me I've dreamed of!
suki na koto wo zutto
With all the things I love,
koko ni shirushitetai kara
I want to make my mark here forever
doushitemo dounikashitemo
So whatever happens, no matter what it takes,
yume janai tte sakebou
let's shout out that this isn't a dream