■
Ugh,
there's
not a
single
thing
to do
■
that's
remotely
fun.
■
I think
I'm gonna
die from
boredom.
■
If that's
the case,
■
then
tomorrow,
■
why don't
we go on
a date?
■
Spring
is coming,
after all.
■
We'll meet
up at that
bus stop
■
We'll meet
up at that
bus stop
■
and go
to the
Town of
Jade.
■
So I fell
into a deep
slumber,
and once
my senses
returned,
I was
floating
in the air,
surrounded
by light
Towards
heaven
I fall
Perpendicular
to the ground
Skirt
fluttering,
flipped
headlong
■
It won't stop,
I can't stop
■
this
impulse
of mine
But if
there were
a love that could...
Music
Mer
Manga
Ameya Ema
Ugh,
If only, tomorrow,
the world
would
just end.
A meteorite
would fall
from the sky
■
and burn
everything,
everything
■
to the
ground–
or so
I wish...
■
"Come
over
here,"
you
beckon
to me
■
"Come
over
here,"
you
beckon
to me
■
Don't worry, it's safe.
Hide in here.
■
And through
a deserted,
burnt field,
■
the two
of us
go sw-sw-
swimming
Towards
heaven
I fall
Perpendicular
to the ground
Skirt
fluttering,
flipped
headlong
■
It won't stop,
I can't stop
This impulse
of mine
But if
there were
a love that could...
I take my
parasol
Swing it around,
lu-la-li la-la
■
I don't
want to
■
grow up.
There's not
a single
good thing
about it.
There's not
a single
good thing
about it.
We are, in this town,
surely being given
the chance to start over once again
Bright
and kind,
our normal lives
overflow with happiness...
Towards
heaven
I fall
Perpendicular
to the ground
Skirt
fluttering,
flipped
headlong
■
You are
my only
light
■
Always
have, and
always
will be
■
So for always being with me,
thank you.
Your hands
slip through as they fade
Town of Jade