"I am me,"
I shouted on
that summer day
To the Lonely You and
The Lone Me
Suzumu feat. Hatsune Miku
Movie Marie
When we were
young, we saw
those stories
in a dream
One by one,
we spoke of
them, and they
began to bud
In this wide,
spacious world,
you watched
over me, who
was nothing
"I'll make your
dreams come true"
What wishful
thinking
Enveloped
by smoke,
everything
seemed like
a dream
In an
unknown
place,
Eligibility Notification
Chorus Contest Federation
You are eligible for the 2013 All-Japan Junior Chorus contest.
I was
a liar,
just like your
forced smiles
Hey, those
sunset-colored
stories
are blending
into one
During tough
times, when I
spoke of made-
up stories
that weren't
ones we
dreamed out
Miracle Voice
tears
overflowed
The simply
pitiful,
pitiful me,
unable
to speak of
the names of
my parents
"Who is this?
This isn't me,"
I said
and a
requiem
was born
Enveloped
by smoke,
You and I
were both
like lies
In an
unknown
place,
I was not
myself
and became
a complete
stranger
To this now
breathless
story,
To this now
breathless
story,
I'm sorry
take care----------
As you stood
on stage,
I was somehow
reflected
painfully
About that
summer day,
I'd been
mistaken
is what
I realized
If I could
go back,
I would,
but I
can't
It can't end,
an adult
smeared
with greed
laughing and
hoping to
live forever
"I don't
want that"
Enveloped
by smoke,
everything
seemed
like a
dream
Goodbye,
our one
and only
loved
"one",
impure
grown-up
feelings
I'll simply sing
a song that
can't be sold
Let it reach
"us"
To the Lonely You and the Lone Me