【Kotonoha Project】
【Music: Tanaka Hidekazu (MONACA)】
【Vocals: Lon】
Pranks
【Illustration: Shiduki Sayaka】
I can't seem to sit still
I haven't even accepted...
the written challenge, and it's showtime?!
Tug off my ribbon
True
Nature
Favorite
Food
Brat
Soul
As my tongue savors the sweet taste of
the mark of a hero
I discreetly arm my trap
Try and open up the door!
My objective - dumbfoundment
Impossible to forsee
The boundary line lets off a dizzying light
Ah, my pure heart had always dreamed of
wandering the picture book world, lost; Now, let's jump in
"Nothing in this world happens without any meaning,"
a bug monologued as if its words had meaning
Oh, just go eat shit
What a loveable sigh
When I was still free of impurities, I had drawn
landscapes you could see even with your eyes closed
Able to touch, to hear places I had never experienced before
Moving at 200 km/hour when completely still
What a strange world...
It's a one-way trip; I'll get you!
True
Nature
Ritsu
Law
Brat
Childhood Friend
Soul
Protagonist
Favorite
Food
W☯rd