Earphones and a Chorus of Cicadas
They don't taste bad enough to throw away,
but aren't good enough to call tasty, either
Downing cheap goods from the vending machine monopoly,
today was the color of summer
As the sunlight beat down,
I dashed across the hot asphalt
Alone on a journey to a world unknown,
towards the world of summer I've longed for my whole life
Not a single person in town 'cause of the sun
I streamed a tune through my earphones
drowned out by the chorus of cicadas
and the sounds of summer carried on the wind
Some sort of irritation nags at me
and I can't throw out the negativity from yesterday,
but the dew formed from anxiety and regrets
is washed away by the evening showers in the world of summer
A Summer Dream
All I want is to live a summer dream
Even after I get rid of all the emotions I don't need,
the unending cries are as loud as ever
"See, everything's okay here, no problem!"
I threw out my bluffs at pretending to be strong
Emptying on the inside, I made my presence transparent
All I want is to live a summer dream
Please, don't wake me
The trees don't cast shade anymore
and the sky's cries have stopped
Where did they go?
And what about my voice?
Drowning in cries,
in some corner of summer,
smiling...
All I want is to live in today, just like this
If each time I find myself wanting something,
I'll end up losing something else...
I'm no longer someone who'd wish like that
So whatever I may lose in the future,
I vow to always look towards the future
If that's enough to make me forget
the colors of that summer,
then with these tears and the price I've had to pay,
I hope I can once again sing with a smile...
Earphones and a Chorus of Cicadas