Heisei Project
Izanami SuppressionMilitary History
Zips
Heiwa
Kairiki Bear
Nachuki
Crossing with voices is to
show haughty weakness
Lies and corruption
will depend on this one swing
Any sort of guesses
will cloud unfamiliar eyes
To agitate the other,
we raised our middle fingers
Having lost
sight of the
meaning
in this
stagnate
world,
I send you this challenge
Even after
you fall
from defeat
in battle
Izanami will bet
the four seasons,
I was threatened
As things have
ended up,
a sprout may
bloom while
that is still held,
As things have
ended up,
a sprout may
bloom while
that is still held,
but don't let it recover,
spear and shield
If you can love the past,
remaining wounds will heal
Affectation and bravado
will drown in this deception
Any sort of irrationality
will cruelly hold aloft faults
So we,
to strike,
lowerd our thumbs
Breaking
free from
reality
in this
artificial
world,
let it resound until it reaches you
Hold up that flower high
even while amazed by secret liaison
Izanami
will bet
ignorance,
I was swayed
As things have
ended up,
you may be led
further than
you wished,
As things have
ended up,
you may be led
further than
you wished,
but don't ask,
spear and shield
Flashing our blades at one another,
after we clash with one another,
let it reach you
Even after...
Even after
you fall
from defeat
in battle
Izanami will make
the right move,
I was forgiven
As things have
ended up,
your body may
be cut up while
that is still held up,
As things have
ended up,
your body may
be cut up while
that is still held up,
but don't disappear,
spear and shield