Project・Production
Committee of Members of the Committee of Young Girls' Books
One
Two
Three
Four
beginning beginning
Outline So Far
This world is so shallow!
A girl with such a complaint
towards her surroundings,
and society, Tsujima Ayaka,
met a strange boy
in the library one day.
■
Boy
The boy asked Ayaka,
「Do you really think there's something wrong with this world?」
Though bewildered, she nodded. The boy, after saying that
he wanted to make the just world she was thinking of, left
the library behind.
Tower
When she left the library, chasing after the boy,
she found a large tower standing there.
■
The boy said,
「The source of this
world's problems
is at the tower's top.」
Lyrics・Composition・ Draft・Script
Karasuyasabou
Anonymous.
■
This tower is a miniature copy of the "world",
and a being causing the world to warp
is at the top.
The boy said this
as Ayaka had her eye on the top of the tower.
For the sake of correcting this world covered in mistakes...
Rooms
There were various rooms within the tower.
A room of people who had stopped thinking,
a room of people who worshiped something fanatically.
A room of people who were drowning in violent pleasure.
The seal "Censored" had been stamped onto all of their faces.
Ayaka remembered those days and felt conviction.
「Like I thought, there's something wrong with this world.」
■
Voice
The inside of the tower itself was like a
frivolous spectacle, and Ayaka couldn't
bear to think that this was a miniature
copy of the world. She asked the people
inside the rooms,
「Don't you think this is strange?」
However, they turned a deaf ear. At the
same time as Ayaka said those words,
laughter resounded from the skies,
erasing her voice.
Doing likewise, the residents again laugh.
Last
Stop
Ayaka arrived at the room at the top of the tower.
A single girl wearing a mask was there.
She was the source of the tower's, the world's problems.
Ayaka and the girl faced one another.
She was a girl who resembled someone very closely.
Shiduki Sayaka
Character Design・Illust.
Unrest
Ayaka killed that girl.
She believed the distortion in the world would be resolved with this.
So, she went to see the state of the tower's rooms.
She believed in a world where everyone would think and act by themselves.
However, reality was not as such.
She was met by the tower's rooms, only increasing in insanity.
「Why?! Wasn't that girl supposed to be the source?!」
Her actions which she believed were justice
didn't bear fruit to anything.
Only the truth that she killed a girl was left.
■
Loss
Ayaka talked to the people in the tower again.
The voice from the sky had disappeared, but the
people were even more creepier than before,
cackling and laughing, and continued to call
out cryptic words.
She tried to run from the disastrous scene she had
seen, but the door through which she entered
had disappeared.
Ayaka fell into despair.
She wasn't able to change the world, nor was
she able to run away from the truth.
Mad-
ness
Ayaka, who had lost her destination, lived a
despair-filled life as a resident of the tower. Her hair
lengthened, her face grew worn, and before she
knew it, began thinking that even thinking in this
world was foolish.
Ayaka despised that kind of world,
and laughed, "AHAHAHAHAHAHA".
The residents of the tower who witnessed this
called her a lunatic.
Having gotten the idea to jump off
from the tower's top and end everything,
Ayaka went towards the room at the top.
■
Mask
On the rooftop, Ayaka heard a voice saying,
「I have been anticipating your arrival, new master of this tower!」
While Ayaka remained bewildered, the voice continued.
「New master, please take that mask on the wall
and guide this degenerate world.
・・ ・・・ ・・・  ・・・
There is no one but you here!
As long as you have that mask, the people in this tower
will prostrate themselves before you at once.」
Ayaka took the mask and obtained power.
With this, Ayaka tried to make the people
use her justice.
Don
Mixing・Mastering
Justified Genocide
Trou-
ble-
some
words
I'll destroy them
before your eyes
Right
now,
the real
answer is
a meaningless
construction
■
censored
Your
cry
won't
be heard by anyone
Or, rather,
I won't let it (lol)
A humorous
imagination
is, of
course,
just illusions
Mass psychology
and
cheap
psych
ology
Look, look
every
one
Towards where
my hands clap,
you can advance.
So to not have anyone doubt
a wildly enthusiastic
show
report
Anyone, the secret police
「Burn him!
that guy's
an ideology violator
One and all are in a daze
disposal purge of
the ones left out
So to not have anyone notice
「Shut your eyes,
just as
god says
The saturation point
of ethics and madness
a bellowing
parade
will probably
kill
you.
You're the one with the wrongdoing!
because justice is only
on the side of the victor,
right?!
Ayaka penetrated the tower
with her own justice
and the fierce effectiveness of the mask
manifested a power
which seemed as if it could
obtain everything in the world.
Everyone prostrated themselves before her
and everyone obeyed her.
She had obtained
the absolute power called "justice".
Everyone thought
similarly, and it became
a world where everything
was how one thought.
「With this, the world
has become just」
Saying this, she looked up at the skies
and revealed her joy.
Her laughter
was already that of a lunatic's.
With the power of "justice",
Ayaka corrected
people's thought,
to make sure they would think.
However, within them
were some who insisted
for the freedom of not thinking.
Ayaka got angry, and thoroughly purged
those people.
Before long, all of the people
were trained to believe
that not thinking was evil,
and censored humans were produced.
That place had already
become a world where
whether or not people were thinking was uncertain.
■
censored
Anonymous.
Fake
words
I'll line nothing
but them up
before your eyes
Right
now,
according to
justice,
everyone
On the philosophers'
gallows,
will disappear
So to not have anyone doubt
market logic's
propaganda
So no one will be able to say it,
a megaphone
giving a report
with propensity
One and all are in a daze
boys and girls
become swords
So while remaining ignorant,
shut your eyes and
await the next order
The saturation point
of reason and absurdity
You'll be killed
by a parade
of bellows
Before that,
standing up is futile, that's right,
because justice is only
on the side of the victor,
right?!
So to not have anyone doubt
a wildly enthusiastic
show
report
Anyone, the secret police
「Burn him!
that guy's
an ideology violator
One and all are in a daze
disposal purge of
the ones left out
While you shout yourself hoarse
the words you cry out
will be trampled over
The saturation point
of ethics and madness
a bellowing
parade
will probably
kill
you.
You're the one with the wrongdoing!
because justice is only
on the side of the victor,
right?!
Literature Girl Insane
Volume 4「The Truth's Propa...」
Ayaka, who had the tower's inside made as she had wanted,
knew someone trespassed within the tower one day.
■
That intruder had looked at a room within the tower and said,
「There is something wrong with this world.」
and began explaining to the residents.
「That's not possible!
This place is perfect!」
Thinking so, Ayaka laughed.
As her voice resounded throughout the tower,
the residents simultaneously laughed.
■
Ayaka had decided
to pay it no mind at first,
but the intruder began climbing
the tower's stairs,
which the residents definitely would not ascend.
Those footsteps gradually got louder,
and finally drew near.
■
Ayaka had remembered
something tremendous.
At the same time,
vigorously,
the door to the top floor was opened.
Behind the door,
a girl with a very familiar face
was watching suspiciously in this direction.
The words Ayaka had once heard in her head were repeated.
■
「There is no one but you here.」
End