I ask the girl inside the mirror,
How can I forget?
Memories
Within the Mirror
Song: Asa
Guitar: Hirosue Kei　　Piano: Mossan　　Tuning: cillia
Illustration: Shigure Ui　　Video: ke-sanβ
What kind of expression
does the me reflected in the mirror have?
One thing after another keeps coming into my mind
The places we went to, your kind words
Getting emotional over only arguing,
being unable to say even 「I'm sorry」
What do I say, what should I do
so I can start over?
I ask the girl inside the mirror,
How can I forget?
If everything there is the complete opposite,
take me away to the inside of the mirror
Am I no good?
The two already separated...
from the finger which pushed
the history button,
are released
Saying the same things over and over,
how many times has it been?
Will I be able to forget? Are these feelings,
is everything fading away?
Your smile, likeable quirks,
even though you'd embraced me...
I ask the girl inside the mirror,
How can I forget?
If everything there is the complete opposite,
take me away to the inside of the mirror
I ask from within the mirror,
Am I still good enough?
I know that's not true,
but my feelings are overflowing
Am I no good?
The two already separated...
from the finger which pushed
the history button,
are released