■A Certain Girl's Gluttony
_______________________________________
I've gotta eat this, that, those things, everything!
_________________________________________________
It'd be a total waste if it weren't made into my flesh or blood!
_____________________________________________________
Since, you know, I can't be satisfied by anything other than eating.
________________
I mean, in this town,
_____________________________
there's just isn't enough of whatever
_____________________
fills me up from my heart.
I want to keep eating on and on, forever and ever.
And if I can't,
I think I'm gonna go crazy!
Shoveling Down
Already, already, already empty
Vacant, vacant, vacant, hollow
Eagerly, eagerly, eagerly wanting
Gurgle gurgle, gurgle gurgle, a gurgling void
Thought I was satisfied once,
but seems like the time's come again...
Can't sit still, gotta do something -
Come on, we're gonna go take it all in
"Shovel it all down."
Just to keep living on,
I'll follow along with this craving
Before it spoils and goes bad,
shovel it down; shall I offer some to you?
Energy, energy, energy not coming forth
Strength, strength, strength escaping
Hungrier, hungrier, hungrier, hungrier, hungrier, too hungry
Irritated, irritated, irritated, who do you think you are?
Somewhere around an important centre,
seems like that's where it was taken
Let's make sure it's gulped down
by this insuppressible urge already
"Shovel it all down."
Only doing it systematically
makes you feel like you're choking on air
Could you forgive me for being momentarily blinded
by a fast-food, junky invitation?
Although you'll probably regret it later,
this desire can't be won against
However much it pains you, no matter how bad it gets,
you'll continue shoveling it all down, won't you?
Ah, such a savory, fragrant smell,
and a rich, thick flavor...
Natural, fresh raw ingredients...
Can't give up the addiction,
this is bad...
Kept alive, roused up,
processed, hidden,
sweet, bitter, sour, salty;
I accept this endlessly expansive blessing harvest with thanks,
Next, raised and reared, tied up and together, drink and eat...
Eat...
Eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...
eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...eat...
Pretend it's unappetizingly bitter,
you might've been saved...
Pretend it's unappetizingly sweet,
no matter how much it's spoiled or already been eaten into...
"I'll shovel it all down."
Just to be satisfied, I'll kneel down before this craving
Before it spoils and goes bad,
I'll shovel it down, graciously accept the energy,
for you, for you;
Shall I show you?
Shoveling Down