As the Gods Say
Composition & Song
Rerulili
Illustrations
Ichinose Yukino
Engineering
KagomeP
Video
Makinosena　Sorarimu
Nothing ever goes the way I want it to,
and I can't help but hate myself for it
To hide from these eight million pains and sorrows,
I've gone off on a search
for a place I can hide away in
I'd rather stay inside a rocky crevice
and sleep without regard for the sun or moon
Why was I even born in the first place?
I don't know, it just doesn't make sense
But while it may seem like that,
it means you have the ability to become even greater
And I'll tell you why
That's right,
As us gods say,
at our every command,
everyone loves the Earth
Drink and sing!
Everyone, be merry
It's not so bad once in a while
That's right,
from north to south,
from right to left,
one thing or another
loves the Earth
The path may be muddy,
but we can still walk forwards
We've still got a
long ways ahead of us
I just want to be a fair person
and I'm sure everyone else wishes to be the same,
but the eight million imperfections in my heart
torment me every day
Why was I born?
I guess you could call it a miracle,
but that'd really be no more than a coincidence,
so I guess there actually isn't any meaning to it...
But, if there're guys out there who bully you,
that means that you're a very great person
And I'll tell you why
That's right,
As us gods say,
at our every command,
everyone loves the Earth
When I laugh
and you laugh, too
everything is forgiven
That's right,
girls and boys
naturally love each other
Just like that,
the world keeps spinning
The path may be muddy,
but let's still walk forwards
We've still got a
long ways ahead of us
The things which are truly important,
they're unexpectedly among the seemingly-worthless things
So let's mess around all together
and dance unclothed, laughing loudly
That's right,
As us gods say,
at our every command,
I'm able to love myself even more and more
Take a look in the mirror
You finally understand, don't you?
You're the light which lets everyone shine
That's right
As us gods say,
thank you, everyone
I really do love the Earth
Let's make a flower bloom,
a huge one
One so giant it'll reach all the way to heaven!
■
Lyrics & Composition　Rerulili
Engineering　KagomeP
Illustrations　Ichinose Yukino
Video　Makinosena & Sorarimu
As the Gods Say