Dear onii-chan,
Sorry for being late. I was finally able to send this.
The sunflowers are growing even taller than us, so they'd surely be easy to find from the sky.
Where are you flying right now?
That person is, even now, with the sunflower landmark...
Your Sky is Sorrowful
Dear person in the future,
I'll entrust this letter to you, okay?
It doesn't matter how many years have passed
This is proof that I'd lived, to her
The ticket I showed you was one-way
and you congratulated me with skinny cheeks
Ah, I hate honor, it's of secondary importance
So long
In the blue sky, I think of you,
as I'm mistaken for a silver arrow
Your sky is sorrowful
The clouds swim, my first love
To a dear person,
forgive me for this letter, okay?
I can't go home no matter how many years pass
You're not crying, are you? I'm worried
As we watched the sunflowers in tedium,
they bloomed in a line with a smile
Ah, home and social status are things of secondary importance
I fell into love for the first time
In the sunset, I think of you,
singing praises of silver arrows
Your sea is sorrowful,
the water's surface being dyed in the crimson of love
An important-seeming letter
from a slightly dirty box,
after many decades pass,
finally reaches you
I think of you today, too
Among sunflowers, a flower garden
While viewing this scenery,
could you please smile?
In the blue sky, I think of you,
as I'm mistaken for a silver arrow
Your sky is sorrowful
Together with that, I think of my last love
Your Sky is Sorrowful