Composition ・ Lyrics
Marasy
Vocals
Kagamine Rin
Bass
drm
Illust. ・ Cont.
Kitsune
Video
Tansangata
Rebellion of the Arc Fox
Today as well,
I'm once again alone,
my shout echoing
towards the darkness,
Mother,
Mother
The day that smile was lost
on a trip to the starry heavens
is only a distant
memory
The timid,
cowardly
kit fox's
first bit of
selfishness
Call forth courage,
raise the start signal
Now, jump into the first battle
With an excited impulse,
the fox dashes through,
dreaming of eternal happiness
Oppose fate
Fire was opened
Rebellion of the arc fox
The moment
we'd bid good-bye,
how had you felt,
Mother,
Mother?
Was it joy? Sorrow?
Fleeting, glistening pupils
only wet
this smile
The timid,
cowardly
kit fox's
first bit of
selfishness
Aah, I hate being alone!
Now, jump into the first battle
It's impossible to return afterwards
The fox dashes
towards the cloudless sky
Oppose fate,
because what you want
is there
The timid,
cowardly
kit fox's
first bit of
selfishness
"Once more,
I want to see you, I want to see you!
it shouts to the celestial fox
Now, jump into the first battle
The last fox from the beginning
dashes through,
dreaming of eternal happiness
Oppose fate
Seize it back with those hands
Rebellion of the arc fox
Mother, I'm home