Weekend Heroines
Koko☆Natsu
Where? There? Over there? I can't find it?!
Papaya, mango, coco☆nuts!
Strawberry-flavored shaved ice
Stick out your tongue and it's bright, bright red!
Late summer heat, a swimsuit show! Say!
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-daaah!
Coco☆nuts!
Yay!
The sun beats down on us, hot and dry
(Passhuba! Coconuts, baby!)
It's the season everyone's been waiting for - it's summer!
I put all my thought into buying this bikini
and I'm super embarrassed, but can't afford to lose!
Coconut-flavored sunscreen
(Passhuba! Coconuts, baby!)
UV rays, the lasers of a neverending summer
My heart skips two beats when you look over here
It feels like it's gonna explode☆
Sa-shi-su-se; there's summer, baby!
Da-di-du-de; where's summer? Baby
Ka-ki-ku-ke; here's summer, baby!
Sun! Sun! Summertime!
YES!!!
Co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-coco☆nuts!
Co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-
co☆nuts! Coco☆nuts!
Coconuts!
Melon-flavored shaved ice
Stick out your tongue and it's a zombie!
It's a showoff; put on a yukata and bon dance! Say!
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-daaah!
Here we go! C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
The nights are hot, slow, and humid
(Passhuba! Coconuts, baby!)
Makes me wanna drink some coconut juice
Long as it seems, we've only got so much summertime
First come, first served!
Sa-shi-su-se; there's summer, baby!
Da-di-du-de; where's summer? Baby
Ka-ki-ku-ke; here's summer, baby!
Sun! Sun! Summertime!
YES!!!
Co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-coco☆nuts!
Co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-
co☆nuts! Coco☆nuts!
Coconuts!
Fire!!
S-s-s-sparking!
L-l-l-l-l-limbo! Fever!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Hot-hot, burning summer!
Kujuukuri Beach!
Ultra-sweet ice-cream!
Our camp is Saitama!
Sa-shi-su-se; there's summer, baby!
Da-di-du-de; where's summer? Baby
Ka-ki-ku-ke; here's summer, baby!
Sun! Sun! Summertime!
YES!!!
Co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-coco☆nuts!
Co-co-co-co co-co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-co-co co-co-co co-co co-co-co-
co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-
co☆nuts! Coco☆nuts!
Co☆nuts! Coco☆nuts!
Where? There? Over there? I can't find it?!
Papaya, mango, coco☆nuts!
Nuts!