■
click
shut...
I'm
off!
Nac-
chan!
Morning~
Sorry,
Did I
keep you
waiting?
No-
pe.
It's
totally
fine.
■
What do
we have for
first period
today?
English.
Didn't I tell
you we had
a quiz?
Wh-
at?!
Serio-
usly?
■
By
the way,
Nacchan,
did you
manage to
tell Seto-
guchi-kun
yester-
day?
Argh!
Let me
tell you
all about
that~
What
is it?
Do
tell.
slump
■
I'm
sorry it's
so sudden,
but...
I've
liked you
for a long
time now!
■
Huh?!
Ju...
■
Just
kidding!
There's
no way
that'd
actually
be true!
Did I
get ya
good?
Natsuki...
you're
really...
wri
ggle
pause...
■
It's a
confession
rehearsal.
Huh?
Rehear-
sal?
■
So?
Was I
cute?
Did
your
heart
skip a
beat?
stare...
D-don't
look at me
like that...
I'm sorry...
■
So you're
gonna get
serious?
■
E-
eh...
Eh
~~
~!
That
was a
lie.
smack
Uu...
trem
ble
Now
we're
even.
■
So,
Who're
you really
going to
confess
to?
■
There's
no way
I can
tell
you!
Ow
ow!!
hit
Hey, c'mon.
Help me
practice～
Guess I've got
no choice.
Yay!
But treat me
to ramen first.
Eeehh?
■
And then,
after that,
we ate at that
ramen place
in front of the
station on the
way back! It
was really
good...
Though it was my
treat...
soft and warm
Wow...
I see...
■
gasp
Wait,
this
isn't
good
at
a
l
!
gasp
Wait,
this
isn't
good
You're cuter
when you're
silent.
Come on,
close
your
legs.
■
How
about
you and
Haruki,
Miou?
Huh?
I...
Things
are
going
nor-
mally!
What's that
supposed
to mean?
It means
what it
means!
■
How
about
you and
Haruki,
Miou?
Huh?
I...
Things
are
going
nor-
mally!
What's that
supposed
to mean?
It means
what it
means!
■
So,
What
about you,
Akari-
chan?
Huh?
Me?
Oh,
don't
worry
about
me.
More
importantly,
we've gotta
think about
Nacchan's
confession
strategy!
Thank
yoooou,
Akari-chan!
So,
What
about you,
Akari-
chan?
Huh?
Me?
Oh,
don't
worry
about
me.
More
importantly,
we've gotta
think about
Nacchan's
confession
strategy!
Thank
yoooou,
Akari-chan!
■
I'll do
my best!
Yeah~!
I'll do
my best!
Yeah~!
■
...!
Akari!
Come to think
of it, you'd
dodged the
question
ealrier.
Huh?
What
was it,
again?
We
were
talking
about who
you like...
Wh-
at?!
■
Good
morning!
Morn'.
Hey,
Haruki!
Don't
put your
butt on
people's
desks!
slump...
Good
morning!
Morn'.
Hey,
Haruki!
Don't
put your
butt on
people's
desks!
slump...
■
Good
morning!
Morn'.
Hey,
Haruki!
Don't
put your
butt on
people's
desks!
slump...
■
Just
warming
it up for
you.
Who
d'you
think you
are, Hide-
yoshi?!
Natsuki...
so you
know who
Hideyoshi
is, huh?
Of
co-
urse
i do!
...wait,
Mochita,
what's
wrong?
...oh,
nothing
really.
■
Just
warming
it up for
you.
Who
d'you
think you
are, Hide-
yoshi?!
Natsuki...
so you
know who
Hideyoshi
is, huh?
Of
co-
urse
i do!
...wait,
Mochita,
what's
wrong?
...oh,
nothing
really.
■
ding
dong
dang
chatter
■
Ah.
Haruki,
some-
one's
waiting
for
you.
Got it,
I'm co-
ming.
See
you
tomor-
row!
■
Are
those
two going
out?
Beats
me...
■
Yuu~...
When they say,
"A single love
continuing for
a long time,"
They mean
"unrequited
love"...
■
I know,
I get
what
you
mean
So
you don't
need to
say any
more...
Let's go grab
ramen.
■
I'm
home.
■
Wah,
no, that's
not it!
Hina-chan!
A-ah!
Watch
out!
Wai-
Nacchan,
what're
you do-
ing?!
click
■
Just
what're
you two
doing in
someone
else's
room...
Ah,
onii-chan!
Welcome
home!
Welcome back.
You're so late!
Where've you
been?
Does it
really
matter?
It's a
confession
rehearsal.
■
Is it
alright
for you to be
over at a guy's
house this
late?
Huh?
Why?
You're
an ex-
ception,
aren't
you?
■
So,
what'd you
come here
for today?
Hehe~
I was thi-
nking you
could help
me with
home-
work-
So,
not for
the ga-
mes...
Of
course
not!!
■
So,
what'd you
come here
for today?
Hehe~
I was thi-
nking you
could help
me with
home-
work,
So,
not for
the ga-
mes...
Of
course
not!
■
So,
what'd you
come here
for today?
Hehe~
I was thi-
nking you
could help
me with
home-
work-
So,
not for
the ga-
mes...
Of
course
not!!
■
tick
tock
Say...
■
If,
If I
happen
to get a
boyfriend...
What would
you do?
tick
tock
Hm?
Well, as
your rehearsal
partner, I'd have
to cheer you
on, right?
■
I see.
Thank
you.
■
...do
your
best.
■
Haa.
Of all people,
Why am I her practice
partner...
Although I was the
one who agreed...
■
Who is she
confessing
to...?
Who is she
confessing
to...?
■
Haa...
Are we
going out
or are we
not? I have
no idea...
I don't
have any
courage,
do I...
■
Everyone's
in love, huh.
I wonder if
I'll fall in
love some-
day too....
Who does
she like...?
she like...?!
slap
■
Yuu's kind
and soft-
hearted...
■
Do
your
best.
So he's
always
being a
good
friend
to me,
always
cheering
me on...
■
Even if
I came
to like
someone,
would he
just accept
that for me?
■
Tomor-
row's
the real
deal.
To-
morrow...
tomor-
row, I'll
definite-
ly...
Try
to
con-
fes
s
Tomor-
row's
the real
deal.
To-
morrow...
tomor-
row, I'll
definite-
ly...
Try
to
con-
fes
s
■
ding-a-ling-a-ling
chirp
■
Today's
most favo-
rable sign
is...
■
Yeah!
Cancer,
lucky
you!
Yeah!
Cancer,
lucky
you!
■
All
good!
ding
dong...
■
Mor-
ning!
Nacchan,
good
mor...?
■
What
hap-
pened
to
your
face?
You like
it? I'm
going to
give it my all
today, so
I tried to
up my fe-
minine
appeal...
No,
it's ac-
tually
kinda...
yeah.
Y-
yeah...
Huh?
What?!
We'll be
coming
in for
a bit!
Now,
take
off
that
lip-
sti-
ck...
Fake
eye-
la-
shes
too!
And
after
that,
your
foun-
dation.
Wha-
aat?
Why?!
■
Mor-
ning!
Nacchan,
good
mor...?
What
hap-
pened
to
your
face?
You like
it? I'm
going to
give it my all
today, so
I tried to
up my fe-
minine
appeal...
No,
it's ac-
tually
kinda...
yeah.
Y-
yeah...
Huh?
What?!
We'll be
coming
in for
a bit!
Now,
take
off
that
lip-
sti-
ck...
■
Fake
eye-
la-
shes
too!
And
after
that,
your
foun-
dation.
Wha-
aat?
Why?!
■
Hey,
Yuu.
Hn?
What?
■
You're too
soft-hearted.
If you don't
like it, just
say so.
What's
this, all
of a su-
dden?
You
know
what I'm
talking
about.
No,
I really
don't.
■
If you've
got someone
you like as well,
then you should
be more honest
about it.
Oh, is
he talking
about our
confession
rehearsal?
Did he
hear some-
thing from
Aida...?
■
Be
more
honest?
Hey,
I'm gonna
leave you
behind!
Haruki,
you're the
last person I
want to hear
that from...
Be
more
honest?
Hey,
I'm gonna
leave you
behind!
Haruki,
you're the
last person I
want to hear
that from...
■
Sensei!
I'm
stepping out
for a bit...
Nacchan!
Your textbook's
upside down!!
Um...
Didn't you
buy a bit
too much?
But I've
gotta fill
my stomach
so I can
go off to
war munch
munch...
This will
be it!
ding
dong
dang
clatter
■
Ah-
Wait!
grab
■
...!
Ah...
■
This is
the last
time...
The
last...?
So please
practice
with me.
■
It really,
really is
the
last
time.
It really,
really is
the
last
time.
■
Nac-
chan...
Do
your
best.
■
Well,
since
practice
is over,
I'll be
heading
home
soon.
■
Ah...
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
Ah...
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
Ah...
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
clench
■
Wait.
Wait...!
■
clench
...!
Wait!
I like you!
Huh?
Everything I said about a
confession rehearsal was a lie!
You're the one...
You're the one that I like, so much that I can't take it!
I'm not very girly,
get jealous easily, and I don't like it
when I'm not taken out on dates often…
I'm a self-centered idiot, but...
but...
I want you to go out with me!
...heh.
Obviously,
I’m the only one that could put up with you, right?
Me too.
I feel the same way.