●
☯
●●
Word Karma
Haphazardly put-away
emotions dirty you
Ear-splitting wails
begin to disturb the night
Average
Student
Order with the name of "freedom"
is tying you down with cold chains
Mischievously clinging affection,
Disciplinary
Committee
according to various consi-
derations, shall be given a day off
Like, hate, like, hate- absolutely hate...
Like, hate, like, hate- not interested...
I'll come meet you right now
The boy resisting oppression
is illuminated by the spotlight, his heart incomplete
He has something even deeper than justice inside -
kindness to cut through the darkness
Let my words...set forth karma.
Positive and negative
The intro starts from left and right,
engraving "the impermanence of worldly things,"
Anonymous slander,
immersed in self-satisfaction, completely ridiculous
Hurry, break through the minefield of
electronic currents as soon as you can
And sever the chain of despair-
Who's laughing in the end?
Like, hate, like, hate- absolutely hate...
Like, hate, like, hate- not interested...
Embrace me right now
The boy fighting against his shackles
is illuminated by the spotlight, his body incomplete
He has something even deeper than justice inside -
the strength to overcome sadness
The boy resisting oppression
is illuminated by the spotlight, his heart incomplete
He has something even deeper than justice inside -
kindness to cut through the darkness
Let my words...set forth karma.