FuwariP
(Enthusiastically) Adoon!
Another Cheerful Day
Lyrics・Song
FuwariP
(Enthusiastically) Yeah, yeah!
Illust.
Yunkel
(Enthusiastically) Afuafua
Video
(Enthusiastically) Yeah, yeah!
Vocals
(Enthusiastically) Afuu
(Native) The clock's bell resounds in the sky
(Sweet) Today as well, tenteke tententen
(Power) The～re! Pinpiki pinpinpin
(Whisper) Morning opens the curtains
(Adult) and rustles them, tenteke tenten, a tententen tenten
(Sweet) I yawn underneath the sun
(Whisper) and stretch diagonally
(Adult) When I gaze up at the small birds,
(Native) I put a piece of bread in the toaster
(Power) and today starts
(All Together) The city is shining brilliantly
(All Together) and everyone is laughing brightly
(All Together) The street continuing towards the plaza
(All Together) swayed with green hair
(Enthusiastically) Adoon!
(Enthusiastically) Yeah, yeah!
(Enthusiastically) Afuu
(Power) It seems like I've accidentally dozed off
(Whisper) A noon tenteke tententen
(Adult) The～re! Pinpiki pinpinpin
(Sweet) The sun climbs the roof
(Native) Playing, tenteke, a tenten tententen
(Adult) I run downhill
(Sweet) and stop at the traffic light
(Native) Looking left, looking right,
(Whisper) Let's look right once more and then cross
(Whisper) Today's another cheerful day
(All Together) The city is shining brilliantly
(All Together) and everyone is laughing brightly
(All Together) The clouds reflected on the car's hood
(All Together) calmly flowed through the sky
(All Together) When I go on a trip,
(All Together) it feels great going wherever I feel like
(Native) Shadows stretch during the evening
(Sweet) Lining up, light shines through
(Adult) The sound of a bouncing ball somewhere
(Power) spread throughout the sky
(Whisper) Stillness flickers and dances
(Adult) The clock's bell resounded
(Whisper) The small birds flapped their wings
(Native) and crossed over to today
(Sweet) The world continues
(Power) and then continues on
(All Together) The city is shining brilliantly
(All Together) connecting towards the next tomorrow brightly
(All Together) The setting sun's light
(All Together) reflects the sky from another day
(All Together) The rain falls and I'm soaked
(All Together) as I walk through puddles today as well
(All Together) The weather finally clears once again, and then tomorrow comes
(All Together) The city is laughing brightly today as well
(Enthusiastically) Adoon!
Lyrics・Song
FuwariP
(Enthusiastically) Yeah, yeah!
Illust.
Yunkel
(Enthusiastically) Afuafua
Video
Not-116
(Enthusiastically) Yeah, yeah!
Vocals
GUMIs
(Enthusiastically) Afuu