I stepped through fallen leaves,
the color of the sunset
and used their sound to bury,
to hide
Tearstains
I wipe with my hands
which can no longer feel them
Towards the station on the way home,
for the next promise―
don't say anything for my sake
to not bind us together,
to deceive and avoid
the inevitable
words,
「good-bye」
The you before my eyes
is beyond the closed door
which had once told of the beginning
of those days which seemingly never existed,
reflected
in a blurry world
The final bell
rings out to us
from fingertips,
before any words
Full of affection
I want to remember,
I grow reserved
We knew we'd be separated,
yet we had loved,
we'd loved one another,
and just can't let go
can't throw these feelings away
All of mine,
I wanted to make you all mine
If we could meet again after 10 years,
then that'd surely mean
that we were bound together
on paths we set out on
which will never meet―
the two of us,
by a red string
I can't bear them anymore,
they're overflowing
These emotions all towards you
will pass countless nights,
within my chest,
never disappearing
I place my hand on my chest,
bringing out distant memories
That color-filled moment
makes my heartbeat quicken
After 10 years, will those days
between the two of us
still be left behind in your chest?
Mistaken for people simply passing by,
we're destined to
never meet again―
the two of us,
by a red string