After worrying, getting lost, and searching, we're here,
living our dreams
We'll be able to laugh and chat again after 10 years
Let's make those kinds of times
Ama
tsuki
Beginnings are, yes,
modest
The impulse that had bud
within my chest
will, together with time,
grow larger
The story had
begun to move
Kony
The pieces scattered about
here and there,
one by
one,
are pieced together
Itou
Kashi-
tarou
I want to see sceneries
I never have before
That's how I've
been thinking
When alone,
you can't see
this kind of
dream
Because you were there for me,
Even when uneasy
in the darkness,
today as well
the piece had seized
that simple chance
Sing, sing
to the limits of your voice
I want to unite
our space into one
Like that, people again
connect with
others, widening the circle
After worrying, getting lost, and searching, we're here,
living out
our dreams
We'll be able to laugh and chat again after 10 years
Let's make those kinds of times
The miracle
of us being able
to meet underneath the unending sky
I imagine
and want to experience it
Isn't this pretty
amazing?!
The journey continues
At times, it's rough
and tests us, but
The number of wounds we've gotten from falling
gives us a bit of hope to aim towards tomorrow
We run and fall
repeatedly
But this means we'll surely
be able to become stronger
Because I'm sending
this song
to you,
who's waiting on the other side of the road
The strings of our hearts tied together tightly
can't be untied, no matter what happens
We'll be able to laugh and chat again after 10 years
Let's be those kinds of friends
On this path,
doing nothing but
stumbling
Each time,
my readiness
scale
seems like it'll lose against the
weight of the pain
It's hard to breathe,
and my chest hurts
all the more
If it's just playing house,
then is this fine?
The secrets in my chest
cause me to face backwards
I'll tell you that one thing
- I came to see you right now -
Sing, sing to the limits of your voice
I want to unite our space into one
Like that, people again connect with
others, widening the circle
After worrying, getting lost,
and searching, we're here
living our dreams
We'll be able to laugh and chat again after 10 years