Song・Lyrics: GigaP, Reol
Illustration: Makoto
Video: Funmatsu
Free from the meter
programming
"I like you," just kidding―
The usual complaints
Bolts?
Nuts?
They're all just
My gaze on you,
a dangerous war
My chest pounding;
......Shoot an arrow in my
......heart, you know?
I'll use my feminine
...charms and take you
down, bitch
With a verse that'll make
..you and only you SICK
Hey, look over at me
With
the
lips
With
the
lips
With
the
lips
With
the
lips
of a
liar,
show me the limits
of your deceit
I won't take
anyone
but you
And more-
Won't you let me
be even more
selfish?
Love's a winning streak,
only for seasoned veterans
Spout lies,
show off
show off,
lean and
You turn, giving me
your usual troubled face
Yeah, yeah.   Hey, are you even listening?!
But,
I can't bring myself
to hate that part of you,
and
you're a step
above, you'd hit me
I can't talk back,
I just can't
say a thing!
The
angry
The angry face I show you is fake
Rely on me
even more
Desire even more, more
Trouble
yourself
over me even more
I want, want you
to bother me for it
Please, go ahead, do it so rough
there's no time to breathe
I wanna be destroyed
with us as we are right now
Knock Down
Take that unbreathing thing
and force it in my mouth
I wanna be destroyed
with us as we are right now
Knock Down
Listen to my voice even more
Lead me astray with your words,
If you've been programmed to do so,
it's all meaningless
You know
what I want?
I, I alone
to be the
subject
of your
LOVE
In my mind, I keep pretending to be tough
But you've realized the truth, right,
my Darling?
A change in enthalpy,
"Why?!"
I don't know what's
going on anymore
All I want is for you to be next to me
Please, go ahead, do it so rough
there's no time to breathe
I wanna be
destroyed
with us as we
are right now
Take that unbreathing thing
and force it in my mouth
I wanna be destroyed
with us as we are right now
-CREATORS-
Song・Lyrics
GigaP
Reol
Illustration: Makoto
Video: Funmatsu