Song: Nem
Video: Sakuma
Mae
rc
he
n
Maerchen
Boyfriend
Girlfriend
The two were bound by the red string of fate
For now, it seems believeable for eternity
On those
words'
backsides,
deception
we search for
If it's real love,
prove it to me
「Delete all of your addresses
from the opposite sex」
「Pick up
the phone within 10 seconds」
Swaying, (swaying,)
sinking, (sinking)
towards the sea for them two alone
Please give this body (Then,)
stabilizers (once more,)
More, please
「Do you love me?」(「I love you.」)
「I do, too.」(「I'm glad.」)
Giving only as much as we take
My uneasiness worsens (I'm not)
Feigning ignorance, (worried)
We are happy
I intercepted a girl's call to your phone
There's a purikura with a boy in your notebook's pocket
「What's the meaning of this?」
「That's what I should be saying.」
「You sl*t!」
「Let's break up already.」
Swaying, (swaying,)
warping, (warping)
the two's story
However, we're (Infantile)
weak (and foolish)
so we can't end it
「I'm sorry」 (「I am, too」)
「 I love you.」(「 I love you.」)
Each time we repeat those words,
the number of cuts on my arm (Why?)
increase (Stop it already)
Hey, come here right now
Who are you with?
What're you hiding?
I hadn't really liked
someone like you
in the first place
Swaying, (swaying,)
drowning, (drowning)
towards the sea for them two alone
I'll kill you (I'm glad)
Afterthat, (I don't have to see you)
I'll die, too
「Do you love me?」(「I love you.」)
「I do, too.」(「That was a lie.」)
Texts merely for the sake of sending them
Our two-faced (I don't get)
love (anything anymore)
strangles each other
Why?
I like you
That's all it was
supposed to be
Song: Nem
Video: Sakuma
Mae
rc
he
n
Maerchen
Boyfriend
Girlfriend