One and unique souls, take flight into legend...
One for all!
Joined by a mysterious fate! Thanksgiving!
Now, to sum it all up!
Alright! Stop on by! Drop in for a look!
It's a splendid occasion of splendor! (Be moved!)
With a great multitude of rebirths, metamorphosis complete!
Everyone, welcome back~!
Hey wait, the mission! Fortune visits a merry home!
This is the duty of a celestial maiden~!
Come! Pure, positive voltage!
Stage built of linked circles!
Momoclo Heaven☆ Momoclo Heaven☆ Come on by just once!
We'll bloom barren flowers with the sparks of your heart and head for!
Nirvana!
The law of causality's catharsystem (The whole lot!)
Allow me to sublimate all which pains you! (Show must go on!)
Follow the holy light to utopia
Shatter it! The past, the future, carrying karma! (Oh~!)
No rehearsal, it's showtime!
Where you yourself are the Creator (Yeah!)
Go forth! Indomitable resolve!
This is where our Mahorovacation begins!
Working with all you've got will lead to mutual good fortune
With my IEM on, I'll quickly change into my holy feathered kimono~ And enchant you!
Refresh your life! Mahorovacation!
A setlist formulated with fun in mind
Determination surges forth in this space-time grand hall of firmament
Come, follow us~!!
Resonate throughout each part of your spirit and body! (High! High!)
A legacy of aspiration transcending generations! (It's alright!)
Let my voice reach even you (Yeah! Yeah!) beyond the horizon! (Let's go!)
More! Go with the flow! We'll make you dance!
A show where all surprises are welcome! (Extreme!)
This level of courage and charm is standard equipment!
Ignition! A hustle and bustle everyday!
But we appreciate the full house! Triumphant and proud!
Serious! An absolute reckless history!
A story that'll shake the heavens!
Momoclo Heaven☆ Momoclo Heaven☆ Come on by anytime!
Knowing true adversity, your strongest courage is Ananda!
Extraordinary document days (Don't sweat it! Let's do this!)
Your tears will someday become your divine protection! (We are united!)
All deeds of love!
Build up! The relation of all creation in the universe! (Oh~!)
The full score is Akashic!
The great alliance resounds, (Up!) extolling heartbeat!
Everyone, get hyped up! Mahorovacation!
Crossing through the uncivilized world below, let us reunite!
Even a halo is a hot spotlight!
A self-transmission of dreams and passions, sparkling bright!
Going on endlessly! Mahorovacation!
All human emotion packed into a concentrate
In a high octave, the encore echoes
Let's go for one more round!
Smiling when our eyes meet
We are joined when we hold hands
You gave me a baton of light
And once I pass it off again, we'll illuminate a new world!
This is where our Mahorovacation begins!
Working with all you've got will show mutual good fortune in time
With my IEM on, I'll quickly change into my holy feathered kimono~ And enchant you!
Refresh your life! Mahorovacation!
A setlist formulated with fun in mind
Determination surges forth in this space-time grand hall of firmament
Come, follow us~!!
Resonate throughout each part of your spirit and body! (High! High!)
A legacy of aspiration transcending generations! (It's alright!)
Let my voice reach even you (Yeah! Yeah!) beyond the horizon!
Strongly! Strongly!