Massugu
Shiritsu Ebisu Chuugaku
A train bursting at the seams
Even during the most unpleasant times
Just thinking of spending the weekend with you would make the time fly
I've come all this way watching you over a friend's shoulder
So could you praise me for having been able to say that I like you?
Another scandal in the weekly magazine ads hanging in the train
I don't want to become a lying adult
If only we could jump into a world with just the two of us
In this turbulent age of nothing but fake love
Earnestly, I offer to only you every single bit of my love
If it could be taken away by someone, I'll hold onto it so tight it breaks
I love you - do you think could I cling to your arm just a bit longer?
Doing up my hair in a way that matches your preferences
I'm a little lacking in self-confidence as is
But I bet you'd get tired of plain cuteness
Boys are so selfish - have I already lost by falling for you?
I'm listening to that Taylor you like, once again
Getting a hair dye doesn't sound like a bad idea
Though I still lose my balance when I don't hold onto the hanging straps
You and I now climb the staircase to adulthood
Earnestly, one step at a time, stepping our ground carefully
Whenever you feel sad, I'll put a smile on your face
Always right by your side, let's keep holding hands
Hold mine tight
Love, wishes, encounters, building up the future
The miracle that we, out of 100 million, were bound together
The moment that we first kissed
Revealed the reason why we were born
In this turbulent age of nothing but fake love
Earnestly, I offer to only you every single bit of my love
I'll always be by your side, because I'm your number one supporter
I love you - do you think could I cling to your arm just a bit longer?
I want to keep living on for your sake
In this turbulent age of nothing but fake love
Earnestly, I offer to only you every single bit of my love
If it could be taken away by someone, I'll hold onto it so tight it breaks
I love you - do you think could I cling to your arm just a bit longer?