'scuse me!
Hi, hi!
Before I knew it, it was love at first sight
Head over heels!
Dummy.
Look straight at me!
Until you pierce holes through
Let's believe in inspiration, 'kay?
It's not all romantic
I'm well aware!
Throughout my body! (Shiver shiver!!)
As I'm flooded with dazzling music
That's right!
and if I act a little spoiled, you get irritated
But I won't ever let you out of my sight ever again
Yes, I'm crazy about you
The more I dream, the faster my heart beats
Stop, stop, I can't be doing this!
Now, right now's the time!
Let's get this love started!!
Love is glittery; our hearts sparkling
Nothing can stop us now
Love is bursting forth; my heart wide open
I want to connect with you
Go all 'round, glittery
Shine, sparkling
With the rhythm of fate,
let's make our mark in history
Go 'round and 'round
in this Future Bowl of love
A pink heart!
Seriously?
Doesn't matter if you trip and skin your knee red
Oh no!!
Though the bruises of youth are left, purple,
with a high yellow voice, confess!
'kay?
All shades of girls dreamingreen are in big trouble!
When we're together
Yes, yes!!
My world is filled with color
See, see!
My dreams are in bloom, and my hands get sweaty
See, your warmth spreads to me
and the tempo of my chest speeds up
The more I hurry forward, the more my eyes swim in a flurry
Stop, stop, I can't be doing this!
Now, right now's the time!
Let's make the love of our dreams reality!!
Love is glittery; our hearts sparkling
I just can't stop feeling this way
Love springs forth, my heart growing bigger
as I gaze at you
Go all 'round, glittery,
Shine, sparkling
With the rhythm of legends,
let's change the course of history
Go 'round and 'round
in this Future Bowl of love
Yes, I'll plunder your heart
Put my soul into it, bang bang bang
Love mode on full throttle
I'll make you my captive completely
Showing off my moves with a boom boom
Come on! Come on!
I love you!
Hey, this one-in-a-billion encounter must have been fate
Hey, I want to live life with you
There's no time like the present
I want to tell you thank you
I'm truly thankful for you being by my side
Dreaming together with you
Together tomorrow, too
We're always connected
Go all 'round, glittery
Shine, sparkling
With the rhythm of fate,
let's make our mark in history
Go 'round and 'round
in this Future Bowl of love
Love is a legend...
Shrouded in mystery...
Profound...
Shining...
Glittering, sparkling
Sparkling, glittering
in this Future Bowl of love!