Advance Towards the Future!
With the radiance of stardust,
we can illuminate the darkness and go forth
Don't be afraid to advance forwards
Release an arrow of light and cut through the wind!
This friendship we have right here is one that we can always believe in
A guidepost for the path I must walk shines in my chest
We'll push on without looking back!
We can go!
Let's vow to always follow
what we believe is right in our hearts
Right here and right now, let's hold high
our hopes for tomorrow
However tough things get,
I'm sure that we have the strength to face it
Though when alone, we sometimes feel crushed under the weight,
if we help each other out, everything's OK!
Someday, we'll finally reach
the place we've dreamed of
So don't ever forget
that you're not alone; Our bonds are strong!
Advance straight towards the future!
With the radiance of stardust,
we can illuminate the darkness and go forth
Don't be afraid to advance forwards
Release an arrow of light and cut through the wind!
The valley between strength and weakness
isn't the place to be hesitating
There's something precious I must protect
My heart knows that well
We'll push on without hesitating!
We can go!
Having the capacity to love others
and knowing you're loved brings happiness
Make sure not to lose your way from the small tricks of fate
However clumsy or awkward you are,
none of that matters anymore
Whenever we feel like we're about to collapse,
if we help each other out, everything's OK!
Someday, we'll finally reach
the place we've dreamed of
We can always stand back up, and that's because
we're not alone; Our bonds are strong!
Advance straight towards the future!
However tough life gets,
I'm sure that we have the strength to face it
Though when alone, we sometimes feel crushed under the weight,
if we help each other out, everything's OK!
Someday, we'll finally reach
the place we've dreamed of
We can always laugh and smile together, and that's because
we're not alone; Our bonds are strong!
Advance straight towards the future!