Day by day, as we struggle,
we continue to fight against something unseen
On a completely fresh canvas,
we simply continue to draw...
Monochrome Sketch
When you feel like you're brimming with strength, paint in a passionate red
Let's keep moving forwards without fear of conflict or wounds
When you're surrounded by happiness, paint in a hopeful yellow
Smiles never failing, let's share our joy with others
Dreams are a sketch -
Onto the monochrome world that we wrote out
We put down the colors that we find ourselves
As we meet all sorts of different colors atop life's palette,
we fill up our blank-white palettes all the way
We'll continue to draw out our dreams, full of all our different hopes and wishes
Under the huge skies of this planet
When you add tears to your passion, you make the color purple
Endure past the anxiety and loneliness on days where nothing goes well
When you add tears to your hope, you make the color green
If you're tired, don't be afraid to take a break before setting off again
Dreams are a sketch -
Onto the monochrome world that we wrote out
We put down the new colors that we made by mixing others together
Whatever color we're missing, there's still no way we can paint the continuation of this dream
All sorts of things will happen, but let's face them without being deterred
Beautiful colors, colors you dislike, colors you'd once liked
They all color this planet and its huge skies
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What's this urge scratching away at the inside of my heart?
Everything before my eyes was dyed pink in a single instant
It's love?!!!! (Love!) It's love??! (Love!)
It's a koi!! (Oi!)
Your face is distinct?! (Face!)
Come more!!!! (Awright!)
Bring it here!!!! (Hold up, hold up!)
More distinct!!!! (Whee!)
Come, spring!!!! (Hold up, hold up!)
We put down all sorts of colors onto our monochrome world
As we meet all sorts of different colors atop life's palette,
we fill up our blank-white palettes all the way
We'll continue to draw out our dreams, full of all our different hopes and wishes
Under the huge skies of this planet
Whatever color we're missing, there's still no way we can paint the continuation of this dream
All sorts of things will happen, but let's face them without being deterred
Beautiful colors, colors you dislike, colors you'd once liked
They all color this planet and its huge skies