Even at the furthest ends of the universe, you're in my thoughts
As I scatter my wishes across the countless shooting stars
Far (yet so close)
I want to see you (but I can't see you)
Seeming to reach you (Not reaching you)
Always teary-eyed
Everyone (someday)
joins the stars (and disappears)
Is it fate? Destiny? Whose doing?
Because I'll devote all of myself to you
Vehemently! Explosively! Fiercely! Bursting! Detonation!
Intensely!
Even when I become dust among the stardust, (Joining the shooting stars)
my love for you will never cease (I can believe)
These feelings are blazing (burning so hot)
Like Antares, shining crimson red
(Yes, always, at any time)
However many hundreds of millions of light years separate us, (I have no fear)
I don't care! I love you! (I can fly!)
My wishes will (for all of eternity) never disappear (ever)
The children of the stars will continue to protect you
Intensely!
Take formation, crew! “Yeah!”
'cause I wanna love you, I love you!
Aye aye, sir!
Keep love close to my heart, always!
All, all is in the name of love!!
Aye aye, sir!
Loving and being loved, that's how we're here now!
(Aye aye, sir!)
Not stopping (Can't be stopped)
Advancing (Moving forth)
Accelerating (Speedily)
Sometimes finding excitement
Shinily (dazzlingly)
shining (more and more)
Full power one moment to the next!
Though one of these days, I may be broken and scattered into pieces
Vehemently! Explosively! Fiercely! Bursting! Cutlet!
Intensely!
Wherever you are in this universe, (No matter what paths you traveled)
I will search until I find you (I can believe)
Illuminate (Let light fill) the darkness
With the brilliance of Centaurus, shining bright yellow
(Yes, shining and shining)
At the furthest reaches of the universe, (I was able to meet you again)
A miracle such as this was sure to happen (I can fly!)
However (far) far away you are (Believe)
You'll always be in my thoughts
Intensely!!
Blazing suns!
Distant moons!
Countless Andromeda galaxies!
Colossal gas giants!
Pitch-dark black holes!
Love! Love! Love! Love! Love!
Intensely!
Do you hate me?
Does my voice not reach you?
But still, even so,
I'll devote all of this love to you! Wao!
Vehemently! Explosively! Fiercely! Bursting! Detonation!
Intensely!
Even when I become dust among the stardust, (Joining the shooting stars)
my love for you will never cease (I can believe)
These feelings are blazing (burning so hot)
Like Antares, shining crimson red
(Yes, always, at any time)
However many hundreds of millions of light years separate us, (I have no fear)
I don't care! I love you! (I can fly!)
My wishes will (for all of eternity) never disappear (ever)
The children of the stars will continue to protect you
Intensely!