Oka
zaki
Tai
iku
Staring straight into the camera as I walk and sing
The other members come in from the side
Suddenly cover up the camera with my hand
Moving to the next place with each cut
Going at fast-forward speed
Going in slow motion
Into stop motion
Black and white shot
Luminous shot
And a shot purposefully made to look old
Multiplying pointlessly
■
How to Act the Part of
Any Female in a Music Video:
For Dummies
Instructor: Okazaki Taiiku
1. Cry
2. Dance
3. Listen to music
4. Lean against window
5. Collapse
■
One more time...
1. Cry
2. Dance
3. Listen to music
4. Lean against window
5. Collapse
■
Good job!
Make the male and female walk alongside in a half-screen cut
Have them finally meet at the end
Make all their friends and people helped along the way sing in separate shots
Stack countless analog TVs and let them play static
Have someone who looks like a ramen shop apprentice act down at the front of the shop
Creation, creation, creation! Music and
Creation, creation, creation! Video work together
Mixing each time, working alongside each other, and right on the timing of the beat,
bam! You can practically hear the "And, cut!"
The unwavering desire to produce is every creator's wish
A steadfast gaze is the receiver's feelings
Let this music video reach a hundred million people!
Film a trendy city at night
Blur the lights as appropriate
Symbolically hold a fruit
And then smash a cake onto the screen
Paste a bunch of your favorite lyrics in the window to up sensitivity
Get slapped in the face
Stand at an intersection
Candid shot - a wonderful smile!
Break stuff!
To Taiiku ♡
Happy birthday!
Burn stuff!
To Taiiku ♡
Happy birthday!
A fleeting expression from behind the fence
Anyway, anyway...
Walk along the beach with no goal
The character which was supposed to have some sort of theme
What kind of message is this trying to...
How am I supposed to feel looking at this?
This is such a waste!
What is this? There's no message here!
I'm playing my guitar outside, but the electricity isn't plugged in
I'll pick up something and turn around
Creation, creation, creation! Music and
Creation, creation, creation! Video work together
Mixing each time, working alongside each other, and right on the timing of the beat,
bam! You can practically hear the "And, cut!"
The unwavering desire to produce is every creator's wish
A steadfast gaze is the receiver's feelings
Let this music video reach a hundred million people!
And, cut.
Good work.
You're using this part too, aren't you?
The camera's still rolling, you know? At the end of a music video,
there's the "And, cut!", and the "Good work!" part that you're going to use.
That's the kind of movie it is, that kind of music video, really...