They sure are sleeping tight.
Perhaps we overdid it a little?
Perhaps indeed.
Our next mission objective... What was it, again?
It's love, Professor.
Love?
Love comes after Kouhaku.
Now there's a real challenge.
There is no force stronger than love, Professor.
Isn't it about time we woke them up?
Roger.
Nervous system at full speed.
Inputting movement commands.
Appetite on full blast.
200 Dum-Dum Hectopascals.
You can hear them upon closing your eyes - the voiceless whispers...
"Release yourself from your fears and awaken." - a spark from within...
Logos urging on evolution,
and another you, yet unknown to yourself,
decree that the day to cross dimensions has come
All have journeyed through rebirth across the stars, to come to this blue earth,
sights aimed at this "present"...
That is why we will fly
Now, open, door slumbering within the depths of the heart
Now, Momoiro Clover Z... Awaken from your 500 million-year sleep!
They have not been asleep for 500 million years.
The spiral of time, nimble
Go forth as you pray
Genomes bearing light
With a flash, we are reborn
The dawn of a beginning
In no books of prophecy
Learning as we hurt one another
The future is rewritten
Struggling within the darkness of a slump
Destroy the pre-established harmony
The creation of "1" and its very consciousness
Raise the density; take off
Soar upwards! Soar upwards!
Release yourself from all that keeps you captive
The moment that you kick away your hesitation will come
Keep on refining yourself
Cut away old paradigms
It's not too late if we act now, so make the shift!
At this moment, the time axis runs in infinity
The code is "love" - a yet-unknown trajectory
Scaling up dimensions
Open the gate
Open your soul
All that has repeated endlessly
Such as war and suffering, everything
is a sin created by the hands of man
Calamities are the teachings of the planet
However, we have already cleansed our minds
We will live on linked hand in hand
Pandora's box, now opened,
will never shut again - as such,
man has no choice but to realize
that we are but all one and the same
Yes, you see; the light is always stronger than darkness
There is no force stronger than that of love
Further... Onwards... Onwards...
The spiral of time, nimble
Go forth as you pray
Genomes bearing light
With a flash, we are reborn
Soar upwards! Soar upwards!
Release yourself from all that keeps you captive
The moment that you kick away your hesitation will come
Keep on refining yourself
Cut away old paradigms
It's not too late if we act now, so make the shift!
At this moment, the time axis runs in infinity
The code is "love" - a yet-unknown trajectory
Scaling up dimensions
Once passionate wishes
surge outwards, it won't be a miracle
The rock door now opens
Let us go, in unison, through our great Star Gate
Open the gate
Open your soul