Enemy planes detected at 3 o’ clock! Destroy!
With innocent girls’ praying
Ring-ring-ri-ring ring-ring-ri-ring ring-ring-ri
“There’s the bell! It’s an enemy invasion!”
“Seriously...?”
Woof woof-woof-woof-woof woof-woof-woof-woof
woof-woof-woof
“Hey, you there! It’s dangerous here!”
“Out of the way!”
Bam bam-bam-bam-bam
bam-bam-bam-bam
bam-bam-bam
“Doesn’t matter where from, come at us!”
“Come!”
We’ll send you happiness of the highest grade
The prayers of innocent, daydream-prone girls at the prime of their youth
The evacuation of all students takes utmost priority
It’s the beginning of a full-scale war
All the grandpas and grandmas at Health Land
Sorry to keep you waiting, brawl!
Unidentified lifeforms of unknown origins
Who would’ve known? It’s the Weekend Heroines!
Please, class prez, pretend I didn’t skip afterschool cleaning
It’s gotten out of control – my broom’s flying through the sky
Please, TA, pretend I didn’t skip out on club
It’s gotten out of control – my uniform’s red with blood
Work miracles!
With the prayers of innocent girls of justice
Beat our enemies down, right now
We’re sure to win with a preemptive attack, but even so...
My daydreaming heart faintly flushes
But no, there’s no dream which will go ungranted
Of course that’s right; we’ll definitely, no matter what,
make them come true
Somewhere, I want to watch that girl forever
Ask her to meet me afterschool, feel like dying
It’s my slightly-romantic school life
And I won’t allow anyone to destroy it;
I want to live out my youth more!
Action! Atchoo! No one knows our muse
Zoom-zoom-zoom-zoom,
zoom-zoom-zoom-zoom,
zoom-zoom-zoom
“Huge guy approaching!”
“Oh no!”
We’ll send you happiness of the highest grade
It’s pretty impossible! But we won’t lose!
Not with the prayers of innocent girls
Plot twist, who would’ve seen this coming?!
Start the countdown to closing time
Ten laps around the campus? What kind of teacher is this?!
Call it a blind spot; overlook it, please?
An unidentified lifeform of unknown origins
It’s one of those “Weekend Heroines”!
Hey, Ellington, it don’t mean a thing if it ain’t got that swing
It’s gotten out of control – even the piano’s dancing through the sky
Hey, Dillinger, watch out for the red dress
It’s gotten out of control – my uniform’s in tatters
Stand back up!
Young girls are innocent girls of justice with their prayers
Go forth!
I don’t get what do you mean
by “burn the sight of corpses into your eyes”...
I’ve realized that weakness comes from the heart
But I won’t surrender, ever
My stubbornness, I got from my dad
Of course that’s right; We’ll definitely, no matter what,
make them come true
I want to play around with everyone forever
and take lots of pics together, too
Our overnight field trip is sure to be exciting
And I won’t show mercy to anyone out to destroy it;
I want to live out my youth!
Action! Fiction? Angels covered in wounds
Repeating a cycle of encounters and farewells throughout our youth
Bookmarking the days of our fresh spring
Step light on the way to our promised land
Proceed forth, proceed forth; shine bright
Rest your wings, look up at the heavens
We will answer the prayers of friends
Even when lost in worries, even when you’ve lost your way,
keep love in your heart and lead the way; shine bright
Help the fallen, comrades
With the prayers of innocent girls of justice
Wipe your tears and join hands
If this is the finale, then let’s go together...
Work miracles!
With the prayers of innocent girls of justice
Beat our enemies down, right now
The closing secret is certain death, see...
Awaken, slumbering lion’s heart
There’s no dream which will go ungranted
Of course that’s right; we’ll definitely, no matter what,
make them come true
The truth is, I want to be fawned on by someone
To be treated gently, ever so softly
A slightly dizzying paradise, a heaven
But you see, I want to protect everyone
I want to grow even stronger and stronger
Action! Atchoo! The legend here is just beginning
Ring-ring-ri-ring ring-ring-ri-ring ring-ring-ri
“There’s the bell! It’s another enemy invasion!”
“Alright!”
Woof woof-woof-woof woof woof-woof-woof woof
woof-woof-woof
“Hey, you there! It’s dangerous here!”
“Out of the way!”
Bam bam-bam-bam-bam
bam-bam-bam-bam
bam-bam-bam
“Doesn’t matter where from, come at us!”
“Come!”
We’ll send you happiness of the highest grade
The prayers of innocent, daydream-prone girls at the prime of their youth