Momoclo
Village
Big trouble!
Momoclo
Village
Guys, it's awful!
Momoclo
Village
Chapa chapa.
What manner of trouble?
This is big trouble, chief.
The enemy...! The enemy, the enemy...!
Calm yourselves!
What of the enemy?
Chapa.
Chapa chapa.
The enemy is attacking, chief!
Oh no!
By the gods! We cannot allow this.
Shaman! We need a divination immediately!
Chapa chapa...
Then, allow me to begin the ritual.
An ill omen!
An ermine?
No, an omen!
The village- The village will be burned to the ground!
We must enter battle immediately!
Oh no!
We must stop them.
Unless we protect this village...
Unless we...
Chapa chapa.
Very well.
We will fight side by side in battle.
Now, move forth!
Chapa chapa!
Pinky Jones
Adventure! It's a tour, it's youth
Aim for the very highest dream
Survival is what I'm always seeking
Don't just go with the flow
Yi, èr, san, sì, wu, liù!
v
-
Chase after it seriously, earnestly
Just being cute isn't enough
Have a hidden side to yourself
Do a handstand, be flexible, and everything's A-okay
Infinite sneezing, achoo!
Kyalalalala, number 1
Off on a journey here and there, clap your feet
I'll refill you with lots of energy!
Open wide~
Dreams bear fruit when you help them bloom
So make sure they blossom powerfully and beautifully
Rely on your connections
C'mon, now's the time!
Turn adversity into opportunities!
Through the rain and through the storm
Now, come here, come on!
I'm ready to give it my all
Whatever the circumstances, I'll overcome them
I want to see you
I want to! See you!
Yeah, that's right!!
Chapa! Chapa!
Saffron, thyme, oregano
Spice up your life
Bring out their each of their scents
A girl's heart feeling aflutter
Here in the adult world,
I've got my sights on an amazing dream
Shout out! C'mon, dance, it's a carnival!
It's a party!
From past to present, east to west, why not sing?
Step right and left, wherever you want
Stamp the ground, growing A-okay!
Let's jump into a different dimension, positively
With a kick and a punch, knock on the door to your dreams!
Giving up 'cause you can't help it? That's a big no~
Dreams are meant to come true with a smile
Keep your tears hidden in your chest
and rely on all your friends
C'mon, let's make our hopes bloom
You're only young once!
Shine bright!
Search! Search for the brightest future, oh!
There's just three things important to me –
you, dreams, and friendship
Keep them all in your heart!
Yeah, that's right!
Let light illuminate the whole world
Even when the days are rainy
I wonder, will my feelings reach you someday?
I have the page of my dreams bookmarked
Even clouds can shine
Stick by your tough, hard-working friends
and share your luck
Let's go!
Turn adversity into opportunities!
Through the rain and through the storm
Now, come here, come on!
I'm ready to give it my all
Whatever the circumstances, I'll overcome them
I want to see you
I want to! See you! Yeah, that's right!!
You're only young once! Shine bright!
Search! Search for the brightest future, oh!
Here we go, off to make the world ours!
Spirit,
willpower,
full bloom,
determination,
passion,
drive –
Make sure to remember them!
Chapa chapa!