Date: ○/×
Class Duty: Rin & Miku
Plus Boy
Music
Giga
Lyrics
Reol
Artwork
Miwashiiba
Video
Okiku
Athletics
Ars Magna
T-
t-
.......................
The class next door has someone I've been a little interested in lately
T-
t-
The class next door has someone I've been a little interested in lately
this girl
Pretty heartshine smile
"kyuute↑"
No, no, no, no!
It's  not  like I like you or anything!
I'd only just, just a bit, a bit, a bit,
My eyes just
started following you
on their own, I swear!
So I say, but c'mon, see,
I'm pretty head over heels for you
And I can't memorize what
I'm studying at all, crap!
I want you to factor
for me!
In my delusions,
expanding formulas
Solve! Solve!
It's come to this,
cross
dimensions,
go!
Let it go!
Inside
you,
directly,
leaving nothing behind,
I'm summiiiiiiiiiiiiiing!
Haa...
.....................................................
"Stop! Stop! I said stop! Stop it...!"
Haa...
So cute...
"Stop! Stop! I said stop! Stop it...!"
You're so cute...
Haa
I told
you to
goddamn
stop.
"Yes, ma'am..."
I shoot it out with peace
Re:Say→Wholehearted Self-Restraint
Riding a wave of technique,
my desire to do it goes up and up
I'm kinda kinda kinda kinda
getting excited
Your, your, your
fucking!
Show me, show me more
Show me, show me properly
Show me, try to seduce me
ABCDEF good guy
But hold on,
hold on a bit,
In the end, I can't hold on!
Puberty is the time of wanting that
'cause I'm a boy...
T-
t-
.......................
There's this 3rd-year, a beautiful, adultlike, knowledgeable, kind
senpai
If you let me get this close to your face...
My heart won't stop pounding (aahn) //
Sneaking a peek at your shirt collar's gap
And your 5cm-folded skirt is the best!
You noticed, but in the end...
"Where do you think you're looking?!"
You spank me
reward me
Tonight's  side dish  is  mackerel?
Non, non
Pork fried with ginger?
Q. Sketch a parabola on senpai.
A. Convex up there, convex down there
I did πr2 (pi r squared) and let it out
Formulas, youth, and desires
I can't stop my
instinct,
my
XXX
.....................................................
"Who do you pick?
"U...uu...um...um...then...both///"
"Please make your decision."
.....................................................
"What???!!!"
"I'm very sorryyyyyy!!"
I shoot it out with peace
Re:Say→Wholehearted Self-Restraint
Riding a wave of technique, Breaking
First one to be out
No, no, no, don't
I'm dizzy
My, my, my
fucking!
Further, further, even further
Further, further, properly
Further, raise your voice
ABCDEF good guy
But listen,
listen a bit,
In the end, this BPM's dangerous!
This is the age where we want that
A boy's...
Just a bit,
hey
Just a bit
Just a bit,
hey
show me
Just a bit,
c'mon
show me
Just a bit,
c'mon
"Wait, is that Boy～?!"
Just a bit,
c'mon
"Wait, is that Boy～?!"
Just a bit,
c'mon
"Wait, is that Boy～?!"
Just a bit,
hey
"Wait, is that Boy～?!"
Just a bit,
hey
show me
Just a bit,
Just a bit...
show me
Also,
Just a bit...
you have a LINE? lol
Also,
Stand
Bow
Be seated
Stand
Bow
Be seated
Stand
Bow
Be seated
Stand
Bow
Let's put our hands
together in thanks
Everyone, happily dig in.
Goodbye
triangle
See you again
square
Sensei, everyone
the great pinkost
I shoot it out with peace
Re:Say→Wholehearted Self-Restraint
Riding a wave of technique,
my desire to do it goes up and up
I'm kinda kinda kinda kinda
getting excited
Your, your, your
fucking!
Show me, show me more
Show me, show me properly
Show me, try to seduce me
ABCDEF good guy
But hold on,
hold on a bit,
In the end, I can't hold on!
Puberty is the time of wanting that
'cause I'm a boy!
Mozuku
seaweed!
Music
Giga
Lyrics
Reol
Artwork
Miwashiiba
Video
Okiku
Athletics
Ars Magna