Let's rewrite the records (Yeah, yeah!)
We hate losing much more than we look it (Yeah, yeah!)
Please cheer us on as loud as you can!
(Fight, yeah! Fight, yeah!)
The stadium erupts into cheers
Only the strongest will grasp victory
Vexation will taste like eating the dust
Only passion will carve your name into history
Where are you from? Japan!
The Land of the Rising Sun
I don't want to lose! I don't want to lose!
I don't want to lose! I don't want to lose! I don't want to lose!
The golden country where even rice stalks shine
Five colors of fine silk (Fight, yeah!)
Are dishevelled in the action (Fight, yeah!)
But I won't give up! I won't give up!
I won't give up! I won't give up! I won't give up!
Bet it on this jet-black hair
Hey, when I take in a deep breath
Hey, I just give it a light touch with my finger
and hey, it's like I've got a button
that can make miracles happen
Be even faster, be even stronger!
Become even more beautiful!
If we push this button, we'll never be able to
go back ever again, but that's fine with us
Jump even higher, run even further!
Even more and more and more
Until it's so painful we can't take it anymore
Even so, that's fine with us
We'll push it
When the cheers suddenly die down
This is the moment of the century
My heart kicks up a gear immediately
and the world goes by in slow motion
Aesthetics in every step we take
Calm and composed through every situation
I don't want to lose! I don't want to lose!
I don't want to lose! I don't want to lose! I don't want to lose!
Put your soul into it, playing fair and square
The five ideals all strive towards: (Fight, yeah!)
Benevolence, righteousness, courtesy,
wisdom, brotherhood (Fight, yeah!)
I won't give up! I won't give up!
I won't give up! I won't give up! I won't give up!
Heroic men and graceful young women cheering us on
Hey, I can't exactly show this part
Hey, even so, with just a light touch
Hey, I'll then have a button
that can make the amazing happen
Focus straight on your goal, focus earnestly!
Be stubborn and press on!
Even though all will change
once we push this button
We'll take victory for ourselves! Grasp it with our hands!
Hold it so tight to our chests
Until it's so precious we can't take it anymore
Even so, that's fine with us
We'll push it
Chasing after our goal, being chased after
Vying for victory to the ends of the world
This is what a contest is –
Across the wide sky, the blue ocean, this earth,
the lives dashing through them burning radiantly
I'll make the flowers swaying in the wind into a necklace
and place it around your neck, no matter what
Right now, I'm running underneath the sun
as hard as one attempting to fulfill a promise
Be even faster, be even stronger!
Become even more beautiful!
If we push this button, we'll never be able to
go back ever again, but that's fine with us
Jump even higher, run even further!
Even more and more and more
Until it's so painful we can't take it anymore
But even so, that's fine with us
Push it!
Do it straightforwardly, earnestly,
and simply stubbornly
All will change once we push this button
The time for us to remain friends will soon be gone
Even though you're so precious to us that we can't take it anymore,
that's fine with us
We'll push it
Do your best, everyone!
We've rewritten the records (Yeah, yeah!)
People are more than just appearances (Yeah, yeah!)
Please cheer us just as you always have!