Heisei Project
Zips
Kairiki Bear
Soul Distortion Terrorism
The ambiguous meaning of 116
stops in agony
Is turning over a palm of the value of life malicious intent?
No matter how unpleasant it is, it's definitely
an accidental death, it's autoscopy
Jump to the memory level
A lonely soldier is fully armed
A scrap paper life, a great work
Brainwashing is expected even with a destroyed core
Invite with a NO
In this era, even if you scatter bait,
predation is also starving
I'm history's sign
Everyone,
Everyone, the cyberterrorism's begun,
run away!
Even if you want to
become a hero of justice,
you can't
Even if you want to
become a hero of justice,
you can't
Keep spitting out soul distortion forever
「Unite and open!」
I ask and gazed
Do unreasonable things with yes or no bodies,
break and be eaten
Kill underestimated hostages with a murder knife
Even if you're reluctant, you're definitely
worthless,
a Soul Distortion Terrorism
a dream foot soldier
Start running to the memory level
Crybaby angels are unprecedented
Trickery judgment, a major premise
Even if a tailwind blows,
{\c