Music: Zips
Illustration: Nanase
Heisei Project
Mix & Mastering: Kairiki Bear
Bass: Nachuki
Logo Design: No. 734
Revolution of Liz's Innermost Heart
Waking up
to a nuisance,
in my usual seat,
I set my head down on the desk,
yawning loudly when I wake up
Blue, the color you chose...!
You may be met with trouble that will unfold suddenly...
Take caution today.
Lucky Item:　　　　 　　White Hairclips
Today's supposed
to be misfortune
for me,
Blue, the color you chose...!
You may be met with trouble that will unfold suddenly...
Take caution today.
Lucky Item:　　　　 　　White Hairclips
Today's supposed
to be misfortune
for me,
"What bad luck..."
I remarked cynically
and rushed out
gallantly,
greeted by the usual Monday scenery
As those
days repeated,
a bud
had definitely
been grown,
"Seriously?"
"Seriously!"
This hurts
my head!
I kicked
the wall
A full heart
drops from
the sky
A full heart
drops from
the sky
Since the
day that
I'd realized,
Since the
day that
I'd realized,
I've kept on
glancing at you,
but
it's just
impo-
ssible!
Looking directly is too dazzling!
"There's
no need
to do this
anymore,"
I say
In the
cowardly,
sympathetic
evening,
I'm spurred on
As things are, it'll always
stay like this, a lie...
Naturally, I get tired
of these emotions I'd gotten attached to
But people being intimate with one another,
I started to feel jealous
A lover of the same sex,
it's not exactly easy,
but even though I know that,
everything
seems like a certain win!
A reverse heart,
I affirmed with these hands
"You'll do it now, right?"
but this isn't too bad...
A friendship
is made cloudy
in the clouds
I'm asking
for too much,
but even so
It's already sprouted,
so I've got no choice
but to be
dragged
with it
"I can't wait any longer!"
I say to myself,
and drown
in willpower,
but reality remains the same as ever
Even from now on, you'll always
be that pathetic?
A full heart is washed away by the rain
I'd tricked even myself
It's not normal,
I know, I get it!
"There's
no need
to do this
anymore,"
I say
to myself,
and confess all of my emotions
"I liked you,"
"and I still like you, even now!"
Don't say anything,
just like this
Revolution of Liz's Innermost Heart