"Dear me, age 25,
how do you think today looks?
oooo
"Hey,
y'know..."
Suzumu
Gibson
drums
Guu
Saine
Komine
sakura-colored time capsule
ooooo
As the
sakura
petals
rained
down,
Graduation Ceremony
ooooo
I'd coun-
ted down
the num-
ber of
days
ooooo
towards
gradu-
ation
on my
fingers
ooooo
This
road I've
walked
ooooo
for the
past 3
years
ooooo
Seems
like it's,
though
only just
a bit,
ooooo
grown
shorter
oooo
and I
fell in
love
oooo
I spent
each day
oooo
oooooo
without
wanting
to find a
meaning
for all
of this,
keeping regrets
hidden within my chest
I've shut my eyes hundreds of times,
pretending to not see my precious feelings
"There's no way,"
"It's not like you,"
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I told myself so many times
My reason for this irritating, impatient feeling
ooooo
I'm a
coward
who can
only rely
on others
Shoddily pretending and showing off,
I told more lies
ooooo
Someone
out there
suggested
one day
Let's bury a time capsule!!
Make sure to bring
something important!
ooooo
a rather
ordinary
ooooo
"Time
Capsule
Plan"
ooooo
What
will
he be
ooooo
leaving
behind, I
wonder?
ooooo
Then I
realized
that I'd
always
ooooo
kept
deep
in my
chest,
ooooo
and
still
deeper
ooooo
Passing
by each
other,
ooooo
just
that
made me
happy,
however
short it
felt
Unable to tell you
the regrets within my chest
I've denied them thousands of times,
the feelings I'm hiding
"It's just your imagination,"
"You're just tired,"
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I fell in love with love itself
The reasons I give for my helplessness pile up
ooooo
I can't
move
forwards
if I keep
relying on
others
The flowers decorating the end
are my feelings for you
I realized
that I'd realized
how I really...
If I don't tell you,
and I'll only come to regret it
then I'll say it aloud
ooooo
to
you...
To 名無し-kun
ooooo
The
day
of the
plan,
ooooo
I held
onto two
letters
ooooo
the last
time I'd
walk
down
that
path
ooooo
The
flashing
lights of
my me-
mory
twinkled
And then
I realized
ooooo
that this confession
isn't too overambitious for me
I've rewritten them tens of times,
my precious feelings
"I want to quit already,"
"But I'll keep writing,"
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I told myself so many times
I'll entrust these two sakura-colored pieces of stationery
oooooo
to myself
in the
future,
once I've
gotten
serious
Today, under the raining sakura petals,
I lied again
and smiled
"So after 10 years have passed,
I'll be able to tell you..."
Sakura-Colored Time Capsule