Samurai Soul
Lyrics:  Kamiuta.......
Composition:  Kamiuta & Matura
Vocals:  LIQU@............
Video: Inukoro
"When asked about the meaning of Japanese spirit,
I will answer that it is the mountain sakura
in the morning sun,"
Motoori Norinaga
The poem of a warrior
almost the same as flowers...
Samurai
Impaling through the heart
with a coldly
unwavering
katana
That which lies in the country of the sun,
its name is
the samurai soul
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
which shall subsequently become taken over
I want to fly out,
away to a place no other knows of -
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
That's what I
think to myself,
but that's all I can do,
and if, if I had
such courage,
would I have been able to walk forwards
without forcing myself to smile?
"I know if I act thus, it will end so,
yet am compelled by the Japanese spirit,"
Yoshida Shouin
The poem of a warrior
which seemed almost as if it were a dream...
almost as if it were a dream...
Samurai
Fervently sounding out life
cutting
through fate
with your katana
That flows and flows through the country of the sun,
its name is
the samurai soul
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
which shall subsequently become left behind
I want to disappear
You see,
everything I do is a failure
Compared to others,
I'm full of nothing but jealousy
All of my clumsy,
desperate efforts
are carried away by a chilly wind
and gradually forgotten...
Life is fifty years.
To spend that amount of time beneath heaven...
Surely this world is nothing but a vain dream.
Life is fifty years.
To spend that amount of time beneath heaven...
Surely this world is nothing but a vain dream.
Life is fifty years.
To spend that amount of time beneath heaven...
Surely this world is nothing but a vain dream.
Life is fifty years.
To spend that amount of time beneath heaven...
Surely this world is nothing but a vain dream.
Living but only a single life,
is there anything that will not decay?
I will,
myself,
cut through
my own neck
I hate it all,
I hate it all
Nothing to be done about it,
my...
Slice through this rotten damn short-lived world
"That's just how it is."
Cut through its shell of lies
Your sword kept sheathed all this time,
now is the time to use it!
Right now -
Now,
cut through
A samurai
Truly indeed,
you are
a samurai
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
"This isn't how it is."
Shout out that truth
Dyed deeply within you is
the samurai soul
Shake the Japanese spirit
Now, you, live for the present!
Soul
Lyrics:  Kamiuta.......
Composition:  Kamiuta & Matura
Vocals:  LIQU@............
Lyrics:  Kamiuta.......
Composition:  Kamiuta & Matura
Vocals:  LIQU@............
Lyrics:  Kamiuta.......
Composition:  Kamiuta & Matura
Vocals:  LIQU@............
Video:  inukoro