One, two!
Merry Christmas!
Everybody, Merry Merry Christmas!
So excited, Merry Christmas!
The whole town's shining, bright lights everywhere☆
Blue and white LEDs!!
In the blink of an eye- just a blink, spring, summer, and fall go by
And suddenly it's the 24th, Merry Christmas!
Is Santa here? Why wouldn't he be?
'course he is, he's right here, Ol' Saint Nick!
But don't start wondering where that red suit came from!
However old I get, I'll still believe in Old Saint Nick!
This year will be my 15th Christmas!
The jingle bells go rin-rin-ring☆
Cake, yeah? Chicken, yeah!
Let's dig in! Merry Christmas!
I'll be eagerly awaiting many jingly presents
〒150-00
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Shibuya, Ebisu
Stardust Promotion Co., Ltd
Takagi Reni Present Inbox
Ichi, ni, Santa!!
Santa-san-san-san! (Santa!) San-san!
Santa-san san-san san-san-san
Santa, Santa Claus! (San-san, San-san)
Santa-san-san, Santa Claus
Santa-san-san, Santa Claus!
Santa-san san-san san san-san san
Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!
(Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!)
Santa-san-san-san! (Santa!) San-san!
Santa-san san-san san-san-san
Santa, Santa Claus! (San-san, San-san)
Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!
Oh, Santa Claus!
Santa-san san-san san san-san san
Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!
(Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!)
Jingle bells! Jingle bells!
Christmas!!
Reni-chan, go!
Show us a little of one of your good points! Yeah!
Santa, Santa, Santa; Santa, Santa, Santa
Santa, Santa, Santa...Santa!!
Reni-chan, go!
Show us one of your even better points! Yeah!
Santa, Santa, Santa; Santa, Santa, Santa
Santa, Santa, Santa...Santa!!
Christmas and New Year's Day
Nice combo!!
One, two, Shanta!
Shanta-shan, jingle (Shanta!) Jingle
Shanta-shan, jingle (Shanta!)  Jingle
Shanta-shan, jingle, jin-jingle
Shanta, Shanta Claus! (Jingle, jingle)
Shanta-shan, jingle, Shanta Claus
Shanta-shan, jingle, Shanta Claus!
Shanta-shan jingle, jingle, jingle
Shanta! Shanta! Shanta! Shanta!
(Shanta! Shanta! Shanta! Shanta!)
Shanta-shan, jingle (Shanta!) Jingle
Shanta-shan, jingle (Shanta!)  Jingle
Shanta-shan, jingle, jin-jingle
Shanta, Shanta Claus! (Jingle, jingle)
Shanta! Shanta! Shanta! Shanta! Shanta! Shanta!
Oh, Shanta Claus!
Shanta-shan, jingle, jingle, jingle
Shanta! Shanta! Shanta! Shanta!
(Shanta! Shanta! Shanta! Shanta!)
Japan has a snowy, midwinter Christmas
and Australia has Christmas in the middle of summer!
Which means...?!?!
Coco-cococo (Co-co-co?) Coco
Coco-coco-co coco-co coco-coco☆nuts (Cocococo-cocococo!)
Coco-coco coco☆nuts
Coco-coco coco☆nuts!
Coco-coco-co co-coco-co
Summer is here! Coco☆nuts! Summer is here! Coco☆nuts!
Samba, sun, sun, sun! (Samba!) Sun, sun!
Samba, sun, sun, sun! (Oooh, mambo!!!)
Santa-san san-san san-san-san
Santa, Santa Claus! (San-san san-san)
Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!
Oh, Santa Claus!
Santa-san san-san san san-san san
Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!
(Santa! Santa! Santa! Santa!)
Merry Christmas!