Farewell,  My
Dear Sorrows
Momoiro Clover Z
You going? Not going? Hey, c'mon, why not?
Say it! Wanna say it vs. can't say it
Tails? Or heads? The ever-bottomless question
Then tell me: Why is it that no matter what I do, it's the same...
Ah-ha! Dig it, dig it
Ah-ha! Dig it up
See no evil, hear no evil, speak no evil; such is evil
The wise man never draws near danger; death
Ask me to do something, and I'll want to not
In that case, if you can let it go, laugh your heart out
The voice of the heart echoes
in this carnival of tears and hopes
Into the dawn breaking impertinently...
Don't go... Don't go...
Don't cry... Don't cry...
Farewell – Cast away all the pain of yesterday
and muster forth the strength to cry out to be brave
so you may know a certain love that is called "the love of yourself"
Flock of restless sheep, hear my reason
Let loose the cries of your lost, wandering hearts
Do not ever look back!
Because this world of ours
Has only begun
I ain't tryna make ya feel lonely, y'know
You doin' it? Ditching? Hey, c'mon, why not?
Looking all distressed – oh great, now sobbing?
Look, I'm praising you, so give it all you've got
Oh, and then I had an endlessly-stretching dream
Angels had descended from the skies
Oh, and then in the endlessly-stretching sky,
I wish to be free
1, 2, and 3, 4, 5! Get up! Stand up! Free your soul!
1, 2, and 3, 4, 5! Stand up and make some noise!
Oh-ho! Do it, do it
Oh-ho! Do it now
The voice of the heart echoes
in this carnival of tears and hopes
By the dawn breaking impertinently...
Swayed back and forth... Swayed back and forth...
Moving forwards... Moving forwards...
Farewell – Cast away all the pain of yesterday
and muster forth the strength to cry out to be brave
so you may know a certain love that is called "the love of yourself"
Flock of restless sheep, hear my reason
Let loose the cries of your lost, wandering hearts
Do not ever look back!
Because this world of ours
Has only begun
Ah-ha! Dig it, dig it
Ah-ha! Dig it now
Oh-ho! Do it, do it
Oh-ho! Do it now, do it now, do it now!
Farewell,  My
Dear Sorrows
Momoiro Clover Z