The morning we were born, we were handed a
rather unfair travelling bag that we've carried with us to this place of learning
Quick to envy, looking down on others at times
Our cowardly selves clashing as our shining luggage kept increasing
All too many things have happened; we simply repeat the words we could never say right
Ah, just the words "I'm sorry" and "Thank you," over and over...
Our memories will be our source of courage
Holding tightly onto the dreams we had found individually
On a path so long we could never hope to reach the end
Even so, we will simply continue to walk on resolutely...
"Friends. We may be parting today..."
"Friends. But this pain within..."
"Friends. Proves the depth of our love."
"Friends. Don't forget."
"Friends. Our radiant..."
The last bell breaks through the air and resounds
Your shoulders trembled ever so faintly
We close our eyes just once more, and say with a deep breath,
Ah, "Farewell" and "Thank you" for now...
When they broke, we picked up the pieces and put them back together
Once we regain our grip our slightly chipped dreams
Even as we find ourselves in doubt or as we cry, we will never stop
aiming for the brightest future, starting here...
How many billion light years of solitude?
Although we may always be apart, if you look
from the bottom of these skies, we've still clung on
If anything happens, even if there is nothing,
we softly vow in our chests to take flight...
Our memories will be our source of courage
Holding tightly onto the dreams we had found individually
On a path so long we could never hope to reach the end
Even so, we will simply continue to walk on resolutely...
The wind still blows cold
But we will keep our heads up