>> 『A week ago, the world's collapse was announced. It was a much too abrupt, cruel・・・』
There, I stopped the writing brush as if I'd remembered.
『Hmm. Then, today I'll talk of a world a day before reaching its lifespan.』
The World’s Lifespan and the Last Day
At last,
tomorrow is
the "world's last"
birthday
At that
fact told
out of
the blue,
people panicked
and danced
sadly
Unable to do
anything, I
simply
prayed
Just like
always,
breathing
in and out,
crying,
laughing,
complaining,
chatting,
saying "I wanna die already",
talking,
telling,
disagreeing,
going places,
living places,
needing,
even if someone
left this world,
it'd always be
an unending game,
or so I'd thought
Wishing
and hoping,
praying
as well
was completely
natural
To me, sighing
because
it was trendy
seemed no more
than a performance
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
World peace
or world collapse,
■■■■■■■■■■■■■
they had no sense of them
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
So the big shots
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
thought once again,
■■■■■■■■■■■■■
isn't that just a prank?
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Because in this lie-covered country,
to us
masses,
the right
to "know"
is practically nonexistent
I had a bad dream
seeming
as if it
were
reality
Everyone
misplaced
their everyday
public masks
People changed,
acting as if they
were
animals
■
Unable to
do a
single
thing, I
simply
looked on
We'd always
hidden our
true nature,
instinct,
worldly
desires,
inferiority,
impulses,
behavior,
And only even moreso
liking,
bonding,
revealing,
emptying,
making gaps,
plowing,
and even if we
did all these things,
it'd always be
a forgiving game,
or so I'd thought
People who
wished,
those who
prayed as well,
did so for
unrealistic ideals
Trendy tragedies
to me,
seemed no more
than a performance
Believing world peace and
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
and the end
■■■■■■■■■■■■■
had nothing to do with them,
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
the big shots
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
thought once again,
■■■■■■■■■■■■■
isn't that all hypothetical?
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
But, the picture of hell was beyond expectations, well,
as expected
It'll simply
end today,
everything'll end
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Even if I pretend to be the heroine of a tragedy, it's still nothing but a performance.
The evening engulfing the city seemed a bit lonelier than usual.
The evening sky's
blurry stars are
unbelievably beautiful
The big shots have already
given up and
exposed their true natures
The plastered on
lies are
laid bare
and upon
us masses
fell the "rain", wetting our cheeks
World peace
or collapse,
either
is fine
On the
final night,
"lies" would
vanish
from this
beautiful
world---
But the desired next morning instead comes calmly
and the people dropped their shoulders, laughing
The world uneventfully
greeted the morning.
"Welcome Back"
"The salarymen
walking towards
the station seems
pained, like always."
>> 『People may die, the earth may die, but the world won't end.』
『So then, how about trying to live honestly at least today?』
『You. Me. And the world.』
『The truth, dirtier than any pile of trash, is
The World's Lifespan and the Last Day