Crescent Moon, Water Jug Waning Night
The runway draws a horizon
continuing endlessly
I was satisfied with this
perfectly clear, calm everyday
I realized that thinking they'd continue forever
was a too fragile ideal
and made memories without time
to even take a breath
but a voice spitting out a pure white wall towards this back
and noise mixing a bit
I follow the back of my head
One more step, I stop my hand
I realized the words we exchanged two days ago
were the last
Our everyday had dissolved, never to return
Rays of light
flow through the starry sky feigning calm
I feign my emotions
as this back of unflowing tears is pushed
If after just a bit more,
this heart
would've been able to deeply understand this feeling
yes, I want to pick up the moon's place
concealed by shadow, ah
Today as well,
the calendar says I had plans to go towards that hill
Misei Hill
I'd certainly seen it yesterday, too,
Astronomical
Observation
Eta Aquariids
the water jug's spilled wish
For what, for whom
I can't remember at all, but I believe
there's definitely meaning
I let the cloudy sky flow past
Reflected on the pure white wall,
the usual scenery
but the miniature garden is too beautiful
My eyes follow its dust which dances as it falls
I'll search for what was lost within that bright, shadowless room
My memories had already dissolved, never to return
The clouds covering the starry sky
hide the brightness that should be there
Alone, I extend my hand
and cut the emptiness
Lying ahead, the other side of the light that burns
I suddenly heard
the sound of footsteps riding on the strong wind
My astir heart realized at the sight
of those figures I was sure I'd never seen before
that the moon concealed by shadow
shines a thin light
Ah...
The sky begins to shine
Make a wish