This is a story of 1000 years into the future;
The princess, having returned to the moon,
sends to the night sky 380,000 km away
of the world that you left
her light
Thousand-Year Time Capsule
Vocals:
Mayu
Music/
Illust.:
Hitoshizuku
x
Arrange/
Video:
Yama△
Thousand-Year Time Capsule
Music/
Illust.:
Hitoshizuku
x
Arrange/
Video:
Yama△
When she awakened in the middle of a quiet bamboo forest,
wrinkled, old faces gently smiled down at her
Pretending to not know a thing,
she hid away her cold heart,
Kaguya
and so began their everyday life, someday to be gone...
Their voices which called her name so affectionately
pricked needles into her heart
Just leave me alone! Stop caring so much!
I don't want your hypocritical love!
After all... 10 years into the future
is just a moment, a blink of the eye away
So don't treat me so kindly!
Don't direct your voice, your eyes, not even your smile at me...
You're near the end of your years, and eventually,
you'll leave me behind alone, won't you?
We're eventually going to have to part,
so you don't have to try so hard
I got another present from some guy I don't know
Kaguya
Enough is enough already!
You can't really tell how serious they are...y'know?
I'd like to confirm it myself
Each and every one of them gives me trouble, until I finally snap
This is your fault, you know!
I'm tired of all of your meddling
And I'm not just saying this to be selfish
It's just that I can't believe anyone
Loving someone else, being loved by someone else –
It's so scary, why don't we just drop the idea?
After all... even 100 years into the future,
I just know I'll be as timid as always
Not even the most wonderful of presents I receive
I can honestly say "thank you" to
But actually, there's just one that I have
The present you gave to me, which I treasure
It was my name, "Princess Kaguya"
I was so happy then...
Do you remember?
Our transient time together was over,
Warning:
Do not dig up no matter what!!
-Kaguya
and the moon had come to pick me up
Clothed in a mantle of feathers,
to forget all that had happened
To
forget
you,
who
I was,
forget
everything,
everything, right here and now...
I really was such an idiot for saying all those things
I thought I preferred being all alone, and yet,
I don't want to forget you
Your voice, your gaze, your smile, our memories together...
So, please don't erase them...
In this world you left,
I forgot who 'you' were
Even so, please, let it remain here...
Warning:
Do not dig up no matter what!!
-Kaguya
The story of you and I
1000 years into the future, I just know
the princess back on the moon
The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter
(Princess Kaguya's Great Adventure)
To Grandpa
from Kaguya
will send to the night sky a whole 380,000 km away
her tears
Even 100 years into the future, no matter what...
Please, all the way, 1000 years into the future...