■A Certain Two's Conversation
'sup! So we meet again.
Did you not trail me
at your own accord...
I shall defeat you for sure today.
C'mon, don't make such a
ferocious face. I'll make
sure to go easy on you.
Then, I will not hold back...I'll
attack with the intent to kill.
Hmm, I see... Well, then,
Come!
■Scorching　　Music by Umetora
Lose all
hesitation
and doubts
and you
can gaze
all you want
An increasingly-
sharp glint
in my eye
cuts through
even the air
As long as
you do not let
fear draw close,
you can continue
talking on
A violently
restive pounding
in my chest
marks the
passage of time
Laugh at
the dark night,
as if tired
of waiting
The eyes of
the moon
are red
Our
resonance
of this
scorching
sensation
Our
resonance
of this
scorching
sensation
points to
a shining
future,
points to
a shining
future,
inviting
everything,
everything
inviting
everything,
everything
What these
honed
nerves
What these
honed
nerves
release and
capture is
your destiny
As long as
you're prepared
to never return,
go ahead and
just step forward
Each footstep,
one by one,
is poured into
courage
This tense
atmosphere
presents
an end
Whose
smile
is that?
The wind
carries a scent,
a burned
scent sticking
The red of
scattering
sparks...
Our
resonance
of this
scorching
sensation
Our
resonance
of this
scorching
sensation
points to
the center
of a world
burst open,
points to
the center
of a world
burst open,
inviting
everything,
everything
inviting
everything,
everything
A huge
blaze of
fury rages,
A huge
blaze of
fury rages,
and what
it directs
its burning
destruction
to is―
and what
it directs
its burning
destruction
to is―
obstructed eyes
The two
thinly-continuing
lines now
accept a sad
meeting carrying
much fury
Is their intersection
an inevitability?
Are they fated to cross paths?
To intently pierce
through innocence
If your wish were granted...
If your hope were granted...
would you like
to hold hands
and smile?
My feelings hidden inside
now point towards the
darkness...
Our
resonance
of this
scorching
sensation
Our
resonance
of this
scorching
sensation
points to
a shining
future,
points to
a shining
future,
inviting
everything,
everything
inviting
everything,
everything
What these
honed
nerves
What these
honed
nerves
release and
capture is
life and will
This
untouched
proof
This
untouched
proof
is like a
blazing
flame
is like a
blazing
flame
as it burns
everything
to the ground
as it burns
everything
to the ground
I will
return you to
nothingness
I will
return you to
nothingness
We now
face the
beginning,
We now
face the
beginning,
of our destinies
Scorching