My responses are incomprehensible; a dull grey morning
It was never my intention, yet I'm again selfishly causing you trouble
It's as if I've come home after learning dirty words at nursery school
Like my brain is being painted in many colored painting materials
The cold smell of a metal rod; a beautiful name in the distance
Echoing at sundown, breaking a promise
Scold me as I stand alone, my nose running
My responses are incomprehensible; a chestnut-colored evening
It was never my intention, yet I'm again selfishly causing you trouble
My elderly ring slips away; I put it on for it to slip away again
I want to feel your warmth from your words, even as white grows in my eyes
Would you be lonely if I grew senile first?
Food spills from my mouth, dirtying the table
Don't forgive me and my broad grin
My responses are incomprehensible; a snow white night
Why do you keep on smiling when I'm just causing you trouble?