Heart C⚙nnect
The cacophonous metropolis runs in mass terror,
silently taken possession of
Acting under the bidding of some sort of
lone miracle
Lacking common courtesy,
lacking aim,
it jumps from brain lobe to brain lobe
Lacking common courtesy,
lacking aim,
it jumps from brain lobe to brain lobe
Lacking common courtesy,
The manifestation
of deep-seated misbeliefs circling through the masses
acting as though it were you
Smeared so deep within people
Try and search me out all you want
The heart of retribution and the boy,
having long seen past the honesty-feigning masks,
simply dream
dreams they are made to dream
Replaying, reaching an end again,
watching the restarts of hundreds of people
What should I worry? It's not me, anyways
It's
again
the works of God
The rain continued to pour past the third night.
Continuing on after land, sea, and life,
it washed away moon, sun, and stars, as prophesied.
The masses, treating it as though it were symbolic of ____,
called for chaos within the dull, cloudy-skied metropolis.
What meaning do the fish and birds of tomorrow hold?
I no longer have the slightest idea.
I will simply continue to keep a record of these events.
One of those days,
unknowingly,
buried among fading memories,
I fell deeply in love
Changing smiles,
general behaviors, even–
Well, to say the least,
It knows no limits,
continuing the chain of slander
in an imitation of you
It knows no limits,
continuing the chain of slander
in an imitation of you
It knows no limits,
continuing the chain of slander
in an imitation of you
It knows no limits,
continuing the chain of slander
in an imitation of you
It knows no limits,
continuing the chain of slander
in an imitation of you
The sound of utopia
resounded throughout my ears, no doubt
The heart of retribution and the boy,
onto punishment for feigning justice,
could only wish
The heart of retribution and the boy,
onto punishment for feigning justice,
could only wish
The heart of retribution and the boy,
onto punishment for feigning justice,
could only wish
for the rain to fall
Replaying and wearing away
the restarts of thousands of people
What should I worry? It's not me, anyways
Replaying and wearing away
the restarts of thousands of people
What should I worry? It's not me, anyways
Replaying and wearing away
the restarts of thousands of people
What should I worry? It's not me, anyways
It's
again
the works of God
However long I wait, clinging on in solitude,
no one will grant me forgiveness
my sin
erase it all
the future
erase it
the past
erase it all
the present
erase it
my breath
cut it off
and then
erase it all
someone, forgive me
Heart of retribution and boy,
what lies beyond the dream you had one day...?
Ah-
ah
I know I must be...
Repeating, succeeding the role, crawling,
the 50,000th person smiling insincerely
After all,
Repeating, succeeding the role, crawling,
the 50,000th person smiling insincerely
After all,
after all...
The cut-out heart and the final station
and the last day of this beloved world
"I told you so," someone
someone laughed condescendingly
I've always waited for this
dream ephemeral
After so many replays, it's already worn out
Not that I can remember...
Tell me,
Just exactly who am I?
Heart C⚙nnect