Moment's Future Arrival
With one or two frustrations of our own,
we haven't got the time to be standing around
Enduring and struggling against a muddy river,
only continuing to stretch out our hands
Hey, wake up!
Follow your heart and go forth!
Now, take a good luck!
This game of life has just gotten started
In this loveless era, let those feelings you've kept hidden now explode!!
We may be unable to see the answer, but we're done with simply waiting
(Ready, steady, go!)
We're determined to sprint at full power every second!
(The anthem of our avaricious selves!)
We'll shatter this world and start running through once more
No more looking both ways before we cross
Just bet it all on our dreams (Moment's Arrival!)
The next jump is grasping the key
We'll let our passion burn however far we go
and challenge our future stage
The gears of forgotten ambitions
have begun to move once more
What will I find among this new wind, I wonder?
Hey, wake up!
It's your time! Stand back up!
Now, take a good look!
A fire has lit the resolve in my soul
In this loveless era, let your cold heart feel excitement
Let yourself be drawn in; life's boring if you don't live it passionately
(Ready, steady, go!)
That's what I decided with all the feeling in my heart!
(It's our offensive! Our anthem!)
We'll shatter this world and start running through once more
Swearing this on the rising sun, we'll make the jump today as well (Moment's Arrival!)
The next jump is grasping the key
We'll say goodbye to our spoiled selves
and leap into our future stage
Even if the goal I'd set for myself
were to meet its end as a dream, and no more
There's just no way
that I'm giving up now
It's my one and only shot at life
As if I'll spend it crying!
Our new story's just gotten started; a new day has dawned upon us
Open your eyes good and wide
It's the rise of my curtain!
(With all your body and soul! Start the story!)
We'll shatter this world and start running through once more
Until we grasp the hour we make the wind our ally (Moment's Arrival!)
The next jump is grasping the key
We'll let our passion burn however far we go,
and take the challenge as many times as it takes
It's only going to get more interesting from here on out!
We'll jump into our future stage