Lyrics・Composition
Illustrations
Mogelatte
Sugarvine
last night came upon me
a breakup convo that fell like a sudden rain
I see
oh well, then
here, have some water,
sugarvine
so just like that, I got on the bus,
went to a cafe I'd been wanting to try out,
and drank some African coffee
dunno where exactly it came from, though
you're not here,
that's all I can think, moping around
but on the other side of window,
the wonderful world's still spinning,
just like it does any other day
yes, shoop shoop
that's probably-bly
enough reason to whoop whoop
a little; yep, that's the kind of situation it is
make this gloomy mood, mood
clear up with a whoop whoop
that's how much you matter
today, I cleaned my house
from morning, even the windows
fruit sauce pancakes
I tried my hand at making,
but burnt them
there's no one for me to give them to,
so I braced myself and ate them all
the contrast between the
berries and the burnt parts
surprisingly wasn't too bad, but that's not enough
I wanna see you
I think as I keep on crying
but when I open the window,
there waits a bright world, just like any other day
yes, shoop shoop
that's probably-bly
enough reason to whoop whoop
a little; yep, that's the kind of situation it is
make this gloomy mood, mood
clear up with a whoop whoop
that's how much you matter
he's a sugarvine
can't live without water,
and doesn't care if the one pouring it is me or not
I'm a sugarvine, too
search for rain all you want
on my dry cheeks; endings are new beginnings
yes, shoop shoop
that's probably-bly
enough reason to whoop whoop
a little; yep, that's the kind of situation it is
make this gloomy mood, mood
clear up with a whoop whoop
that's how much you matter
that's probably-bly
enough reason to whoop whoop
a little; yep, that's the kind of situation it is
make this gloomy mood, mood
clear up with a whoop whoop
because I am me, and nobody else