In a certain city, there lived 8 girls.
Each of them wore
on their backs
a cape of a unique color.
Audition stage
is this way
And they knew
that no matter what,
no one else could see those capes.
Shiritsu Ebisu Chuugaku
Superhero
Career Path Proposal #2
Actress
I hit the stop button on my alarm and stretch deeply
The sun smiles down on us; breathe in happiness
We are superheroes, you and I both,
because we possess true strength welling up from the bottom of our hearts
It's a heart-pounding, windy morning
C'mon, we've gotta go, to the place of our fight
I rush up the stairs, test my quick wits
Today feels like one of those days I'll be able to run on at full determination
That dark heat haze of a coward
I'll turn it into a kind-hearted angel, just watch!
All right, we are superheroes
Anyone and everyone has their own twinkle power within
Even if we cry a bit, I strongly want to believe
Right here, right now, is just the start line
Audition stage
is this way
In a distant, faraway place where a voice calls out to me
You must be there, crying all alone
I want to see you, precious and irreplaceable to me, right now
I want to fly to your side
All right, we are superheroes
When you're looking downwards, eyebrows furrowed
Let me grasp your hand and stay by your side
Even when we're apart, I'm watching over you
Yes, that's right - you're a superhero, too
There will never be any sadness such as this again
Just give the acceleration pedal in your chest a gentle push
I've won and I've lost
"Without comparing yourself to anyone else..."
Your enemy is right here
"Dwelling deep within you..."
Stand up! Stand up!
Build up your energy
"It's too early to admit defeat."
We're heroes who still have nights we cry
Not everyone can be strong all the time
Anxiety and loneliness
Take those kinds of words and find the opposite, and then walk once more
All right, we are superheroes
Anyone and everyone has their own twinkle power within
Even if we cry a bit, I strongly want to believe
Right here, right now, is just the start line