Kaizoku Ou
Mogelatte
Akutoku Kinyuu Ichigou
Bamboo-Cutter's Overnight Sensation
Anyway, I have fallen in love
Uhyoo!
Princess
Kaguya
is srs
cute!
Uhyoo!
Princess
Kaguya
is srs
cute!
I want
to make
her my
wife!
Haa,
haa!
For a thousand years, my heart has retained its desire to sing and dance
Oh my, my, for the many people I have played with...
Shabby
Men are
nothing
to me...
How about I
think about
it once you
come back
with a little
something
for me?
Shabby
Men are
nothing
to me...
All of
you do
your
best,
trash.
The emperor still somehow would like to meet and serve me,
How about I
think about
it once you
come back
with a little
something
for me?
All of
you do
your
best,
trash.
but a display of your reasons is a necessity
But of course, that is only natural
Al-
right!
Once I
take full
advantage
of my po-
litical
power...
Al-
right!
I'll
have a
tight
grip on
kaguya's
heart!
Once I
take full
advantage
of my po-
litical
power...
I'll
have a
tight
grip on
kaguya's
heart!
Got-
cha!
As the moon pleases, we shall clap our hands
Got-
cha!
Just like that, break through the meridian of fate, it's not time to sleep yet
Here
we go,
you
all!
Servant 1
Servant 2
Servant 3
Here
we go,
you
all!
Just like this, sever Hourai's boundary line, no use arguing about it
Her back turned away from the moon,
the selfish bamboo princess - Ah, how I love her
Huff...
Kaguya's
house
sure is
far...
Are
you
all
here?
Kaguya's
house
sure is
far...
Ack,
they're
all
gone!
All
that's
left...
is the
japanese
sweets
I'm hol-
ding.
Aw,
how
can I
face
her
now...
Here,
I'm des-
perate!
please
accept
this off-
ering!
His only
present
for me
is this
red bean
mochi...
Is this
emperor
making
fun of
me?!
I can't
believe
this!
munch...
It's
so
good!
What's
goin'
on
here!
Aah...
Anyway, I have fallen in love
I can't
sleep at
night
thinking
about
that red
bean
mochi...
The
mo-
chi?!
Most beautiful in the country, a heavenly scent, both intelligent and virtuous, grandly generous...
Cer-
tain-
ly...~
Some-
one
like
this!
Well,
well...
Only now do I take the medicine of eternal life and smoke of Fuji
It's
consi-
derably
okay.
or sh-
ould
...I say...
Just ac-
cording
to keikaku.
Doing
these
things
and
those
things
with
kaguya...
When it's for your sake, and we both think of one another, what should I murmur?
gufu
fufu
Em-
pe-
ror-
sama!
I shall speak it honestly and directly...
How- How would you like one wife?
Just like that, break through the belt line between heaven and earth, it's not time to sleep yet
It
will
not
hap-
pen!
Messenger Messenger Mesenger
Prin-
cess
Ka-
guya!
Just like this, towards mayhem better than this boring freedom
You
must
return
to the
moon!
Messenger
You
are
an in-
habi-
tant of
the
moon!
My back turned away from the moon,
I can't
believe
it...!
please forgive me for being selfish, please, please, please?
Let us
go home
immedi-
ately!
What?!
No
way!
Armory: Please take care entering.
That place, throw it away; This place, want it...
That place, throw it away; This place...
"Tap-tap." "Hm?"
I want to be over there, but I want to be here, too
I want to be over there, too...
I know, searching for freedom when it's now too late is foolish
Is it not the same as a bird jumping from one cage to another?
I know, whatever I do, I have to choose between one or the other
That is, my present complete devotion of body and soul, is all...
true - that's why...
Break through the meridian of fate, it's not time to sleep yet
Just like this, sever Hourai's boundary line, no use arguing about it
Her back turned away from the moon,
majestically dignified, invincible in all the Orient,
the selfish bamboo princess - Oh, how I love her
Messenger. Messenger. Messenger.
Kaizoku Ou
Mogelatte
Akutoku Kinyuu Ichigou
Bamboo-Cutter's Overnight Sensation