Let's all join hands
Even moreso during tough times,
let's work together
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands!
Let's all join hands
Even moreso during tough times,
let's work together
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands!
Not at the fault of you or anyone else,
you fell down in the middle of the road
and just laid there, looking up at the blue sky
The shining tears rolling down your cheeks
aren't for show
You can't forget the joy of being alive
after you've come this far
When you get back up after falling to your knees,
your back is covered in mud
The pain of those scars will cheer you on
I want to join hands with you
Even moreso during tough times,
let's restart from the ground up
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands!
Let's all join hands
Even moreso during tough times,
let's work together
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands
Your beloved friends
aren't here anymore
despite having promised so sincerely
to pursue the same dreams together
No matter how small you are
or however powerless you seem,
let's believe that the promise we made that day
will someday be fulfilled
Whenever you shrink back and cast your eyes downwards,
on the verge of crying,
summon the courage to start walking again
To the future!
I want to join hands with you
Even moreso during tough times,
let's start over from scratch
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands!
Let this love reach the night sky, the stars
so everyone's wishes will be tied together
To the future!
I want to join hands with you
Even moreso during tough times,
let's take the first step right here
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands!
Let's all join hands
Even moreso during tough times,
let's work together
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands!
I want to join hands with you
Even moreso during happy times,
let's join hands together
C'mon! C'mon! Let's join hands!
Let's all join hands
and smile cheerfully!
Let's work together
Let's join hands! Even more!
Let's join hands! Always!