Theo
Hatsune Miku
I wonder
How long will I be able to keep up the act?
Will I be able to say good-bye when you want to go home?
The signs I'd missed that day fade bit by bit
But I'm sure things will be fine - we'll meet again, just as we have...
I close my eyes
Is it too late to leave a few small wishes?
Will I be able to say "welcome back" when the light has returned?
I must go
Call that the most beautiful thing in the world,
Just wait until we take back
all that's been stolen from us!
More
Round and round, make me dizzy
Back and forth, sway me like never before
Brighter and brighter, let it shine
Softly
I summon forth the wounded night
And cast a single little magic spell
And just like that, we can fly!
Don't avert your gaze! Keep it straight
Nothing will stop us at this point
Until the magic wears off - until then,
Hold on tight! To my hand
My hand!
Not a single one left behind
We'll reclaim every last piece, that's all
Until the magic wears off - until then,
Hold on tight! To my hand, my hand
My hand!
"It was impossible from the start for us to avoid committing crime.
And so we decided accordingly that if we at least were to continue
to hide the fact,       that in itself       would be      an honest act."
Just wait until we take back
all that's been stolen from us!
Softly
I summon forth the wounded night
And cast a single little magic spell
And just like that, we can fly!
More!
Round and round, make me dizzy
Back and forth, sway me like never before
Brighter and brighter, let it shine
Don't avert your gaze! Keep it straight
Nothing will stop us at this point
Until the magic wears off - until then,
Hold on tight! To my hand
My hand!
Not a single one left behind
We'll reclaim every last piece, that's all
Until the magic wears off - until then,
Hold on tight! To my hand, my hand
My hand!
Theo
Hatsune Miku