Set my mind on writing
a letter that can't be
expressed with words
I'd been considering
sending it to the person
I'd be in the days to come,
but I don't have an
address to send it to,
and don't know
where I am, either...
So then what am I
supposed to do with
these feelings?
How's it feel to have
become someone you
never wanted to be?
god's laughing up there
in heaven, pointing
his finger down at you
Shut up, you useless
piece of shit;
Hurry up and get
out of my sight
The misery
grows upon you
bitterly...
Squinting, turning away from love
and being shut in a 6-tatami
room, that's terrorism
This whole time,
I've been singing out -
no, I've been crying out
If you say that's wrong,
then take a bullet
heavier than those words
and shoot
when struck at,
strike back - It's your turn now!
It's time for you to seize every
single dream thrown away
I've bet my heart's
place on this
resistance
Laugh back as much as you were
laughed at, but no more
A coup d'etat of life, so to speak
Neither victories
nor any losses
through overtime
It's the eve of our
counteroffensive
I used to earnestly
believe that things
could change if I put
my thoughts to song
I'd thought simply
that without
embarrassment or guilt
Domination
and the like, who's
talking about that?
maybe there
aren't any huge
idiots who would
Trapped by fear of the voices
of the heartless crowd,
that's terrorism
Just like that,
I've rejected others -
no, I've run from them
If this is our final
chance, then for
this terrible stage...
I guess I'm sorry
when struck at,
strike back - It's your turn now!
Ignore all those who abuse and jeer at you
A cry for help
leaks out from
the wounds in
my heart,
mayday
Laugh back as much as you were
laughed at, but no more
This intifada occurred in a single room
A defensive battle with
neither soldiers nor officers
It's the eve of
our revolution
Even when
worn out,
take it
back
Your heart is yours
and yours alone
Life shines
so brightly
because that's
what makes it life
You may fall over,
trip, or collapse,
but that is proof you
tried to advance forwards
That's why anyone who
laughs at that is the worst
But despite everything, the world'll keep going 'round
Is that right? Is it?
give me an answer...
Terrorism
Song: Neru
Video, Illustrations: Ryuusee