The singing voice of the season sakura bloom
gives me the feeling this is
the beginning of something new
Fly far off,
far off,
into the
distance,
pure-white
flower petals...
Lyrics・Composition・Arrangement: Sunamori Taketeru (SunaP) feat. Hatsune Miku
Text»Over
And
then
I
met you
the moment coincidence and fate overlapped
My colors were spun into
your thread right next to mine
Tying together and entwining
Here I draw out
magic!
Let's go on a journey to
the other side of that rainbow, together
We should be
able to
fly far off
into the distance
As long as we're
not alone...
Standing
in the
sunset,
Standing in
the sunset,
my vision
dissolves into
crimson
my vision
dissolves into
crimson
my vision
dissolves into
crimson
The townscape
is softly
covered in
monochrome
Whenever I'm not sure which way to go,
I remember your line connected
to my pinky finger
I'm no longer
scared when
I follow it
This right here is magic!
The world is reborn
and a new season arrives
Our illusory connection
weaves me
and you
together once again
The tall, tall, tall sky is so blue
and the bitter summer oranges
sway in the wind
If I push myself a little,
I feel like I might be able to touch
the tiny sun
Let's go on a journey to
the other side of that rainbow, together
Fly far off,
far off
into the
distance,
pure-white flower petals...
We're not alone
Drums: HAZE, Bass: Sano Masaru (Acacia-o), Piano: Matsuoka Miyako, Guitar: Futatsugi Gentarou (Fromnou), Mixing: PUPI, Video: MastakaP