Woah, what is this?
I'm scared!
■■■■■■
Notice
This music video was filmed
without a single word of information
given to any of the members.
I mean, don't you think there's something fishy about our outfits?
The★Golden
●
★History★
Well, now that we're doing this, let's have you all go in at once.
The Complete
Flawless Prank MV
Let's go in together.
There's something fishy about our outfits!
One, two...
Just meet!!
The season has finally arrived!
It's showtime.
It is summer in our fine Japan, giving the ladies going to town a suntan!
Just who will be able to beat the summer heat?!
Yes! As you know, they are Momoiro Clover...
One more time! Momoiro Clover...
That's right!
Not even a single meeting explaining beforehand what is to come -
this is the complete, flawless prank music video, The Golden History!
I, Fukuzawa "Just Meet" Akira, will be your host for today.
Host
Fukuzawa Just Meet Akira
Allow me to ask what you all think of the current situation!
Takagi-san! How do you feel right now?
Huh?! Hold on, I don't get it, what are we supposed to do?
It seems that the summer heat has driven her a little crazy!
Let us begin without further ado! Question time!
■■■■■■
Question
Momoiro Clover Z's
"Electric Girl", also known as the "Steel Girl", Takagi Reni.
Takagi-san is known for having the best smile.
However, among the five photos displayed over there,
there lies only one real smile. Now, which picture is it?
Among these five photos, there is one real smile mixed in.
Repeating the question. Among the five photos displayed over there, there is one real smile mixed in.
Now, which picture is it?
Which is it?!
Now, ladies, please make your way over to the start line.
What does a "real smile" mean?
How will they interpret the meaning of a "real smile"?
Soon, the countdown will begin.
Wait, wait! I don't get what's happening at all!
The moment the countdown hits zero, please start running all at once.
Run through!
Among these five photos, there is one real smile mixed in.
The question is, which photograph is it?
The moment the countdown hits zero, please start running, and run through!
Now, shall we begin? Countdown, start!
Go!! Golden fire!
Let's sing!
C'mon, let's get started!
The time of harvest has come - it's finally arrived!
After shedding sweat and keeping our heads up, it's arrived!
Unyielding to any trials, naturally getting through
We dreamed just by making it into song
The more fruit it yields, the more hey-hey-hey!
Sharing ears of rice, hey-hey-ho!
When the season rolls around, the country of gold shines
How does south sound? Should we go all the way north?
Move to the stage of the first chorus.
Reach the central stage of the
first chorus, "Tohjin Pond's Trial"
We're on the front lines of friendship - our feelings form a wave
■■■■■■
Sing on the central
stage platform,
"Tohjin Pond's Trial"!
I love you!
In the utmost strongest, bestest, greatest,
most loving future, we'll head over to see you!
So we want you to greet us with the best smile you have!
Let's transcend time and connect our history
It's a wonderful (It's a golden) history!
■■■■■■
Costume change!
What's inside the box?!
Don't stop singing!
Let's enjoy ourselves!
■■■■■■
What's in the box?!
Will they be able to
keep on singing?
We're gonna return to the place of our hearts in triumph
We'll go to the sea and mountains, wearing honors
Smiling on the outside, and crying on the inside
For the sake of those tears of happiness
Let's sow the seeds of smiles!
Let's dance with the world!
We'll bloom the flowers of the hit parade brought to you from Japan!
We want to keep on singing
The songs that'll give everyone courage in any century!
In the utmost strongest, bestest, greatest,
most loving future, we'll head over to see you!
Croquette-san is here with us.
Let's all sing together!
So we want you to greet us with the best smile you have!
Let's transcend time and connect our history
It's a wonderful (It's a golden) history!
Good luck!
Thank you!
■■■■■■
The final stage!
Let's all sing with
the greatest smiles!
Utmost! Strongest! It's a golden history!
Bestest! Greatest! It's a golden history!
Onto the last chorus's stage!
With the greatest smiles!
Utmost! Strongest! Bestest! Greatest!
(We can go!)
The more generations pass, the more we grow even stronger
One more step, one more step
Let's move forwards!
It'll never end!
This is the greatest, most beautiful, tear-jerking light
If I change, the future will change too!
We'll leave new footprints across the path of history!
Our brand-new history keeps on going
Let's walk through our (It's a golden) history!
Smile, golden country!
Who films a PV like this?!