"Hi there.
Nice day, huh?"
"Nice day."
"So,
how're you feeling?"
"Average, I guess."
Lyrics: Gom, shito........
Song: Gom, Oji........
Arrangement: HoneyWorks
Illustration:
keepout, M.B,......
Gito, Tama,
Yamako, Rocor,....
Mogelatte......
Movie: ....
"Did you hear? There's gonna
......be a fireworks show next week!"
Plus, Haruki's
already back
in Japan,
so maybe
everyone
else'll be
there too!
Plus, Haruki's
already back
in Japan,
so maybe
everyone
else'll be
there too!
Plus, Haruki's
already back
in Japan,
so maybe
everyone
else'll be
there too!
Plus, Haruki's
already back
in Japan,
so maybe
everyone
else'll be
there too!
Plus, Haruki's
already back
in Japan,
so maybe
everyone
else'll be
there too!
Plus, Haruki's
already back
in Japan,
so maybe
everyone
else'll be
there too!
"Those kinda
......crowded events
...........aren't really my thing."
"Aw, jeez..."
"Well, it looks like I'll just have to try my
....luck with someone else, then (hmph!)"
"But on second thought,
....it sounds like it could be fun -
........I might wanna go after all." (sweating)
"I'm a little thirsty."
"Want a sip of this?"
"Is this what they call an..."
indi
rect
ki
s
?
"...so you noticed?"
"...yeah, I noticed."
But I'm still thirsty
I try to touch your waiting left hand ever so slightly
I want to hold it
I want to hold it,
but instead,
I hide mine away in my pocket
I've actually noticed it
..This distance that could be closed in an instant
I want to hold yours,
....I secretly want to hold yours
but I hide mine behind my back
"What're you mad about?
....Did I do something
........that bothered you?"
hint:
"Don't you think something about
....me today is different from usual?"
"Oh, I
know!"
"You gained weight, didn't you?
....There's no need to worry about it."
"Don't
make
me hit
you!"
"Notice how my hair's 15 cm shorter!"
"Boy, I'm
hungry."
"Have a bite of these."
"Could these be the legendary
homemade cookies?"
"Even though it's summer?"
"Even though it's summer.♡."
I'm still thirsty...
I've actually noticed it; this distance that could be closed in an instant
I want to hold yours; I want to hold yours, so I grab
your sleeve and tug at it
So beautiful...
Aren't they?
Absolutely stunning.
They are.
The fireworks I'd only watched from afar are now right in front of me
It's the kind of day where you wish you could stop time and never go home
"...I think I like you."
I try and touch your waiting left hand ever so slightly
I want to hold yours,
...I want to hold yours, so I'll shush you
and steal your lips away
I've actually noticed it
..This distance that could be closed in an instant
I want to hold yours, I want to hold yours, so I tightly-
tightly grip yours back