Even if you glorify the past by
calling it "youth"
your inferiority complex won't disappear,
vomit's coming out
They say, "Wait behind the white line,"
but the truth is,
I can't even
see one anymore
Using both hands,
I'd scooped out
a reality
completely dirtied
When I rub my eyes,
it's like I can't see anything anymore
No matter how much my cheeks are pinched,
I won't wake up
You're irritating,
shut that mouth
Flight Instinct
With a shallow
message just like
ready-made items
they said how important it is
to face yourself
To the masses, full of people like that hunchback guy,
I've got no
response
On the monitor which had
reflected one's self,
was the "me" there,
by a sudden service termination
announcement,
ended?
Execution
I was killed
It's unfortunate, but no visitors are allowed
Take what few
emotions you have
and throw them out
Don't remain incomplete
it makes me feel nauseous
It's the rebellion's starting signal
Now's the eve to awaken
Resist,
resist
conflict instinct
Swear,「I don't believe in things like god」
to god,
and shout out,
The future has such
grim prospects
Why?
It's hard
to breathe
I'm sick,
worr           ied,
and can't sleep
Hey,
『the future I'd thrown away that day』
『the future I'd thrown away that day』the train towards
Hey, when will the train towards
"the future I threw away that day" come?
This is my lonely war
but I can't just simply end it
Light,
I hate it,
and prefer strolls at night
I gathered all the clovers without four leaves
I don't want
"happiness".
All I ever wanted
was "normality"
just kidding
Rehabilitation,
the adults laughed easily
the parameters of daydreams
were completely deep red
If I would've been fine not knowing this pain,
then I wish I could've remained ignorant
It's a public execution, isn't it?
Fuck off and die
I spit on that
weak justice
I've forgotten how to fight against reality
since a long time ago
I'm tired
My flight instinct came forth
Read the atmosphere
with random guesswork
With a suitably loud voice,
shout out,
I've been
broken
into pieces
I'm already dead
With tacit understanding,
I lose interest,
and get
depressed
Won't you laugh at me?
Then, edit it well
please add up even the laughter
I don't need a train anymore
Let's watch
the last scene from the other side
I install a new "me"
Wearing clean textures,
I'm reborn
Throw out what few emotions you have
Don't remain incomplete,
it makes me feel nauseous
I don't need it anymore
It's the rebellion's starting signal
Now's the eve to awaken
Resist,
resist
Flight instinct
Swear,「I don't believe in things like god」
to god
and shout out,
The future has such
grim prospects, why?
It's hard to breathe,
I'm sick,
worried,
and can't sleep
Hey,
『the future I'd thrown away that day』
『the future I'd thrown away that day』the train towards
Hey, will a train towards
"the future I threw away that day" not come?
If I miss it, it's over
I'll never again be able to catch up
This is my lonely war
but I can't just simply end it