Heisei Project
This ill-fated heart
will feign peace
so to the insolent you,
bye-bye
Music: Zips
Illustration: Nanase
Bass: Nachuki
Mastering: Kairiki Bear
True Emotion Deficit
A seedling of desire
laughed innocently
and clumsily
connected fate
The end's return,
going back to nihility,
this confusion
along with this fake name
Guiltily harboring wishes,
proof of existence
I threaten the
real, wavering       .
meaning .
with pride
unable to
allow regret
this ill-fated
heart will
feign peace,
so to the insolent you,
bye-bye
Desire,    darkness,      I suddenly hate
My new life started with the beckoning of a hand
Isolation itself, dwelling deep within
The one-winged zero was shut
Tempting valuable jealousy,
it won't reach
I'll break that
.   wavering, blooming
meaning into pieces,
unable to take back
the other side
in the future
These completely off the mark
These completely off the mark emotions
will love peace,
so the twisted you
I'll high-five
No matter what kind of happy world it is,
it'll someday be invaded
This heart hidden
within will
destroy the peace
So with the lonely you,
within the darkness,
for that wavering meaning,
we'll search
and rewrite the
the unloveable future
This overflowing
heart will
will allow
peace,
So to the insolent you,
and the twisted you,
and the innocent you,
bye-bye