They say that there's a world unseen by anyone; Forever, hide yourself from
reality
Patched  and  Logical
They say that there's
a certain unspeakable secret
"While the addicts kiss..."
They say that
there are certain
words which cannot
be heard by anyone
"Hey, kill me instead..."
Now, join hands,
I'd heard your voice
Y'know, just
about everything
seems as if it'll disappear
36 different emotions inside,
changed from swallowing so many pills, they say
The final logic of "bye-bye"
I wished
for it
and wish-
ed for it
Mind calmed after being shaken
Saying that terrible scene was an illusion
The final logic of "the worst"
I drew it,
I drew it
They say that there's
a pain only I don't know of
"Sincerity always got in the way."
They say
that there's
a future
only I can't
proceed to
"Hey, since when, while kissing..."
I realized
Now, cover your eyes
I'd waited for the fleeting night
I thought I'd locked away
such a beautiful past
My wounded body is tired,
so I'll shut myself
away in a shell
It's now, it's still, it's stupid, stupid
I hadn't expected...
Now, join hands,
I'd heard your voice
Y'know, just about everything
seems as if it'll disappear
36 different emotions inside,
changed from swallowing so many pills, they say
The final logic of "bye-bye"
I wished for it
and wished for it
Mind calmed after being shaken
Saying that terrible scene was an illusion
The final logic of "the worst"
I drew
it
The final logic of "the worst"
Isn't it bitter? Hard? Circumstance betterment ―
don't do it, cry, and end up waiting,
and for the final truth, one's "beloved,"
I had blackmailed
Lyrics・Song  ShiroKuro
Arrangement  HASEWO
Illustrations・Video Umetarou
Patched and Logical