MOONSHINE
Moonshine -Tsukiakari-
The signal lasting no longer than a moment remade God’s will
That guy’s footsteps resounded with a "click click click"
The situation is uncertain, not to mention the dull weather instable
A gaze which glared bewitchingly...
I saw within overlaid palms
a crimson spirit with the name “resolution”
"Ringing thunder, cleave through this silence,"
a lost heart cries out
Within those eyes, the proof of a vow
Burn intensely, intensely,
sun blooming within the darkness
Words cursed with a blade only 3 cm
When the drum is beat, that smile will disappear, ah...
A clicking tongue, who was the cause of that sigh?
The same is for tonight,
causing a pale soul to overflow
Love, dreams, a handful of fate
Not a single one can be defiled
In the uneasing light of the moon,
what, who will you save?
The nameless stray cat held back a yawn
In ones, twos, flower petals fall
A dazzling flash of light illuminated the lone path
Love, dreams too, a handful of fate
Not a single one can be defiled
In the uneasing light of the moon,
who do you think of?
"Ringing thunder, cleave through this silence,"
a lost heart cries out
Within those eyes, the proof of a vow
Burn, burn,
sun blooming within the darkness
illust & design　 Kawano
sound engineer　 TomodachiBoshuuP