Ume flowers majestically blooming, known to none...
Number Zero
Attendance Number Zero
Sho Chiku Bai
Pine|Bamboo|Plum
Ebisu Private Middle School Grade 1 Class 1
Attendance Number 0
Birthday: January 18, 1999
Blood Type: AB
Hometown: Tokyo Metropolitan Area
Special Skill: Floating Tea Stalks Vertically
Ebisu Private Middle School
(Ume, ume, ume, ume...)
Whenever the topic of flowers in spring rolls around,
it's all "sakura this, sakura that"
Well, you know what else has gotten past winter just the same?
Sweet, fragrant ume flowers
What's up with this? We're treated differently
And of the Three Friends of Winter, ume comes last!
Not a single person will turn to look at us
Not one! Seriously, no one! I can't believe this!
When it comes to flower viewing, it's sakura
Graduation ceremony? Sakura, too
Argh! We're always the runner-up
I'm blooming, too
Senpai...! Sakura-senpai...!! I-I'm Koume, Matsutake Koume. So you came here once again, huh...? Oh yeah,
ever since I met you one of those days, I've been trying all sorts of things, this and that, and finally made
them float vertically. Made what? Tea stalks, I made the tea stalks stand again! Feels like something good
might happen　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　 today. Koume's
heart just won't　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　stop racing! By
the way, the　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　   blizzard of
falling sakura　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　petals is pretty
beautiful today　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　 too, and watching
you stand here　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　  for such a long
time, I just can't　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　help but worry...
Huh? Why is　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　that, you ask?
Well y'see, you're　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　wrapped in all
these flower　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　petals, it gives
me the kind of　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　feeling like you
might be taken　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　   away at any
moment..., Oh,　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　but please don't
worry, because　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　when or if that
happens, I'll definitely come bring you back, Senpai, just like how you've always been the one there, giving
me bits of your advice or just a second opinion when I needed one. You're a real lifesaver. That's why, some
My scent is sweet through and through
Sigh... Sakura, these tea stalks are the kind that stand
all on　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　 　 their
own, so　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　I'm not
the one　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　who's making
them stand,　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　am I... I mean,
Koume　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　 isn't, so...
there's　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　 something
I'd like　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　    know..."
No matter how much time goes by, Sakura never changes.
Oh, love me, please
Ebisu Private
Middle School
"Monologue"
Matsutake
Koume
Sakura-senpai is a high school girl, 3 grades above me, from the next town over. She's a super cool senpai whom I respect. She's a calm and collected, mature, wonderful big sister who always comes help me out whenever I've got any troubles. Her figure blown by the spring wind, like a sakura petal, is so lovely and elegant, I've fallen head over heels watching her. I haven't forgotten our first encounter, even now. It was a very windy day. I was on the road most students take home, the blizzard of sakura petals raining along the avenue, and there Sakura-senpai quietly stood, looking dignified. Her thin, light brown,
long hair swaying in the wind, her whole figure wrapped in sakura petals... The moment I saw her, my feet uncon- sciously came to a stop, that's how lovely she was... I've been chasing after Sakura- senpai ever since that day, hoping I would someday match up to her...
By the way, my tea stalk floated vertically again, just like yesterday. Something wonderful, just like when I met Sakura-senpai, will happen whenever my tea stalk floats vertically. I can't wait for the day my tea stalk floats vertically once again...
Oh, notice me, please
I can't be a sakura!
Seed
Ume flowers, bloom majestically!
Although we can't match up to the sakura,
We've withstood the weight of the snow and survived,
so illuminate spring with that pride!
Soar up into the sky, ume flowers!
Nimbly flutter and flutter, scattering in the wind
Because, for sure, at least one person is watching
For those people, make your flowers bloom!
U-faM-E!
We may not be famous, but even so
Open, flowers of our dreams!
(Ume, ume, ume, ume...)
(R-I-N-A!)
Bloom, bloom, ume flower –
you've endured all the loneliness with your own power
Is it 'cause umeboshi is too sour?
(Hara, hire, hore, hara!)
U-faM-E makes ume
and getting that fame is our dream
Sakura are nice, but sometimes you'd rather have ume
yUM-E!
Ume!
What's everyone's rice ball filling for flower viewing?
That's right, umeboshi are in there
Thought they'd be useful, but then,
it's ignored?! Ignored?! Ignored...
Ume flowers, bloom majestically!
Although you fall to the ground, known by none
Keep living the way only you can
and sing of this shining spring!
Soar up into the sky, ume flowers!
Bring word of the coming of spring!
Although we fall after but an instant
and are trampled underfoot
one of these springs,
we will make our dreams come true
"I thought it was spring." I heard senpai say, "I thought it was spring." No matter where you are at school, it'd always
I tried writing senpai's name on the edge of my desk to see if it'd help, but the girl sitting next to me soon discovered the writing
ot, and tried pretending those manga-like situations were actually happening to me. That is now my number one problem.
more interesting than doing all those things, better than reading the original English texts of Karl Popper, the Tosa Nikki era setting
This is the kind of problem that you can't solve even if you make use of that. I can't handle this.
←Well, no, that's not quite exactly it. It's not like I don't like it or anything. It's just that, well, something which feels so warm.
," and when she said that, her betrayal, it felt as though something was pricking at... ←No, that's not quite right either, sorry.
Everything's just lying in piles, kind of tall enough to make you to go "Ugh," and it's like that "Oh, that was all a dream" feeling
Like some sort of fretfulness, or irritation...I've gradually gotten worse and worse at similes.
aren't they thought of that way, or at least something similar? Because honestly, ume flowers blooming, rather than sakura flowers
is the problem. Besides, like global warming and other related issues, you can't get a grasp on them because they feel so distant
Please, don't sigh, "Ugh, why an ume?"
See, I am who I am
I'm blooming, too
I share many similarities with you. You share many similarities with me.
I am gazing at you. You never once notice me.
That part of you is so beautiful. I wish I could become you. This ume wants to become a sakura.
My scent is sweet through and through
ume
sakura
When an ume attempts to be a sakura, the sakura is the real. However,
(spring = sakura* + α)
梅-ume- is ≠ to 桜-sakura-
(ume ≠sakura* + α)
thus making the ume the fake.
I am not you. You are not me.
However close I am, you do not notice me.
I cannot reach you because of this. I cannot become you. This ume cannot become a sakura.
Oh, love me, please
Triangle
Symbol Likeness
Oh, notice me, please
I can't be a sakura!
Ume flowers, bloom majestically!
Although we can't match up to the sakura,
We've withstood the weight of the snow and survived,
so illuminate spring with that pride!
Soar up into the sky, ume flowers!
Nimbly flutter and flutter, scattering in the wind
Because, for sure, at least one person is watching
For those people, make your flowers bloom!
U-M-E!
We aren't planning on surrendering
our dreams to anyone else
U-M-E!
Closing the distance,
overtaking our rivals
U-faM-E!
We may not be famous, but even so
U-M-E!
Open, flowers of our dreams!