Li
Liar
Pe
Peter
PeterPa
PeterPan
The seasons came
and went,
and the
colors of
summer faded
The chilly
autumn
wind's
scent
And the
shadows at
sunset
stretched
just a bit more,
An important day
coming once a year
『 Those days were nostalgic. 』
That's how
I felt,
I wonder why?
Sobs resound in a large, five and a half tatami room
I gazed into the distance, alone and lonely
If there is a god, then please, don't let these memories
be undone; For something that unusual,
I had wished
By the evening shower, my
『 always 』
was erased
along with the
crowd and
the sound of
cellphones
That was the liar you's
dying "that"
I want to think,
merely a weakling
I realize,
am I
growing up
little by little
as things
are?
A birthday party where the innermost seat is empty
You, always oversleeping,
are late again
At least let me say happy birthday
without being shy
Come on, everyone's here
Our sobs resound,
illuminating this room
A single candle went out
Were you able to catch the last bus without being late?
Please wait up ahead,
because once I arrive,
I'll wake you once again...
Good night.
If god really does exist,
don't let this song be undone
Liar Peter Pan