Waaaah!
Pushed out into the world, we are born!
Adjust to your surroundings!
Jump out, and breathing from the lungs is an emergency must!
Now, make some music - your very first shout!
Happy b-day! The birth of new life!
Hey boy - this world is ruthless
Hey girl - it's a solitary warground
A survival game with no start-overs
Beep beep! Cry all you want
It's no use reaching out desperately
The rule here is that there's no getting by easy
What about my disturbance-free shelter?
I still want to live snug and cozy
Panic upon realizing there's no going back, ever
We are simply poor, helpless beings
Dropped in a wilderness full of unknown creatures, ego, and ambition...
Hold me, mother!
We are born now!
We have always, with tears in our eyes,
searched for a reason to live in this new world
Born now - we have nothing to lose
So we have nothing to fear
Yet powerlessly, ironically, we are born!
A fanfare rises, fever & dance!
This ain't a disco - it's discommunication!
I need to tell you, but I no hablo language!
Speak! Babel will come later - catch up!
The origin of all of humanity
(I am a baby. I am a baby. I'm a baby.)
No matter how great they were
(Yes, yes, yes, yes. I was, once.)
Life continues on
(Fear & fearless, a neverending cycle.)
From the moment they awaken...
"Misfortunes seldom come alone."
No voice - Where we're born...
No choice - Who we'll meet...
In the end, they're not for us to decide
Starting off being a nobody
"For a cute little baby like you..."
Forced to assume an identity
"Baby, let me give you a name!"
An unstoppable rollercoaster ride driven by the forces of fate
And it's too late to get off!
We are born now!
We have always, with tears in our eyes,
been unable to stop ourselves from stepping into a new world
Born now - we are hurt countless times,
and betrayed
But we will never lose hope
Ironically, as if it were love, we are born!
Deep within the darkness, we found a light (To the light...)
Ever drawn to it,
we've crawled our way out of our comfortable world
Through a dark, narrow path (Onwards, onwards...)
All alone (Onto the next world...)
We are born now!
We have always, with tears in our eyes,
searched for a reason to live in this new world
Born now - we have nothing to lose
So we have nothing to fear
Born now! Born now!
For the sake of securing our rebirth,
cast aside your fear, raise your head, and let us go!
Yet powerlessly, ironically, we are born!