(Here we go to the brand-new world!)
Wee-tee too-too kah toh-loo oo-nye
Ah-may koh-koh noo-loo noo-loo
Nee-tye nee-tye boo-dah loo-loo
Towards the wide-open world, here we go!
Chatterbox (Noo-noo toh-toh)
Singing and dancing (Wee-tee noh-lah)
My learning ability is number one! (Koh-koh koh-koh)
Big eater (Ee-day ah-tah)
Funny faces (Doo-loo)
I'm so lucky to have met you
Even if you get up, open your eyes,
this dream can't, won't ever end
In these shining eyes, you're reflected
C'mon, let's go! Yeah!
Wee-tee too-too kah toh-loo oo-nye
Ah-may koh-koh noo-loo noo-loo
Nee-tye nee-tye boo-dah loo-loo
Always together with you
Wee-tee too-too kah toh-loo oo-nye
Ah-may koh-koh noo-loo noo-loo
Nee-tye nee-tye boo-dah loo-loo
Towards the wide-open world, here we go!
Busy busy, livin' it up! Wassup!
Take it easy, throw up your hands!
Up-down, up-down, po-po-pon pon!
All day long, to the break of dawn!
I'll get scolded for playing around too much
but I can't stop having fun!
Trying to stuff everything down in one gulp, it got stuck in my throat!
We'll definitely have lots of failures, but it's our motto to take risks!
Over there, over here, that way, everywhere's in a flurry of activity!
Spin-spin spin-spin whee!!
If I do well,
make sure to pet me more and more, 'kay?
You're the one I want to show more than anyone else
Get excited! Yeah!
Wee-tee too-too kah toh-loo oo-nye
Ah-may koh-koh noo-loo noo-loo
Nee-tye nee-tye boo-dah loo-loo
Everyone has their own color, and so do you
Wee-tee too-too kah toh-loo oo-nye
Ah-may koh-koh noo-loo noo-loo
Nee-tye nee-tye boo-dah loo-loo
Towards the wide-open world, here we go!
Crying and laughing
Getting angry, worrying
Playing around without rhyme or reason
That's how things are supposed to be - here we go!
I love your innocent smile
I love your earnest gaze as well
Even when your shoulders suddenly drop in disappointment,
I'm diligently watching over you
Let's recite the mysterious words linking heart to heart
Oo-nye may-may kah noo-lah
Take off running! Leap out! Here we go!
Wee-tee too-too kah toh-loo oo-nye
Ah-may koh-koh noo-loo noo-loo
Nee-tye nee-tye boo-dah loo-loo
Always together with you
Wee-tee too-too kah toh-loo oo-nye
Ah-may koh-koh noo-loo noo-loo
Nee-tye nee-tye boo-dah loo-loo
Towards the wide-open world, here we go!