Dempagumi.inc
Hello! We are Dempagumi.inc.
Bonjour! Nous sommes “Dempagumi.inc”
A Japanese idol group.
Grupo del idolo japones.
Diàn bo in Chinese
是中文電波
-
Akihabara to all over the world!!!
Please remember us!
Per favore ci ricordi.
Are you ready?
Sind Sie bereit?
Yeah! Here we go!
Mirin! Risa! Nemu! Ei! Moga! Pinky!
Dempagumi!
I'd been bullied and shut myself away in my room
The arcade was the only place where I felt like I fit in
My dreams had fallen apart, and I'd become desperate
But before I knew it, I was here smiling with everyone
The radio was my only friend
I had a horrible case of chuunibyou, and scared everyone away
I uploaded lots of odottemita videos to video-sharing sites
and stayed glued to my PC just for the views
Living in the countryside, I'd always wanted to be like anime and manga characters
Akiba is my holy land, and here I live!
For the longest time, I'd played MMOs, never leaving my room
Because my two hands weren't enough,
I used my feet to push the function keys
Even nobodies like us
are now aiming big!
Sure, make fun of us - that's just fine!
We're long used to that - go ahead!
Dem-dem-dem-dem-
dem-dem-dem-dem-dem-dem-dem-dem!
Dempagumi.inc!
Although we stand on a tiny, tiny, tiny, tiny stage right now
we'll someday take flight into the big, big, big, big world
We'll send everyone electifying dempa waves!
There's no limit to where we can go, we've got nothing to lose
Don't look down on us just because
we started out as less than nobodies!
Today, we'll be struggling all over, making a ruckus
But we're constantly making progress, Monday to Sunday
With our unique style,
we'll win over the whole world!
Before, there was no place I could truly live
Now we'll let off our waves for the sake of our dreams!
Dempa pathos!
Let me tell you how to use “urya-oi”
Please shout it twice after our singing.
Five! Four! Three! Two! One! Go!
Japan! America! Italy!
Urya oi! Urya oi!
France! Spain! Taiwan!
Brazil! China! Singapore!
Urya oi! Urya oi!
World-Wide Dempagumi!
I'm absolutely no good at English!
Urya oi! Urya oi!
Japanese is tough, too!
It's not about words - it's about spirit!
Urya oi! Urya oi!
Dempagumi!!
Even if everything's all jumbled up and
topsy-turvy and makes no sense,
our individual points will eventually form a single line
Many thanks to the me who had cried that day!
I've finally begun to understand why I was born into this world
It's not about yourself, but about
singing for the sake of someone else!
Dempa Big Bang!
I didn't want to go to school. I just played MMOs.
Online, I'm not lonely.
I was the same. I didn't want to
take a single step out of my room.
To me, MMOs were everything.
While fighting an an enemy party
in my favorite MMO, I... saw her.
Yeah. In a rival party.
We were mutual enemies!
I've been a cosplayer ever since I was little!
The world of cosplaying was so cute and radiant, and I'd looked up to it.
I'd always watched her.
She was so small, and shined so bright.
Meanwhile, I couldn't do anything...
Time went by, and I became a high-schooler.
Time went by, and I became the lead maid.
Yet for some reason, the two of us...
....are here together.
I had despaired over my powerlessness.
I didn't know why I was in Akihabara...
There was this girl in the maid cafe I worked at.
She was really cute, and seemed so lonely...
She put a huge smile on my face,
even with my wounded heart.
I wanted to help her out, even just a little.
And so the two of us met...
Mirin! Risa! Nemu! Ei! Moga! Pinky!
Our six lights now combine
to form a single light!!!!
We've crawled through the earth before
We know what it's like to be at the very bottom
Nothing wrong with dreaming big!
We'll make you reevaluate us!
Our name is...
Dempagumi.inc!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
From this small stage, we've got our sights on the world
We'll send you electrifying dempa waves!
There's no limit to where we can go, we've got nothing to lose
Don't look down on us just because
we started out as less than nobodies!
Today, we'll be struggling all over, making a ruckus
But we're constantly making progress, Monday to Sunday
With our unique style, we'll win over the whole world!
Before, there was no place I could truly live
Now we'll let off our waves for the sake of our dreams!
Dempa pathos!
It's not about yourself, but about
singing for the sake of someone else!
Dempa Big Bang!