12. On the Eighth Day,
Before the Rain Stops.mp3
Afterschool, before the rain stops, sing together with me
an awkwardly-made, unsuccessful song still in the works
At least at the very end, I hope that my words reach you - hey...
Tomorrow will be as so kind to us as today,
so don't spend it crying out of loneliness as well - come over here to me
Because I know you can change with one small sliver of courage
Now, don't let go of this hand
Another day alone on the Seibu Line,
shutting myself away in the world of my headphones
I'd been drawing out stories which couldn't possibly be true
Going through what-ifs - even if "the end of the world" were to come,
it'd leave behind utopia and nothing else; those kinds of cliched, overdone miracles
Afterschool, before the rain stops, go search for me
The me who'd kept my true name hidden
Though we'll most likely forget the way we felt without realizing it - hey...
This gentle love song played by machines,
and this unbelievably wonderful fairytale -
I hope, just as much as anyone else does, that they play on into the future,
which is why I now ask this of God
Someone had said this:
"I was happier back then."
Always clinging onto the shadows of the past,
wishing and wishing for something they could never have.
But you and I
reach our hands out towards that summer...
If it's already disappeared,
then let's make it anew.
Onto the traces of interrupted tears, orange overflows
The sunset sky is beautiful as ever, never changing
And were that a lie, I wouldn't mind, so I'd like to say:
thank you for showing me this illusion for just a moment
If everyone is out there, smiling, then that's all I need
Rolling down our cheeks, the voice of the world resounded loud and clear
People called it a "pulse" and listened carefully
We can't learn unless we know pain,
so we gave this shoddily-made organ a name -
we called it a "heart"...
If we must cling onto the days we can no longer return to,
then let's leave them as happy memories and move onwards
Because we've got legs to walk with
and a future to head towards
"Hey, one last thing."
Until the morning sun rises, sing with me
this awkwardly-made, unsuccessful song still in the works
Once we do that, I think my words will reach you
Now, "On the Eighth Day, Before the Rain Stops", go search for me
because I'll always be here in this unbelievably wonderful world,
Don't forget that - that'll never ever change,
so don't let go of this hand
so don't let go of his hand
150P / Matsushita
Yuuki no Natsuki / ETA / YOU
Movie: bunshichi & kenken
End Illustration: Saine
Music & Lyrics: Suzumu