If the wind blows at the command of a dream,
I will sing, without any destination
of dream fireworks, towards the other side of the sky...
Dream Fireworks
Song&Lyrics
Mafumafu
Illustration  Soraneshii
Video  Not-116
Vocals  IA
I've always,
always
been dreaming
and finally,
finally
have found you
The path
the two
of us had
walked
somehow
feels just
so wide
Holding a photo of you,
I rest in solitude
If the wind blows at the command of a dream,
I will sing, without any destination
Could you, within this transient world,
please smile for me?
I've always, always searched for you
and finally, finally have found you
Dressed in yukata in the summer night,
we played around on the way home
Separated by a "see you later,"
the distance between our
hands becomes infinite
I like you, I like no one but you
The day we both ascertained that is already...
Dream fireworks, towards the other side of the sky
Are they disappearing?
Each time we say goodbye,
I feel as if I'll never be able to see you again
This voice will cross through time
It'll reach, right?
Hey...
I've always liked...
If the wind blows at the command of a dream,
I will sing, without any destination
This voice of mine, cross through the moonlit night,
and reach, please...
Once more,
just only once more,
I want to be able to tell you that I'm happy
Once more, just only once more,
all I want is to see you
I like you, I like no one but you
The day we both ascertained that is already...
Dream fireworks, leaving me behind
Are they disappearing?
Hey...