Bloom Within this
Transient Dream World
Come all, now, and listen
Hear of this exceedingly foolish tragedy
After all, we are but human
After all, such is life
C, c, come, firefly!
Ho-ho-hotaru koi!
F, f, face the other way!
A-a-acchi muite hoi!
While you're busy looking to the side,
your happiness will have run off!
Take this colorless world
and paint it over, make it flashy!
■■■■■■■■
Takagi Reni
■■■■■■■■■■■
Ariyasu Momoka
■■■■■■■■■■
Momota Kanako
■■■■■■■■■
Tamai Shiori
Sasaki Ayaka
■■■■■■■■
Takagi Reni
■■■■■■■■■■■
Ariyasu Momoka
Dazzlingly gorgeous; you know, anyone
can be a dreamer for life
What those lives are colored with
color
is love and dreams - that's all
love
dreams
You are a finely-woven flower, so go on and bloom
you
flower
painting of this transient world
An ukiyo-e scroll
We of these cosmos are but a single fragment
squishy
Oh, and what then?
A tattered nightly tragedy
That's just human empathy
It's not reality
Rise, rise, rise up to the heavens!
H, h, hey ho!
Once you face forwards grandly
you'll be able to seize your tomorrow
Take this world of nothingness
and paint it all over, make it flashy!
Ever-changing at will; you know, anyone
should be free to live as they please
Everyone is different,
and is all not fine because of that?
Even the sun, even the moon
Is it all not splendid, each on its own?
painting of this transient world
An ukiyo-e scroll
We of these seas are but a single droplet
Ah, as your heart desires
Surpass the ages wherever you go
Come, you too, let us go see it together
Off to the country where unending enthusiasm begins
With the birds, with the fish
With the wind, and with the flames
And now, the girl has opened the door
painting of this transient world
Ah, an ukiyo-e scroll
We of these cosmos are but a single fragment
Ah, as your heart desires
Surpass the ages wherever you go