The Truth of the Evening
No matter where I go, who I meet, the future has all of its doors closed
Your memories that
had disappeared one
year ago will return.
How?
I asked that
girl with eyes
which looked
straight ahead
If you take this
medicine, everything
of yours can be
made clear, but...
You had once again lost everything
Your pupils are wavering
It doesn't
matter anyways,
because there's
no place for
me to return
to, after all.
Is Ena safe?
I swallowed the medicine
Like the inside of my head could be
burned away, my body convulses in pain
At super speed, the racing scenery asks,
「What’ll you do? How is it?」
The scene visible from that gap
shoots me out
That kind voice, bloodstained sleeve,
and fading temperature...
are already disappearing
Even if I remember and find a solution, my emotions have all their doors closed
You know, the one
who cut up that
person was your
friend.
Why?
I asked you
as I wiped
my teary eyes
Because you’re a
human, those guys
are machines, and
reality is ruthless.
Are you saying that the smile and the voice that’d comforted me,
that everything was a lie?
I don’t know
about that.
But, in the
world that
you lived
in,
「Don't go...Haru.」
the lone human was you
While dragging along the
emotions I can’t get rid of,
I run through the wasteland
In your smile I’d seen the day before yesterday,
「Do you believe? Can you?」
I melt into the daily life of the
machines who’d destroyed mine
without trying to face the me up until yesterday
If I turn that corner, I’ll be able to see you again
I suddenly realize one hand of mine was clutching a weapon dyed in black
This world, and her again, are both deceiving me
The fresh, overflowing blood runs
across your legs, dying the earth
Even though they're machines,
they're imitating people?
「Really? How is it?」
「Let’s go」
that girl whispers to me,
reflected in her pitying eyes
I had a crazed face dyed
in red like the setting sun
The Truth of the Evening