Evening
Dye
With the flickering flashlight,
you quietly melt away
Once I knew it, this dream
had turned all upside-down
The sun sets, and I can
no longer fall asleep
I again miss the night's coming
In this town dyed in evening
A figure held a broken umbrella,
eyes cast downward
Their back truly resembled yours...
Now,
■■■■■■■■■■
If, and just if, you were to taint our tomorrow
■■■■■■■■■
even these scorching days would change
■■■■■
As if to meaninglessly
confirm your existence
Through the
dusk, a voice
echoed
When even the scenery before us
is someday scattered
my very presence
will end up in pieces
Going 'round,
impatience and
summer rumors
I still won't
forget them
But upon
remembrance,
they'll have lost
all purpose
I faked my way through today giving vague smiles
And yet for some reason,
my voice grows quieter...
■■■■■■
If, and just if, I were
to desire a tomorrow
that would be stealing away
your fading fervor
■■■■■■■■■■
Because simply dragging you around selfishly
■■■■■■■
would only be causing you trouble
I know;
no matter how many
words I cover myself in
I know;
no matter how many
words I cover myself in
I know;
no matter how many
words I cover myself in
In the end, I'll always be myself,
shallow and superficial
Oh, how it suffocates me,
I always hated the summer
"Hurry up and turn to night,"
so I had wished,
and wished
These days end
in such simplicity
it makes me
wearisome...
Now,
■■■■■■■■■■■■
If, and just if, we'd been able to turn our backs to the future
■■■■■■■■■■■
and sleep soundly, perhaps we would've been happy
■■■■■■■
We fall into the depths of the dusk
waiting for night to come
Unable to even say good-bye,
I simply pulled your hand along
Those were lovably pathetic days
Vocals
Movie
Avogado6
Music
Balloon