Oh, man!
This is the life.
No but really, nothing's better than otsumami!
These straws are seriously long.
But, like, in the end,
no one's really sure about the meaning of Z.
Shredded squid, please.
They didn't even tell us anything in advance,
how were we supposed to know how to react?
You know what I mean?
Hey, pass me the dried salmon.
Thanks!
Even we were opposed to it,
but it was more like "Majority rule, we're going with Z!" you know?
Yeah, seriously.
Pass me a ray fin.
Got it!
Thanks!
Oh and also,
it's supposed to be "one cream puff a day",
but no one'd be able to pull that off! It's impossible, right?
I mean, if there were that many, then no way!
Kanako, you've been eating ray fins for a while.
That was the first time I asked her to pass me one!
See?
No no, you've definitely been eating them.
I haven't–
I think it's fine. This Z thing.
I mean, doesn't it sound like these people are capable of keeping the peace on Earth?.
If we wear those belts...
To do what we can.
To sing with all of our energy.
To dance with all of our energy.
To protect everyone's smiles.
And that is...
The meaning of Z!
After overcoming countless hardships,
Momoiro Clover is now down to 5 members.
What do the girls think of the
transformation belts suddenly given to them?
Episode 4: Z Legend ~Unending Revolution~
RED!!!
With my wide, wide-open forehead,
my dimples are pitfalls of love!
YELLOW!!!
I'm the group crybaby, spoiled, love eating –
I'm everyone's little sister!!
PINK!!!
Ahrin☆ Yes!! Ahrin☆
Momoclo-chan's idol!
GREEN!!!
Don't look down on me just 'cause I'm small!
My singing and dancing are second to none!
PURPLE!!!
Piiple, puuple, peple, purple,
piiple, purple, piiple, zapping electric shock!!
What can we do for all the people out there who are crying?
Well, we can sing and dance with all we've got!
Let's do this!!
We are idols!
The weekend heroines, Momoclo!!
Clench your fists! Beat up those tears so they won't come back
No rain lasts forever
Believe in the light
We'll strongly, nobly, happily, beautifully
continue to sing on!!
We won't lose!
Get back up!
It's OK!
We're not weak!
We won't give up no matter what! We are
Momoiro Clover!
Z!!!!!!!!!!
Allow me to explain. Momoiro Clover Z is made up of
Momota Kanako, Tamai Shiori, Sasaki Ayaka,
Ariyasu Momoka, and Takagi Reni.
A group of five weekend heroines.
Today, they again fight for their friends, big and small,
performing their hardest!
Hurry, Momoiro Clover Z!
The second verse is starting!
PURPLE!!!
When you can't take it anymore...
GREEN!!!
Just leave it to us!
BLUE!!
Oh...
PINK!!
Although we're full of shenanigans...
YELLOW!!!
We'll put a smile on your face!
RED!!!
Come see us, okay? We'll go see you.
'cause we're always your allies!
Don't feel lonely whenever you're by yourself
Never forget this, okay? We're always
keeping you in our hearts as we sing!
Wachaaaa!
However tough or long the battle gets,
keep on believing and your dreams will someday come true
No night lasts forever
The morning sun will rise!!
Believe in the future and focus on your goal, never giving up
Blaze through the present!
Love you!
I really do!
Trust me, okay?
I'm starved!
We can get stronger! We are
Momoiro Clover!
Z!!!!!!!!!!
Because sadness never lasts for a whole lifetime!!
We are idols!
The weekend heroines, Momoclo!!
Clench your fists! Beat up those tears so they won't come back
No rain lasts forever
Believe in the light
We'll strongly, nobly, happily, beautifully
continue to sing on!!
Not gonna lose!
Stand up!
It's OK!
We're not weak!
We won't give up no matter what! We are
Momoiro Clover!
Z!!!!!!!!!!
And so, everyone's smiles have been protected again.
In order to spread more and more smiles,
sing again tomorrow! Dance again!
Go forth! Momoiro Clover Z
Work! Momoiro Clover Z
Do your best! Momoiro Clover Z!!