"What an embarrassment! He's so clumsy, I seriously can't take it!"
"Always calm and taking it easy - it pisses me off!"
The reputation of that one guy who saved the Earth is all over the place
On the news, on clouds, on his high horse
Again declaring that it's no sweat
Overconfidence is your greatest enemy
That's right, he needs a good lecture!
(Ready yourself!)
Isn't it about time you understood your position as protagonist, master?
You take too long to get serious - you're enjoying your battles too much!
Also, could you stop cracking jokes when you're in a tough spot?! I'm worried!
Who's supposed to teach us the meaning of "courage" if you end up in disaster?
Once people learn that even the future they'd believed to be eternal
could be destroyed at any time, they are reborn as warriors
The first step is to protect the small dream that's grown in my heart
Will I be able to protect it from being crushed by the darkness?
Those sorts of doubts are also our duty - Team "Z"
Our Z Pledge
Putting my hands together and charging them with ki
Someday I'll let loose a kamehameha!
All that came out was a sigh
All that flew was a single tissue
Nothing goes as planned
Biting away at my nails
In that case, I'll cheer you on!
Here it comes! Lecture number 4
(Be patient!)
You're taking a few punches on purpose
for some laughs from the crowd, aren't you, master?
My heart can't handle it! The suspense is too much!
On the weekends, you must feel the fatigue from living a life out of the norm
But your unfailing mischievous smile is the proof of a hero
The protectors of the future, called heroes
Have long passed down love and hope on this planet
Next up, it's my turn - I'll protect this little dream
Because the morning waits beyond the darkness
Why had you given up?
You'd believed that there was nothing you could do, all propaganda of despair
The song of the beginning echoes
The "Z" flag flies in the wind
Now, let's go - our comrades await
To the future....
Once people learn that even the future they'd believed to be eternal
could be destroyed at any time, they are reborn as warriors
The first step is to protect the small dream that's grown in our hearts
That is...
Our "Z" pledge
The protectors of the future, called heroes
Have long passed down love and hope on this planet
Next up, it's my turn - I'll protect this little dream
Will I be able to protect it from being crushed by the darkness?
To be honest, I'm a little worried, but I strongly want to protect it
Troubles and doubt are also part of our duty - Team "Z"