In both love and war, you're allowed to have a strategy.
And that's why I've decided to go with this one.
I'll say this now, but by no means did I mean to run away.
I'm just buying some time.
Sorry it's so sudden, but...
I've liked you for a long time now!
Confession Rehearsal
Enomoto Natsuki
CV:Tomatsu Haruka
Setoguchi Yuu
CV:Kamiya Hiroshi
Aida Miou
CV:Toyosaki Aki
Serizawa Haruki
CV:Suzumura Kenichi
Hayasaka Akari
CV:Asumi Kana
Mochizuki Souta
CV:Kaji Yuuki
■
click
shut...
I'm
off!
Nac-
chan!
Morning~
Sorry,
Did I
keep you
waiting?
No-
pe.
It's
totally
fine.
■
What do
we have for
first period
today?
English.
Didn't I tell
you we had
a quiz?
Wh-
at?!
Serio-
usly?
■
By
the way,
Nacchan,
did you
manage to
tell Seto-
guchi-kun
yester-
day?
Argh!
Let me
tell you
all about
that~
What
is it?
Do
tell.
slump
■
I'm
sorry it's
so sudden,
but...
I've
liked you
for a long
time now!
■
Huh?!
Ju...
■
Just
kidding!
There's
no way
that'd
actually
be true!
Did I
get ya
good?
Natsuki...
you're
really...
wri
ggle
pause...
■
It's a
confession
rehearsal.
Huh?
Rehear-
sal?
■
So?
Was I
cute?
Did
your
heart
skip a
beat?
stare...
D-don't
look at me
like that...
I'm sorry...
■
So you're
gonna get
serious?
■
E-
eh...
Eh
~~
~!
That
was a
lie.
smack
Uu...
trem
ble
Now
we're
even.
■
So,
Who're
you really
going to
confess
to?
■
There's
no way
I can
tell
you!
Ow
ow!!
hit
Hey, c'mon.
Help me
practice～
Guess I've got
no choice.
Yay!
But treat me
to ramen first.
Eeehh?
■
And then,
after that,
we ate at that
ramen place
in front of the
station on the
way back! It
was really
good...
Though it was my
treat...
soft and warm
Wow...
I see...
■
gasp
Wait,
this
isn't
good
at
a
l
!
gasp
Wait,
this
isn't
good
You're cuter
when you're
silent.
Come on,
close
your
legs.
■
How
about
you and
Haruki,
Miou?
Huh?
I...
Things
are
going
nor-
mally!
What's that
supposed
to mean?
It means
what it
means!
■
How
about
you and
Haruki,
Miou?
Huh?
I...
Things
are
going
nor-
mally!
What's that
supposed
to mean?
It means
what it
means!
■
So,
What
about you,
Akari-
chan?
Huh?
Me?
Oh,
don't
worry
about
me.
More
importantly,
we've gotta
think about
Nacchan's
confession
strategy!
Thank
yoooou,
Akari-chan!
So,
What
about you,
Akari-
chan?
Huh?
Me?
Oh,
don't
worry
about
me.
More
importantly,
we've gotta
think about
Nacchan's
confession
strategy!
Thank
yoooou,
Akari-chan!
■
I'll do
my best!
Yeah~!
I'll do
my best!
Yeah~!
■
...!
Akari!
Come to think
of it, you'd
dodged the
question
earlier.
Huh?
What
was it,
again?
We
were
talking
about who
you like...
Wh-
at?!
■
Good
morning!
Morn'.
Hey,
Haruki!
Don't
put your
butt on
people's
desks!
slump...
Good
morning!
Morn'.
Hey,
Haruki!
Don't
put your
butt on
people's
desks!
slump...
■
Good
morning!
Morn'.
Hey,
Haruki!
Don't
put your
butt on
people's
desks!
slump...
■
Just
warming
it up for
you.
Who
d'you
think you
are, Hide-
yoshi?!
Natsuki...
so you
know who
Hideyoshi
is, huh?
Of
co-
urse
i do!
...wait,
Mochita,
what's
wrong?
...oh,
nothing
really.
■
Just
warming
it up for
you.
Who
d'you
think you
are, Hide-
yoshi?!
Natsuki...
so you
know who
Hideyoshi
is, huh?
Of
co-
urse
i do!
...wait,
Mochita,
what's
wrong?
...oh,
nothing
really.
■
ding
dong
dang
chatter
■
Ah.
Haruki,
some-
one's
waiting
for
you.
Got it,
I'm co-
ming.
See
you
tomor-
row!
■
Are
those
two going
out?
Beats
me...
■
Yuu~...
When they say,
"A single love
continuing for
a long time,"
They mean
"unrequited
love"...
■
I know,
I get
what
you
mean
So
you don't
need to
say any
more...
Let's go grab
ramen.
■
I'm
home.
■
Wah,
no, that's
not it!
Hina-chan!
A-ah!
Watch
out!
Wai-
Nacchan,
what're
you do-
ing?!
click
■
Just
what're
you two
doing in
someone
else's
room...
Ah,
onii-chan!
Welcome
home!
Welcome back.
You're so late!
Where've you
been?
Does it
really
matter?
It's a
confession
rehearsal.
■
Is it
alright
for you to be
over at a guy's
house this
late?
Huh?
Why?
You're
an ex-
ception,
aren't
you?
■
So,
what'd you
come here
for today?
Hehe~
I was thi-
nking you
could help
me with
home-
work-
So,
not for
the ga-
mes...
Of
course
not!
■
So,
what'd you
come here
for today?
Hehe~
I was thi-
nking you
could help
me with
home-
work,
So,
not for
the ga-
mes...
Of
course
not!
■
So,
what'd you
come here
for today?
Hehe~
I was thi-
nking you
could help
me with
home-
work-
So,
not for
the ga-
mes...
Of
course
not!!
■
tick
tock
Say...
■
If,
If I
happen
to get a
boyfriend...
What would
you do?
tick
tock
Hm?
Well, as
your rehearsal
partner, I'd have
to cheer you
on, right?
■
I see.
Thank
you.
■
...do
your
best.
squeak...
■
Haa.
Of all people,
Why am I her practice
partner...
Although I was the
one who agreed...
■
Who is she
confessing
to...?
Who is she
confessing
to...?
■
Haa...
Are we
going out
or are we
not? I have
no idea...
I don't
have any
courage,
do I...
■
Everyone's
in love, huh.
I wonder if
I'll fall in
love some-
day too....
Who does
she like...?
she like...?!
slap
■
blub
Yuu's kind
and soft-
hearted...
■
Do
your
best.
So he's
always
being a
good
friend
to me,
always
cheering
me on...
■
Even if
I came
to like
someone,
would he
just accept
that for me?
■
Tomor-
row's
the real
deal.
To-
morrow...
tomor-
row, I'll
definite-
ly...
Try
to
con-
fes
s
Tomor-
row's
the real
deal.
To-
morrow...
tomor-
row, I'll
definite-
ly...
Try
to
con-
fes
s
■
ding-a-ling-a-ling
chirp
■
Today's
most favo-
rable sign
is...
■
Yeah!
Cancer,
lucky
you!
Yeah!
Cancer,
lucky
you!
■
All
good!
ding
dong...
■
Mor-
ning!
Nacchan,
good
mor...?
■
What
hap-
pened
to
your
face?
You like
it? I'm
going to
give it my all
today, so
I tried to
up my fe-
minine
appeal...
No,
it's ac-
tually
kinda...
yeah.
Y-
yeah...
Huh?
What?!
We'll be
coming
in for
a bit!
Now,
take
off
that
lip-
sti-
ck...
Fake
eye-
la-
shes
too!
And
after
that,
your
foun-
dation.
Wha-
aat?
Why?!
■
Mor-
ning!
Nacchan,
good
mor...?
What
hap-
pened
to
your
face?
You like
it? I'm
going to
give it my all
today, so
I tried to
up my fe-
minine
appeal...
No,
it's ac-
tually
kinda...
yeah.
Y-
yeah...
Huh?
What?!
We'll be
coming
in for
a bit!
Now,
take
off
that
lip-
sti-
ck...
■
Fake
eye-
la-
shes
too!
And
after
that,
your
foun-
dation.
Wha-
aat?
Why?!
■
Hey,
Yuu.
Hn?
What?
■
You're too
soft-hearted.
If you don't
like it, just
say so.
What's
this, all
of a su-
dden?
You
know
what I'm
talking
about.
No,
I really
don't.
■
If you've
got someone
you like as well,
then you should
be more honest
about it.
Oh, is
he talking
about our
confession
rehearsal?
Did he
hear some-
thing from
Aida...?
■
Be
more
honest?
Hey,
I'm gonna
leave you
behind!
Haruki,
you're the
last person I
want to hear
that from...
Be
more
honest?
Hey,
I'm gonna
leave you
behind!
Haruki,
you're the
last person I
want to hear
that from...
■
Sensei!
I'm
stepping out
for a bit...
Nacchan!
Your textbook's
upside down!!
Um...
Didn't you
buy a bit
too much?
But I've
gotta fill
my stomach
so I can
go off to
war munch
munch...
This will
be it!
ding
dong
dang
clatter
■
Ah-
Wait!
grab
■
...!
Ah...
■
This is
the last
time...
The
last...?
So please
practice
with me.
■
It really,
really is
the
last
time.
It really,
really is
the
last
time.
■
Nac-
chan...
Do
your
best.
■
Well,
since
practice
is over,
I'll be
heading
home
soon.
■
Ah...
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
Ah...
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
Ah...
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
■
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
It's the
real thing...
so
good
luck.
clench
■
Wait.
Wait...!
■
clench
...!
Wait!
I like you!
Huh?
Everything I said about a
confession rehearsal was a lie!
You're the one...
You're the one that I like, so much that I can't take it!
I'm not very girly,
get jealous easily, and I don't like it
when I'm not taken out on dates often…
I'm a self-centered idiot, but...
but...
I want you to go out with me!
...heh.
Obviously,
I'm the only one that could put up with you, right?
Me too.
I feel the same way.
■
I wonder
if Nacchan
pulled
it off.
Was she
able to
tell him
how she
feels…?
I-
■
What's
wrong?
No...
it's
just...
■
Ha...
Haruki-kun,
do you have
a crush on
anyone?
Eh?
■
Awawa,
what am
I even
saying...
Ah,
no,
um...
■
Yeah,
I do.
■
I do
have a
crush.
■
Ah...
I
see.
■
How
about
you?
■
I do.
clench...
■
I see.
Oh, I just remembered I had something to do,
so I'll be going home now.
See you later, then...
It isn't me!?
Just who could it be...the one she likes...
It isn't me...
He said that he has someone he likes already.
I was the only who thought...
Yeah.
But, I don't want to give up.
Yeah. I know...
Come to think of it, I've got cake at home!
Huh?
It's a new menu item from the Hoshiya across the station!
Will you eat some?
Yeah!!
I can allow myself to eat sweets just for today, can't I?
C'mon, Akari-chan! Let's hurry!
'kay! Time to stuff myself!
■
Ah,
Akari
chan~
Miou-
chan!
What's
up?
■
Which store
did you buy
yesterday’s
cake from,
again?
■
Hoshiya.
Did you
like it?
Yep.
Then,
let’s
eat
there
next
time!
Yeah!
Their
lemon
tart
is
seri-
ously
deli-
cious!!
■
I'm
glad.
■
I’m glad
that you’ve
cheered up.
■
Love
sure is
compli-
cated...
■
Love,
huh...
Love
sure is
compli-
cated...
Love,
huh...
■
If I also
find some-
one I like,
I want to
walk home
together...
And
maybe we
could hold
hands...
■
And go
eat cake
too...
Haya-
saka-
san.
...Mochi-
zuki-
kun?
Uh,
umm...
■
I have
some-
thing to
talk to
you
about.
At
4:10 after
school
today,
could
you wait
for me
in this
class-
room?
■
This is
the sec-
ond time
we've
talked.
nod
ding
dong
dang
■
I got so
nervous I
ended up
coming too
early.
What
could
it be...
■
What
if it’s a
confes-
sion...
thump
Th-
there’s
no way
it is!
shake
I mean,
we've only
talked
twice...!
Am I not good enough?!
N-no, I think you're fine...
E-eh...?
Eh?
I-I mean I like you!
Like I said, I like you!
I'd never make you feel sad, and
I'll make sure you're smiling every day!
And, I'd love it if you
made me a bento daily!
It's too much work to make one
every single day, so no thank you.
Seriously?!
Oh, come to think of it, a new cake
shop's opened across from the station!
If you'd like, shall we go there together?
Y-yes!
I'd love to!
■
step
Wh-what
should I do?
I need a topic,
something we
have in com-
mon...
■
Wait, huh? Was my confession even okay
in the first place? Or did she reject me?
But we're going to have cake together,
so it's an after-school date...but wait!
Hayasaka-san said she liked someone,
so... I should make up my mind right
now and ask her...
■
Wait, huh? Was my confession even okay
in the first place? Or did she reject me?
But we're going to have cake together,
so it's an after-school date...but wait!
Hayasaka-san said she liked someone,
so... I should make up my mind right
now and ask her...
flinch
■
Wait, huh? Was my confession even okay
in the first place? Or did she reject me?
But we're going to have cake together,
so it's an after-school date...but wait!
Hayasaka-san said she liked someone,
so... I should make up my mind right
now and ask her...
■
Nacchan
and Seri-
zawa-kun
are over
there.
What're
they...
■
You might
be misunder-
standing
something,
but...
■
sneak
I don't
like that
girl.
■
thump
Eh?
Isn't
this
a...
■
I like
you!
■
I like
you!
Yuu's Room
Hm hmhm hmm～
■
Haruki-kun
said he had
something to
do today, so
he couldn’t
walk home
with me…
I won-
der what
it was.
■
Woah
woah
woah!
Cast
Enomoto Natsuki: Tomatsu Haruka
Setoguchi Yuu: Kamiya Hiroshi
Aida Miou: Toyosaki Aki
Serizawa Haruki: Suzumura Kenichi
Hayasaka Akari: Asumi Kana
Mochizuki Souta: Kaji Yuuki
Setoguchi Hina: Asakura Momo
Horoscope Announcer: Shouji Umeka
Surprised Mister: Gom
Sound Director: Nagasaki Yukio
Recording Adjustment: Nogawa "Zill" Seiyuu
Sound Effects: Takanashi Emi
Recording Studio: Sound in Don Juan
Casting: Isokawa Ai
Casting Collaboration: Aoni Production
Sound Production: Milestone Music Publishing
Animation Parts
Original Picture
Scenery
Shooting
Digital Comic: Yamako
Opening Theme
「Confession Rehearsal/HoneyWorks feat.GUMI」
Composition: shito
Lyrics: shito
Arrangement: HoneyWorks
Guitar: Pirate King
Bass: Shito
Piano: Pasta
Ending Theme
「Diagnosis: Lovesickness/HoneyWorks feat.GUMI」
Composition: shito
Lyrics: shito, Gom
Arrangement: HoneyWorks
Guitar: Pirate King
Bass: Shito
Piano: Pasta
Ending Motion: ziro
Special Thanks
Overall Production
Original Work, Script, Storyboarding
Character Design